<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:3">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">12</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">15</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">13</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">6</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">42</age>
		<alignment type="string">Good</alignment>
		<background type="string">Priest</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>background.id-00046@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">I have an elegant locket which hides a fine key in a tiny hidden compartment. I don't know why my wife gave it to me but I will seek that answer no matter how long it takes.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d8</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">5</level>
				<name type="string">Druid</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>class.prodruid@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">53</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">53</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">EP</name>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">50</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">1</armor>
				<disstealth type="number">0</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">13</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">65</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">130</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">390</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">86.1</load>
			<max type="number">195</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">0</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">1200</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Druidic</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You know Druidic, the secret language of druids. You can speak the language and use it to leave hidden messages. You and others who know this language automatically spot such a message. Others spot the message's presence with a successful DC 15 Wisdom (Perception) check but can't decipher it without magic.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Drawing on the divine essence of nature itself, you can cast spells to shape that essence to your will.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="lists.spells.druid@Incarnate-Engine">Druid Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you know two cantrips of your choice from the druid spell list. You learn additional druid cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Druid table.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00038@Incarnate-Engine">The Druid</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Druid table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these druid spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of druid spells that are available for you to cast, choosing from the druid spell list. When you do so, choose a number of druid spells equal to your Wisdom modifier + your druid level (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you are a 3rd-level druid, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With a Wisdom of 16, your list of prepared spells can include six spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination. If you prepare the 1st-level spell <i>cure wounds </i>, you can cast it using a 1st-level or 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can also change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of druid spells requires time spent in prayer and meditation at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Wisdom is your spellcasting ability for your druid spells, since your magic draws upon your devotion and attunement to nature. You use your Wisdom whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Wisdom modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a druid spell you cast and making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<list>
						<li><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</li>
						<li><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</li>
					</list>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast a druid spell as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag and you have the spell prepared.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a druidic focus (see &#34;Equipment&#34;) as a spellcasting focus for your druid spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Holy Man</name>
				<source type="string">Priest</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>After years of prayer and seeking after the divine you have become sensitive to what is going on in the spiritual realm, as such you can &#34;feel&#34; it when you walk onto holy ground.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Priest - Starting Items</name>
				<source type="string">Priest</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Parcel</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="treasureparcel" recordname="treasureparcels.id-00057@Incarnate-Engine">Starting Items - Priest</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Circle of Life</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>&#147;Peace, my child. Though his wounds are great, his spirit still lingers,&#148; said the totem-draped shaman. The glade filled with a sudden burst of sunlight and the great chieftain&#146;s ragged breathing smoothed and calmed.</p>
					<p>Some say life is the first Circle, the birthright of all druids, but few still practice all its tenets. Druids in this circle draw on positive energy to achieve their goals, granting them remarkable healing powers and the ability to restore the land. These druids, though few in number, are the ones most likely to be seen in villages and on the edge of settlements, rather than tucked away in the deep forest.</p>
					<p>2</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00006@Incarnate-Engine">Circle of Life - Spells</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00007@Incarnate-Engine">Life Energy Recovery</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>6</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00008@Incarnate-Engine">Cleanse the Blight</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>10</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00009@Incarnate-Engine">New Life, New Growth</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>14</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00010@Incarnate-Engine">Cradle of Life</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Circle of Life - Spells</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of Life</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level and above, your connection to positive energy grants access to certain spells. You automatically know and prepare these spells as they become available at the appropriate levels. The spells do not count against any limit of spells known or prepared per day and you gain access to them even if they would not normally appear on the druid spell list.</p>
					<p>Life:</p>
					<p>3rd lesser restoration, healing word</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.lesserrestoration@Incarnate-Engine">Lesser Restoration</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.healingword@Incarnate-Engine">Healing Word</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>5th beacon of hope, revivify</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.beaconofhope@Incarnate-Engine">Beacon of Hope</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.revivify@Incarnate-Engine">Revivify</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>7th death ward, mass healing word</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.deathward@Incarnate-Engine">Death Ward</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.masshealingword@Incarnate-Engine">Mass Healing Word</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>9th mass cure wounds, raise dead</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.masscurewounds@Incarnate-Engine">Mass Cure Wounds</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.raisedead@Incarnate-Engine">Raise Dead</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wild Shape</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd Level, you can use your action to magically assume the shape of a beast that you have seen before. You can use this feature twice. You regain expended uses when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>Your druid level determines the beasts you can transform into as shown in the Beast Shapes table. At 2nd level, for example, you can transform into any beast that has a challenge rating of 1/4 or lower that doesn't have a flying or swimming speed.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td colspan="6"><b>Beast Shapes</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td></td>
							<td><b>Max.</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Level</b></td>
							<td><b>CR</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"><b>Limitations</b></td>
							<td><b>Example</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2nd</td>
							<td>1/4</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying or swimming speed</td>
							<td>Wolf</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4th</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying speed</td>
							<td>Crocodile</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8th</td>
							<td><b>1</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td>Giant eagle</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>You can stay in a beast shape for a number of hours equal to half your druid level (rounded down). You then revert to your normal form unless you expend another use of this feature. You can revert to your normal form earlier by using a bonus action on your turn. You automatically revert if you fall unconscious, drop to 9 hit points, or die.</p>
					<p>While you are transformed the following rules apply:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Your game statistics are replaced by the statistics of the beast, but you retain your alignment, personality, and Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma scores. You also retain all of your skill and saving throw proficiencies, in addition to gaining those of the creature. If the creature has the same proficiency as you and the bonus in its stat block is higher than yours, use the creature's bonus instead of yours. If the creature has any legendary or lair actions, you can't use them.</li>
						<li>When you transform, you assume the beast's hit points and Hit Dice. When you revert to your normal form, you return to the number of hit points you had before you transformed. However if you revert as a result of dropping to 0 hit points, any excess damage carries over to your normal form. For example, if you take 10 damage in animal form and only have 1 hit point left, you revert and take 9 damage. As long as the excess damage doesn't reduce your normal form to 0 hit points, you aren't knocked unconscious.</li>
						<li>You can't cast spells, and your ability to speak or take any action that requires hands is limited to the capabilities f your beast form. Transforming doesn't break your concentration on a spell you've already cast, however, or prevent you from taking actions that are part of a spell, such as <i>call lightning </i>, that you've already cast.</li>
						<li>You retain the benefit of any features from your class, race, or other source and can use them if the new form is physically capable of doing so. However, you can't use any of your special senses, such as darkvision, unless your new form also has that sense.</li>
						<li>You choose whether your equipment falls to the ground in your space, merges into your new form or is worn by it. Worn equipment functions as normal, but the GM decides if it is practical for the new form to ear a piece of equipment based on the creature's shape and size. Your equipment doesn't change size or shape to match the new form and any equipment that the new form can't wear must either fall to the ground or merge with it. Equipment that merges with the form has no effect until you leave the form.</li>
					</list>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Life Energy Recovery</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of Life</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Once per day when you finish a short rest, you can choose expended spell slots to recover. The spell slots can have a combined level that is equal to or less than half your Druid level (rounded up), and none of the slots can be 6th level or higher.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">As much as I pretend to love fighting, I secretly hate hurting others.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">5'9</height>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">38</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Charity - I'm doing what I do so others can benefit. (Good)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">2</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">15 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Vestments</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tiny leather pouch is perfect for keeping your coins close at hand. Just watch out for someone trying to cut it off of your belt.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Coin Pouch - Small</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A holy symbol is a representation of a god or pantheon. It might be an amulet depicting a symbol representing a deity, the same symbol carefully engraved or inlaid as an emblem on a shield, or a tiny box holding a fragment of a sacred relic. Appendix B lists the symbols commonly associated with many gods in the multiverse. A cleric or paladin can use a holy symbol as a spellcasting focus. To use the symbol in this way, the caster must hold it in hand, wear it visibly, or bear it on a shield.</p>
					<p>A holy symbol is a representation of a god or pantheon. It might be an amulet depicting a symbol representing a deity, the same symbol carefully engraved or inlaid as an emblem on a shield, or a tiny box holding a fragment of a sacred rite. Appendix B lists the symbols commonly associated with many gods in the multiverse. A cleric or paladin can use a holy symbol as a spell casing focus, as described in Part 3: The Rules of Magic. To use the symbol in this way, the caster must hold it in hand, wear it visibly, or bear it on a shield.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Reliquary</name>
				<subtype type="string">Holy Symbol</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A druidic focus might be a sprig of mistletoe or holly, a wand or scepter made of yew or another special wood, a staff drawn whole out of a living tree, or a totem object incorporating feathers, fur, bones, and teeth from sacred animals. A druid can use such an object as a spellcasting focus.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Yew Wand</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Wand</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A magical wand.</nonidentified>
				<subtype type="string">Druidic Focus</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">7</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack (Empty)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tin box contains a cup and simple cutlery. The box clamps together, and one side can be used as a cooking pan and the other as a plate or shallow bowl.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mess Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Equipment Kits</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<ac type="number">11</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The breastplate and shoulder protectors of this armor are made of leather that has been stiffened by being boiled in oil. The rest of the armor is made of softer and more flexible materials.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">Yes</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Leather</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Leather Armor</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Some well-crafted leather armor.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">common</rarity>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Light Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 slashing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Scimitar</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Scimitar</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A sharp scimitar.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">priceless</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.heartstone@Incarnate-Engine">Heartstone</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>By concentrating on this stone for 1 minute you are teleported into the Nexus, a place of safety for most adventurers. (It is your ticket back, so guard it with your life.)</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heartstone</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Heartstone</nonid_name>
				<rarity type="string">legendary</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 bludgeoning</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Quarterstaff</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Quarterstaff</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A sturdy quarterstaff.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d8)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00016>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">deep speech</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Infernal</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Celestial</name>
			</id-00004>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">5</level>
		<name type="string">Astral the Dreamer</name>
		<perception type="number">13</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I feel great empathy towards the plight of all living things. I seek to help the hurting.</personalitytraits>
		<powerdisplaymode type="string">action</powerdisplaymode>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">4</prepared>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
			</id-00001>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">4</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">2</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">combat</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Whispering to the spirits of nature, you create one of the following effects within range:</p>
					<list>
						<li>You create a tiny, harmless sensory effect that predicts what the weather will be at your location for the next 24 hours. The effect might manifest as a golden orb for clear skies, a cloud for rain, falling snowflakes for snow, and so on. This effect persists for 1 round.</li>
						<li>You instantly make a flower blossom, a seed pod open, or a leaf bud bloom.</li>
						<li>You create an instantaneous, harmless sensory effect, such as falling leaves, a puff of wind, the sound of a small animal, or the faint odor of skunk. The effect must fit in a 5-foot cube.</li>
						<li>You instantly light or snuff out a candle, a torch, or a small campfire.</li>
					</list>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Druidcraft</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Shillelagh; ATK: [-STR], melee; ATK: [WIS], melee; DMG: [-STR], melee; DMG: [WIS], melee; DMGTYPE: magic</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (mistletoe, a shamrock leaf, and a club or quarterstaff)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The wood of a club or quarterstaff you are holding is imbued with nature's power. For the duration, you can use your spellcasting ability instead of Strength for the attack and damage rolls of melee attacks using that weapon, and the weapon's damage die becomes a d8. The weapon also becomes magical, if it isn't already. The spell ends if you cast it again or if you let go of the weapon.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shillelagh</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch regains a number of hit points equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cure Wounds</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature of your choice that you can see within range regains hit points equal to 1d4 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d4 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Healing Word</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">ability</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atkstat type="string">strength</atkstat>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Flame Blade; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (leaf of sumac)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You evoke a fiery blade in your free hand. The blade is similar in size and shape to a scimitar, and it lasts for the duration. If you let go of the blade, it disappears, but you can evoke the blade again as a bonus action. You can use your action to make a melee spell attack with the fiery blade. On a hit, the target takes 3d6 fire damage. The flaming blade sheds bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for every two slot levels above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Flame Blade</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10</dice>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Moonbeam; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (several seeds of any moonseed plant and a piece of opalescent feldspar)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A silvery beam of pale light shines down in a 5-foot- radius, 40-foot-high cylinder centered on a point within range. Until the spell ends, dim light fills the cylinder. When a creature enters the spell's area for the first time on a turn or starts its turn there, it is engulfed in ghostly flames that cause searing pain, and it must make a Constitution saving throw. It takes 2d10 radiant damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. A shapechanger makes its saving throw with disadvantage. If it fails, it also instantly reverts to its original form and can't assume a different form until it leaves the spell's light. On each of your turns after you cast this spell, you can use an action to move the beam 60 feet in any direction.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d10 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Moonbeam</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a miniature cloak)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch one willing creature. Once before the spell ends, the target can roll a d4 and add the number rolled to one saving throw of its choice. It can roll the die before or after making the saving throw. The spell then ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Resistance</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00020>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level and above, your connection to positive energy grants access to certain spells. You automatically know and prepare these spells as they become available at the appropriate levels. The spells do not count against any limit of spells known or prepared per day and you gain access to them even if they would not normally appear on the druid spell list.</p>
					<p>Life:</p>
					<p>3rd lesser restoration, healing word</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.lesserrestoration@Incarnate-Engine">Lesser Restoration</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.healingword@Incarnate-Engine">Healing Word</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>5th beacon of hope, revivify</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.beaconofhope@Incarnate-Engine">Beacon of Hope</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.revivify@Incarnate-Engine">Revivify</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>7th death ward, mass healing word</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.deathward@Incarnate-Engine">Death Ward</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.masshealingword@Incarnate-Engine">Mass Healing Word</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>9th mass cure wounds, raise dead</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.masscurewounds@Incarnate-Engine">Mass Cure Wounds</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.raisedead@Incarnate-Engine">Raise Dead</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Circle of Life - Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of Life</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Once per day when you finish a short rest, you can choose expended spell slots to recover. The spell slots can have a combined level that is equal to or less than half your Druid level (rounded up), and none of the slots can be 6th level or higher.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Life Energy Recovery</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of Life</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00023>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature and can end either one disease or one condition afflicting it. The condition can be blinded, deafened, paralyzed, or poisoned.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lesser Restoration</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00025>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Common Transformations</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.ape@Incarnate-Battles">Ape</link>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.blackbear@Incarnate-Battles">Black Bear</link>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.crocodile@Incarnate-Battles">Crocodile</link>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.giantgoat@Incarnate-Battles">Giant Goat</link>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.giantseahorse@Incarnate-Battles">Giant Sea Horse</link>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.id-00078@Incarnate-Battles">Reef Shark</link>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.id-00090@Incarnate-Battles">Warhorse</link>
						<link class="" recordname=""></link>
					</linklist>
					<p>Starting at 2nd Level, you can use your action to magically assume the shape of a beast that you have seen before. You can use this feature twice. You regain expended uses when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>Your druid level determines the beasts you can transform into as shown in the Beast Shapes table. At 2nd level, for example, you can transform into any beast that has a challenge rating of 1/4 or lower that doesn't have a flying or swimming speed.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td colspan="6"><b>Beast Shapes</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td></td>
							<td><b>Max.</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Level</b></td>
							<td><b>CR</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"><b>Limitations</b></td>
							<td><b>Example</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2nd</td>
							<td>1/4</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying or swimming speed</td>
							<td>Wolf</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4th</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying speed</td>
							<td>Crocodile</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8th</td>
							<td><b>1</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td>Giant eagle</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>You can stay in a beast shape for a number of hours equal to half your druid level (rounded down). You then revert to your normal form unless you expend another use of this feature. You can revert to your normal form earlier by using a bonus action on your turn. You automatically revert if you fall unconscious, drop to 9 hit points, or die.</p>
					<p>While you are transformed the following rules apply:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Your game statistics are replaced by the statistics of the beast, but you retain your alignment, personality, and Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma scores. You also retain all of your skill and saving throw proficiencies, in addition to gaining those of the creature. If the creature has the same proficiency as you and the bonus in its stat block is higher than yours, use the creature's bonus instead of yours. If the creature has any legendary or lair actions, you can't use them.</li>
						<li>When you transform, you assume the beast's hit points and Hit Dice. When you revert to your normal form, you return to the number of hit points you had before you transformed. However if you revert as a result of dropping to 0 hit points, any excess damage carries over to your normal form. For example, if you take 10 damage in animal form and only have 1 hit point left, you revert and take 9 damage. As long as the excess damage doesn't reduce your normal form to 0 hit points, you aren't knocked unconscious.</li>
						<li>You can't cast spells, and your ability to speak or take any action that requires hands is limited to the capabilities f your beast form. Transforming doesn't break your concentration on a spell you've already cast, however, or prevent you from taking actions that are part of a spell, such as <i>call lightning </i>, that you've already cast.</li>
						<li>You retain the benefit of any features from your class, race, or other source and can use them if the new form is physically capable of doing so. However, you can't use any of your special senses, such as darkvision, unless your new form also has that sense.</li>
						<li>You choose whether your equipment falls to the ground in your space, merges into your new form or is worn by it. Worn equipment functions as normal, but the GM decides if it is practical for the new form to ear a piece of equipment based on the creature's shape and size. Your equipment doesn't change size or shape to match the new form and any equipment that the new form can't wear must either fall to the ground or merge with it. Equipment that merges with the form has no effect until you leave the form.</li>
					</list>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wild Shape</name>
				<prepared type="number">2</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00025>
			<id-00026>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Drawing on the divine essence of nature itself, you can cast spells to shape that essence to your will.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="lists.spells.druid@Incarnate-Engine">Druid Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you know two cantrips of your choice from the druid spell list. You learn additional druid cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Druid table.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00038@Incarnate-Engine">The Druid</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Druid table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these druid spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of druid spells that are available for you to cast, choosing from the druid spell list. When you do so, choose a number of druid spells equal to your Wisdom modifier + your druid level (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you are a 3rd-level druid, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With a Wisdom of 16, your list of prepared spells can include six spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination. If you prepare the 1st-level spell <i>cure wounds </i>, you can cast it using a 1st-level or 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can also change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of druid spells requires time spent in prayer and meditation at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Wisdom is your spellcasting ability for your druid spells, since your magic draws upon your devotion and attunement to nature. You use your Wisdom whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Wisdom modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a druid spell you cast and making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<list>
						<li><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</li>
						<li><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</li>
					</list>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast a druid spell as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag and you have the spell prepared.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a druidic focus (see &#34;Equipment&#34;) as a spellcasting focus for your druid spells.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00026>
			<id-00027>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You know Druidic, the secret language of druids. You can speak the language and use it to leave hidden messages. You and others who know this language automatically spot such a message. Others spot the message's presence with a successful DC 15 Wisdom (Perception) check but can't decipher it without magic.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Druidic</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00027>
			<id-00028>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Restrained; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Grasping weeds and vines sprout from the ground in a 20-foot square starting from a point within range. For the duration, these plants turn the ground in the area into difficult terrain. A creature in the area when you cast the spell must succeed on a Strength saving throw or be restrained by the entangling plants until the spell ends. A creature restrained by the plants can use its action to make a Strength check against your spell save DC. On a success, it frees itself. When the spell ends, the conjured plants wilt away.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Entangle</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">90 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00028>
			<id-00030>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Charmed</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You attempt to charm a humanoid you can see within range. It must make a Wisdom saving throw, and does so with advantage if you or your companions are fighting it. If it fails the saving throw, it is charmed by you until the spell ends or until you or your companions do anything harmful to it. The charmed creature regards you as a friendly acquaintance. When the spell ends, the creature knows it was charmed by you.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st. The creatures must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Charm Person</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00030>
			<id-00031>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">24</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Charmed</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a morsel of food)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell lets you convince a beast that you mean it no harm. Choose a beast that you can see within range. It must see and hear you. If the beast's Intelligence is 4 or higher, the spell fails. Otherwise, the beast must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be charmed by you for the spell's duration. If you or one of your companions harms the target, the spells ends.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can affect one additional beast t level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">24 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Animal Friendship</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00031>
			<id-00032>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: constitution; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: strength; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: dexterity; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
					<id-00005>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: charisma; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">5</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00005>
					<id-00006>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: intelligence; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">6</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00006>
					<id-00007>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: wisdom; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">7</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00007>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (fur or a feather from a beast)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature and bestow upon it a magical enhancement. Choose one of the following effects; the target gains that effect until the spell ends.</p>
					<p>Bear's Endurance. The target has advantage on Constitution checks. It also gains 2d6 temporary hit points, which are lost when the spell ends.</p>
					<p>Bull's Strength. The target has advantage on Strength checks, and his or her carrying capacity doubles.</p>
					<p>Cat's Grace. The target has advantage on Dexterity checks. It also doesn't take damage from falling 20 feet or less if it isn't incapacitated.</p>
					<p>Eagle's Splendor. The target has advantage on Charisma checks.</p>
					<p>Fox's Cunning. The target has advantage on Intelligence checks.</p>
					<p>Owl's Wisdom. The target has advantage on Wisdom checks.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour.</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Enhance Ability</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Sorcerer</source>
			</id-00032>
			<id-00035>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of dirt)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature. The target's speed increases by 10 feet until the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Longstrider</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger, Wizard</source>
			</id-00035>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">3</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Clubs, daggers, darts, javelins, maces, quarterstaffs, scimitars, sickles, slings, spears</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Tool: Herbalism kit</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Armor: Light armor, medium armor, shields (druids will not wear armor or use shields made of metal)</name>
			</id-00003>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Human</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>race.id-00010@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00006_token</token>
		<traitlist>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">slashing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Scimitar</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00014</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Quarterstaff</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d8)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00016</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00002>
		</weaponlist>
	</character>
</root>
