<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:3">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">12</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">15</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">11</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">13</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">5</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">345 (mature adult)</age>
		<alignment type="string">Neutral Neutral</alignment>
		<background type="string">Criminal</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>background.id-00008@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">I owe my guild a great debt for forging me into the person I am today.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d8</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<name type="string">Druid</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>class.prodruid@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">48</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">43</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">EP</name>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">48</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">1</armor>
				<disstealth type="number">0</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">2</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">13</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">65</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">130</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">390</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">88.701</load>
			<max type="number">195</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">404</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">500</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Guild Member</name>
				<source type="string">Criminal</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Like an artisan you belong to a guild but instead of merchants you consort with criminals. You live a comfortable lifestyle without charge, and your guild will grant you protection from any crimes you are charged with. To remain part of the guild you must pay them 10 gold you earn every month. In addition your guild provides for the upkeep of your weapons and your living costs (food) while away from the guild.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Druidic</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You know Druidic, the secret language of druids. You can speak the language and use it to leave hidden messages. You and others who know this language automatically spot such a message. Others spot the message's presence with a successful DC 15 Wisdom (Perception) check but can't decipher it without magic.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Drawing on the divine essence of nature itself, you can cast spells to shape that essence to your will.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="lists.spells.druid@Incarnate-Engine">Druid Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you know two cantrips of your choice from the druid spell list. You learn additional druid cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Druid table.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00038@Incarnate-Engine">The Druid</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Druid table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these druid spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of druid spells that are available for you to cast, choosing from the druid spell list. When you do so, choose a number of druid spells equal to your Wisdom modifier + your druid level (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you are a 3rd-level druid, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With a Wisdom of 16, your list of prepared spells can include six spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination. If you prepare the 1st-level spell <i>cure wounds </i>, you can cast it using a 1st-level or 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can also change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of druid spells requires time spent in prayer and meditation at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Wisdom is your spellcasting ability for your druid spells, since your magic draws upon your devotion and attunement to nature. You use your Wisdom whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Wisdom modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a druid spell you cast and making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<list>
						<li><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</li>
						<li><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</li>
					</list>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast a druid spell as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag and you have the spell prepared.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a druidic focus (see &#34;Equipment&#34;) as a spellcasting focus for your druid spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Circle of Life</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>&#147;Peace, my child. Though his wounds are great, his spirit still lingers,&#148; said the totem-draped shaman. The glade filled with a sudden burst of sunlight and the great chieftain&#146;s ragged breathing smoothed and calmed.</p>
					<p>Some say life is the first Circle, the birthright of all druids, but few still practice all its tenets. Druids in this circle draw on positive energy to achieve their goals, granting them remarkable healing powers and the ability to restore the land. These druids, though few in number, are the ones most likely to be seen in villages and on the edge of settlements, rather than tucked away in the deep forest.</p>
					<p>2</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00006@Incarnate-Engine">Circle of Life - Spells</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00007@Incarnate-Engine">Life Energy Recovery</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>6</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00008@Incarnate-Engine">Cleanse the Blight</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>10</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00009@Incarnate-Engine">New Life, New Growth</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>14</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00010@Incarnate-Engine">Cradle of Life</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Circle of Life - Spells</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of Life</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level and above, your connection to positive energy grants access to certain spells. You automatically know and prepare these spells as they become available at the appropriate levels. The spells do not count against any limit of spells known or prepared per day and you gain access to them even if they would not normally appear on the druid spell list.</p>
					<p>Life:</p>
					<p>3rd lesser restoration, healing word</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00172@Incarnate-Engine">Lesser Restoration</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00150@Incarnate-Engine">Healing Word</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>5th beacon of hope, revivify</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00030@Incarnate-Engine">Beacon of Hope</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00241@Incarnate-Engine">Revivify</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>7th death ward, mass healing word</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00077@Incarnate-Engine">Death Ward</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00191@Incarnate-Engine">Mass Healing Word</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>9th mass cure wounds, raise dead</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00189@Incarnate-Engine">Mass Cure Wounds</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00231@Incarnate-Engine">Raise Dead</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wild Shape</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd Level, you can use your action to magically assume the shape of a beast that you have seen before. You can use this feature twice. You regain expended uses when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>Your druid level determines the beasts you can transform into as shown in the Beast Shapes table. At 2nd level, for example, you can transform into any beast that has a challenge rating of 1/4 or lower that doesn't have a flying or swimming speed.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td colspan="6"><b>Beast Shapes</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td></td>
							<td><b>Max.</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Level</b></td>
							<td><b>CR</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"><b>Limitations</b></td>
							<td><b>Example</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2nd</td>
							<td>1/4</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying or swimming speed</td>
							<td>Wolf</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4th</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying speed</td>
							<td>Crocodile</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8th</td>
							<td><b>1</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td>Giant eagle</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>You can stay in a beast shape for a number of hours equal to half your druid level (rounded down). You then revert to your normal form unless you expend another use of this feature. You can revert to your normal form earlier by using a bonus action on your turn. You automatically revert if you fall unconscious, drop to 9 hit points, or die.</p>
					<p>While you are transformed the following rules apply:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Your game statistics are replaced by the statistics of the beast, but you retain your alignment, personality, and Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma scores. You also retain all of your skill and saving throw proficiencies, in addition to gaining those of the creature. If the creature has the same proficiency as you and the bonus in its stat block is higher than yours, use the creature's bonus instead of yours. If the creature has any legendary or lair actions, you can't use them.</li>
						<li>When you transform, you assume the beast's hit points and Hit Dice. When you revert to your normal form, you return to the number of hit points you had before you transformed. However if you revert as a result of dropping to 0 hit points, any excess damage carries over to your normal form. For example, if you take 10 damage in animal form and only have 1 hit point left, you revert and take 9 damage. As long as the excess damage doesn't reduce your normal form to 0 hit points, you aren't knocked unconscious.</li>
						<li>You can't cast spells, and your ability to speak or take any action that requires hands is limited to the capabilities f your beast form. Transforming doesn't break your concentration on a spell you've already cast, however, or prevent you from taking actions that are part of a spell, such as <i>call lightning </i>, that you've already cast.</li>
						<li>You retain the benefit of any features from your class, race, or other source and can use them if the new form is physically capable of doing so. However, you can't use any of your special senses, such as darkvision, unless your new form also has that sense.</li>
						<li>You choose whether your equipment falls to the ground in your space, merges into your new form or is worn by it. Worn equipment functions as normal, but the GM decides if it is practical for the new form to ear a piece of equipment based on the creature's shape and size. Your equipment doesn't change size or shape to match the new form and any equipment that the new form can't wear must either fall to the ground or merge with it. Equipment that merges with the form has no effect until you leave the form.</li>
					</list>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Life Energy Recovery</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of Life</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Once per day when you finish a short rest, you can choose expended spell slots to recover. The spell slots can have a combined level that is equal to or less than half your Druid level (rounded up), and none of the slots can be 6th level or higher.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I have no problem with betraying people who trust me.</flaws>
		<height type="string">3' 7&#34;</height>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">31</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">People - I help people who help me--that's what keeps us alive. (Neutral)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">0</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tiny leather pouch is perfect for keeping your coins close at hand. Just watch out for someone trying to cut it off of your belt.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Coin Pouch - Small</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This pouch of cosmetics, hair dye, and small props lets you create disguises that change your physical appearance. Proficiency with this kit lets you add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make to create a visual disguise.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Disguise Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Kits / Sets</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>These dark clothes are great for sneaking through shadows and dark allys.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Dark Common</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This set of tools includes a small file, a set of lock picks, a small mirror mounted on a metal handle, a set of narrow-bladed scissors, and a pair of pliers. Proficiency with these tools lets you add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make to disarm traps or open locks.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Thieves' Tools</name>
				<subtype type="string">Kits / Sets</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 bludgeoning</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Quarterstaff</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Quarterstaff</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A sturdy quarterstaff.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d8)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield (Wooden)</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Shield</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A well crafted shield.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">common</rarity>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Shield</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">7</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack (Empty)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tin box contains a cup and simple cutlery. The box clamps together, and one side can be used as a cooking pan and the other as a plate or shallow bowl.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mess Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Equipment Kits</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<ac type="number">11</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The breastplate and shoulder protectors of this armor are made of leather that has been stiffened by being boiled in oil. The rest of the armor is made of softer and more flexible materials.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">Yes</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Leather</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Leather Armor</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Some well-crafted leather armor.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">common</rarity>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Light Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A druidic focus might be a sprig of mistletoe or holly, a wand or scepter made of yew or another special wood, a staff drawn whole out of a living tree, or a totem object incorporating feathers, fur, bones, and teeth from sacred animals. A druid can use such an object as a spellcasting focus.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sprig Of Mistletoe</name>
				<subtype type="string">Druidic Focus</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">priceless</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00503@Incarnate-Engine">Heartstone</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>By concentrating on this stone for 1 minute you are teleported into the Nexus, a place of safety for most adventurers. (It is your ticket back, so guard it with your life.)</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heartstone</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Heartstone</nonid_name>
				<rarity type="string">legendary</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1000 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This ring may be attuned to two creatures at a time, one primary, one secondary. To bind as a primary you must make a competing wisdom save against the current primary owner. If you attune and do not win the competition then you bind to the secondary slot. You cannot choose to unatune it, but someone else may attune to it taking over the secondary slot. You may only attempt to take primary ownership during an equinox.</p>
					<p><b>Binding of Engagement:</b></p>
					<p>This ring is attached to your life essence. It magically shrinks to perfectly fit one of your fingers. No one but the primary binding can remove it from you. If you loose the finger/hand/arm then the ring detaches itself and flies to seek out your life essence and reattach itself to you.</p>
					<p><b>Farwatching: </b>the primary individual can see true vision through the ring for 30 ft.</p>
					<p><b>Farspeaking: </b>the primary individual can speak telepathically to the secondary binding.</p>
					<p><b>Prestige 0:</b></p>
					<p>Insight + 2</p>
					<p><b>Prestige 1:</b></p>
					<p>Persuasion Check: +2</p>
					<p><b>Prestige 2:</b></p>
					<p>Wisdom + 4 while wearing the ring.</p>
					<p><b>Prestige 3:</b></p>
					<p>Can see through a solid surface no thicker than 12 inches and with no lead within 20 feet of you.</p>
					<p><b>Prestige 4:</b></p>
					<p>Truesight 30 ft.</p>
					<p></p>
					<p>Add:</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ring of Athena - Prestige 1</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Ring of the Maiden</nonid_name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.001</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">33 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00391@Incarnate-Engine">Potion of Healing</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You regain hit points when you drink this potion.</p>
					<p>The number of hit points depends on the potion's rarity, as shown in the Potions of Healing table. Whatever its potency, the potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</p>
					<h>Potions of Healing</h>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Potion of .</td>
							<td>Rarity</td>
							<td>HP Regained</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Healing</td>
							<td>Common</td>
							<td>2d4 + 2</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Potion of Healing</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Dull Potion</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">The potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<type type="string">Potion</type>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">300 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>These crystal lenses fit over the eyes. While wearing them, you can see much better than normal out to a range of 1 foot. You have advantage on Intelligence (Investigation) checks that rely on sight while searching an area or studying an object within that range.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Eyes of Minute Seeing</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Crystal Lenses</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Two crystal lenses bound together with a little bit of wire.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00020>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Gnomish</name>
			</id-00002>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">4</level>
		<name type="string">Astral the Dreamer</name>
		<notes type="string">Specialization: Trickster</notes>
		<perception type="number">15</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I don't like killing.</personalitytraits>
		<powerdisplaymode type="string">action</powerdisplaymode>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">3</prepared>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
			</id-00001>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">4</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">combat</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00002>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning, magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You and the earth are one. When you are in danger you may summon balls of earth that fly at your enemies. 1d6 bludgeoning damage.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">0</locked>
				<name type="string">Earth Shot - from subrace</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30ft.</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d12</dice>
								<type type="string">poison</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You extend your hand toward a creature you can see within range and project a puff of noxious gas from your palm. The creature must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or take 1d12 poison damage. This spell's damage increases by 1d12 when you reach 5th level (2d12), 11th level (3d12), and 17th level (4d12).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Poison Spray</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Whispering to the spirits of nature, you create one of the following effects within range:</p>
					<list>
						<li>You create a tiny, harmless sensory effect that predicts what the weather will be at your location for the next 24 hours. The effect might manifest as a golden orb for clear skies, a cloud for rain, falling snowflakes for snow, and so on. This effect persists for 1 round.</li>
						<li>You instantly make a flower blossom, a seed pod open, or a leaf bud bloom.</li>
						<li>You create an instantaneous, harmless sensory effect, such as falling leaves, a puff of wind, the sound of a small animal, or the faint odor of skunk. The effect must fit in a 5-foot cube.</li>
						<li>You instantly light or snuff out a candle, a torch, or a small campfire.</li>
					</list>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Druidcraft</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">24</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Charmed</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a morsel of food)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell lets you convince a beast that you mean it no harm. Choose a beast that you can see within range. It must see and hear you. If the beast's Intelligence is 4 or higher, the spell fails. Otherwise, the beast must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be charmed by you for the spell's duration. If you or one of your companions harms the target, the spells ends.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can affect one additional beast t level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">24 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Animal Friendship</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Charmed</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You attempt to charm a humanoid you can see within range. It must make a Wisdom saving throw, and does so with advantage if you or your companions are fighting it. If it fails the saving throw, it is charmed by you until the spell ends or until you or your companions do anything harmful to it. The charmed creature regards you as a friendly acquaintance. When the spell ends, the creature knows it was charmed by you.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st. The creatures must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Charm Person</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a drop of water if creating water or a few grains of sand if destroying it)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You either create or destroy water.</p>
					<p><b>Create Water </b>. You create up to 10 gallons of clean water within range in an open container. Alternatively, the water falls as rain in a 30-foot cube within range, extinguishing exposed flames in the area.</p>
					<p><b>Destroy Water </b>. You destroy up to 10 gallons of water in an open container within range. Alternatively, you destroy fog in a 30-foot cube within range.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you create or destroy 10 additional gallons of water, or the size of the cube increases by 5 feet, for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Create or Destroy Water</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch regains a number of hit points equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cure Wounds</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any. The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Magic</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a yew leaf)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you can sense the presence and location of poisons, poisonous creatures, and diseases within 30 feet of you. You also identify the kind of poison, poisonous creature, or disease in each case. The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Poison and Disease</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Restrained; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Grasping weeds and vines sprout from the ground in a 20-foot square starting from a point within range. For the duration, these plants turn the ground in the area into difficult terrain. A creature in the area when you cast the spell must succeed on a Strength saving throw or be restrained by the entangling plants until the spell ends. A creature restrained by the plants can use its action to make a Strength check against your spell save DC. On a success, it frees itself. When the spell ends, the conjured plants wilt away.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Entangle</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">90 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">GRANTADVATK; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Each object in a 20-foot cube within range is outlined in blue, green, or violet light (your choice). Any creature in the area when the spell is cast is also outlined in light if it fails a Dexterity saving throw. For the duration, objects and affected creatures shed dim light in a 10-foot radius. Any attack roll against an affected creature or object has advantage if the attacker can see it, and the affected creature or object can't benefit from being invisible.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Faerie Fire</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid</source>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create a 20-foot-radius sphere of fog centered on a point within range. The sphere spreads around corners, and its area is heavily obscured. It lasts for the duration or until a wind of moderate or greater speed (at least 10 miles per hour) disperses it.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the radius of the fog increases by 20 feet for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fog Cloud</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature of your choice that you can see within range regains hit points equal to 1d4 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d4 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Healing Word - Circle Spell</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a grasshopper's hind leg)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature. The creature's jump distance is tripled until the spell ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Jump</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of dirt)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature. The target's speed increases by 10 feet until the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Longstrider</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger, Wizard</source>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>All nonmagical food and drink within a 5-foot-radius sphere centered on a point of your choice within range is purified and rendered free of poison and disease.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Purify Food and Drink</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain the ability to comprehend and verbally communicate with beasts for the duration. The knowledge and awareness of many beasts is limited by their intelligence, but at minimum, beasts can give you information about nearby locations and monsters, including whatever they can perceive or have perceived within the past day. You might be able to persuade a beast to perform a small favor for you, at the GM's discretion.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Speak with Animals</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">thunder</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A wave of thunderous force sweeps out from you. Each creature in a 15-foot cube originating from you must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, a creature takes 2d8 thunder damage and is pushed 10 feet away from you. On a successful save, the creature takes half as much damage and isn't pushed. In addition, unsecured objects that are completely within the area of effect are automatically pushed 10 feet away from you by the spell's effect, and the spell emits a thunderous boom audible out to 300 feet.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Thunderwave</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self (15-foot cube)</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature and can end either one disease or one condition afflicting it. The condition can be blinded, deafened, paralyzed, or poisoned.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lesser Restoration - Circle Spell</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a morsel of food)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>By means of this spell, you use an animal to deliver a message. Choose a Tiny beast you can see within range, such as a squirrel, a blue jay, or a bat. You specify a location, which you must have visited, and a recipient who matches a general description, such as &#34;a man or woman dressed in the uniform of the town guard&#34; or &#34;a red-haired dwarf wearing a pointed hat.&#34; You also speak a message of up to twenty-five words. The target beast travels for the duration of the spell toward the specified location, covering about 50 miles per 24 hours for a flying messenger, or 25 miles for other animals. When the messenger arrives, it delivers your message to the creature that you described, replicating the sound of your voice. The messenger speaks only to a creature matching the description you gave. If the messenger doesn't reach its destination before the spell ends, the message is lost, and the beast makes its way back to where you cast this spell.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: If you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3nd level or higher, the duration of the spell increases by 48 hours for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">24 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Animal Messenger</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a handful of oak bark)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a willing creature. Until the spell ends, the target's skin has a rough, bark-like appearance, and the target's AC can't be less than 16, regardless of what kind of armor it is wearing.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Barkskin</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (either a pinch of dried carrot or an agate)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a willing creature to grant it the ability to see in the dark. For the duration, that creature has darkvision out to a range of 60 feet.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Darkvision</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: constitution; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: strength; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: dexterity; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
					<id-00005>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: charisma; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">5</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00005>
					<id-00006>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: intelligence; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">6</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00006>
					<id-00007>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: wisdom; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">7</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00007>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (fur or a feather from a beast)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature and bestow upon it a magical enhancement. Choose one of the following effects; the target gains that effect until the spell ends.</p>
					<p>Bear's Endurance. The target has advantage on Constitution checks. It also gains 2d6 temporary hit points, which are lost when the spell ends.</p>
					<p>Bull's Strength. The target has advantage on Strength checks, and his or her carrying capacity doubles.</p>
					<p>Cat's Grace. The target has advantage on Dexterity checks. It also doesn't take damage from falling 20 feet or less if it isn't incapacitated.</p>
					<p>Eagle's Splendor. The target has advantage on Charisma checks.</p>
					<p>Fox's Cunning. The target has advantage on Intelligence checks.</p>
					<p>Owl's Wisdom. The target has advantage on Wisdom checks.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour.</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Enhance Ability</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Sorcerer</source>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00025>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You sense the presence of any trap within range that is within line of sight. A trap, for the purpose of this spell, includes anything that would inflict a sudden or unexpected effect you consider harmful or undesirable, which was specifically intended as such by its creator. Thus, the spell would sense an area affected by the alarm spell, a glyph of warding, or a mechanical pit trap, but it would not reveal a natural weakness in the floor, an unstable ceiling, or a hidden sinkhole. This spell merely reveals that a trap is present. You don't learn the location of each trap, but you do learn the general nature of the danger posed by a trap you sense.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Find Traps</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00025>
			<id-00026>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (leaf of sumac)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You evoke a fiery blade in your free hand. The blade is similar in size and shape to a scimitar, and it lasts for the duration. If you let go of the blade, it disappears, but you can evoke the blade again as a bonus action. You can use your action to make a melee spell attack with the fiery blade. On a hit, the target takes 3d6 fire damage. The flaming blade sheds bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for every two slot levels above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Flame Blade</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00026>
			<id-00027>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a bit of tallow, a pinch of brimstone, and a dusting of powdered iron)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A 5-foot-diameter sphere of fire appears in an unoccupied space of your choice within range and lasts for the duration. Any creature that ends its turn within 5 feet of the sphere must make a Dexterity saving throw. The creature takes 2d6 fire damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. As a bonus action, you can move the sphere up to 30 feet. If you ram the sphere into a creature, that creature must make the saving throw against the sphere's damage, and the sphere stops moving this turn. When you move the sphere, you can direct it over barriers up to 5 feet tall and jump it across pits up to 10 feet wide. The sphere ignites flammable objects not being worn or carried, and it sheds bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Flaming Sphere</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Wizard</source>
			</id-00027>
			<id-00028>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a legume seed)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A line of strong wind 60 feet long and 10 feet wide blasts from you in a direction you choose for the spell's duration. Each creature that starts its turn in the line must succeed on a Strength saving throw or be pushed 15 feet away from you in a direction following the line. Any creature in the line must spend 2 feet of movement for every 1 foot it moves when moving closer to you. The gust disperses gas or vapor, and it extinguishes candles, torches, and similar unprotected flames in the area. It causes protected flames, such as those of lanterns, to dance wildly and has a 50 percent chance to extinguish them. As a bonus action on each of your turns before the spell ends, you can change the direction in which the line blasts from you.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Gust of Wind</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self (60-foot line)</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00028>
			<id-00029>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a piece of iron and a flame)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose a manufactured metal object, such as a metal weapon or a suit of heavy or medium metal armor, that you can see within range. You cause the object to glow red-hot. Any creature in physical contact with the object takes 2d8 fire damage when you cast the spell. Until the spell ends, you can use a bonus action on each of your subsequent turns to cause this damage again. If a creature is holding or wearing the object and takes the damage from it, the creature must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or drop the object if it can. If it doesn't drop the object, it has disadvantage on attack rolls and ability checks until the start of your next turn. At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heat Metal</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid</source>
			</id-00029>
			<id-00030>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Paralyzed; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a small, straight piece of iron)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose a humanoid that you can see within range. The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be paralyzed for the duration. At the end of each of its turns, the target can make another Wisdom saving throw. On a success, the spell ends on the target.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you can target one additional humanoid for each slot level above 2nd. The humanoids must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hold Person</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00030>
			<id-00031>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a bit of fur from a bloodhound)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Describe or name a specific kind of beast or plant. Concentrating on the voice of nature in your surroundings, you learn the direction and distance to the closest creature or plant of that kind within 5 miles, if any are present.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Locate Animals or Plants</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00031>
			<id-00032>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a forked twig)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Describe or name an object that is familiar to you. You sense the direction to the object's location, as long as that object is within 1,000 feet of you. If the object is in motion, you know the direction of its movement. The spell can locate a specific object known to you, as long as you have seen it up close-within 30 feet-at least once. Alternatively, the spell can locate the nearest object of a particular kind, such as a certain kind of apparel, jewelry, furniture, tool, or weapon. This spell can't locate an object if any thickness of lead, even a thin sheet, blocks a direct path between you and the object.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Locate Object</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger, Wizard</source>
			</id-00032>
			<id-00033>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10</dice>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (several seeds of any moonseed plant and a piece of opalescent feldspar)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A silvery beam of pale light shines down in a 5-foot- radius, 40-foot-high cylinder centered on a point within range. Until the spell ends, dim light fills the cylinder. When a creature enters the spell's area for the first time on a turn or starts its turn there, it is engulfed in ghostly flames that cause searing pain, and it must make a Constitution saving throw. It takes 2d10 radiant damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. A shapechanger makes its saving throw with disadvantage. If it fails, it also instantly reverts to its original form and can't assume a different form until it leaves the spell's light. On each of your turns after you cast this spell, you can use an action to move the beam 60 feet in any direction.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d10 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Moonbeam</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00033>
			<id-00034>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (ashes from a burned leaf of mistletoe and a sprig of spruce)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A veil of shadows and silence radiates from you, masking you and your companions from detection. For the duration, each creature you choose within 30 feet of you (including you) has a +10 bonus to Dexterity (Stealth) checks and can't be tracked except by magical means. A creature that receives this bonus leaves behind no tracks or other traces of its passage.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Pass without Trace</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00034>
			<id-00035>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVSAV: poisoned; RESIST: poison</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature. If it is poisoned, you neutralize the poison. If more than one poison afflicts the target, you neutralize one poison that you know is present, or you neutralize one at random. For the duration, the target has advantage on saving throws against being poisoned, and it has resistance to poison damage.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Protection from Poison</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00035>
			<id-00036>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
								<type type="string">piercing,magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (seven sharp thorns or seven small twigs, each sharpened to a point)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The ground in a 20-foot radius centered on a point within range twists and sprouts hard spikes and thorns. The area becomes difficult terrain for the duration. When a creature moves into or within the area, it takes 2d4 piercing damage for every 5 feet it travels. The transformation of the ground is camouflaged to look natural. Any creature that can't see the area at the time the spell is cast must make a Wisdom (Perception) check against your spell save DC to recognize the terrain as hazardous before entering it.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spike Growth</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">150 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00036>
			<id-00037>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd Level, you can use your action to magically assume the shape of a beast that you have seen before. You can use this feature twice. You regain expended uses when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>Your druid level determines the beasts you can transform into as shown in the Beast Shapes table. At 2nd level, for example, you can transform into any beast that has a challenge rating of 1/4 or lower that doesn't have a flying or swimming speed.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td colspan="6"><b>Beast Shapes</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td></td>
							<td><b>Max.</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Level</b></td>
							<td><b>CR</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"><b>Limitations</b></td>
							<td><b>Example</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2nd</td>
							<td>1/4</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying or swimming speed</td>
							<td>Wolf</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4th</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying speed</td>
							<td>Crocodile</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8th</td>
							<td><b>1</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td>Giant eagle</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>You can stay in a beast shape for a number of hours equal to half your druid level (rounded down). You then revert to your normal form unless you expend another use of this feature. You can revert to your normal form earlier by using a bonus action on your turn. You automatically revert if you fall unconscious, drop to 9 hit points, or die.</p>
					<p>While you are transformed the following rules apply:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Your game statistics are replaced by the statistics of the beast, but you retain your alignment, personality, and Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma scores. You also retain all of your skill and saving throw proficiencies, in addition to gaining those of the creature. If the creature has the same proficiency as you and the bonus in its stat block is higher than yours, use the creature's bonus instead of yours. If the creature has any legendary or lair actions, you can't use them.</li>
						<li>When you transform, you assume the beast's hit points and Hit Dice. When you revert to your normal form, you return to the number of hit points you had before you transformed. However if you revert as a result of dropping to 0 hit points, any excess damage carries over to your normal form. For example, if you take 10 damage in animal form and only have 1 hit point left, you revert and take 9 damage. As long as the excess damage doesn't reduce your normal form to 0 hit points, you aren't knocked unconscious.</li>
						<li>You can't cast spells, and your ability to speak or take any action that requires hands is limited to the capabilities f your beast form. Transforming doesn't break your concentration on a spell you've already cast, however, or prevent you from taking actions that are part of a spell, such as <i>call lightning </i>, that you've already cast.</li>
						<li>You retain the benefit of any features from your class, race, or other source and can use them if the new form is physically capable of doing so. However, you can't use any of your special senses, such as darkvision, unless your new form also has that sense.</li>
						<li>You choose whether your equipment falls to the ground in your space, merges into your new form or is worn by it. Worn equipment functions as normal, but the GM decides if it is practical for the new form to ear a piece of equipment based on the creature's shape and size. Your equipment doesn't change size or shape to match the new form and any equipment that the new form can't wear must either fall to the ground or merge with it. Equipment that merges with the form has no effect until you leave the form.</li>
					</list>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">0</locked>
				<name type="string">Wild Shape</name>
				<prepared type="number">2</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00037>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">2</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: Disguise Kit, Thieves&#146; tools</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Clubs, daggers, darts, javelins, maces, quarterstaffs, scimitars, sickles, slings, spears</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Tool: Herbalism kit</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Armor: Light armor, medium armor, shields (druids will not wear armor or use shields made of metal)</name>
			</id-00004>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Cliff Gnome</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>race.id-00006@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<senses type="string">Darkvision 60</senses>
		<size type="string">Small</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">2</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">2</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">25</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">25</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00011_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Gnome Cunning</name>
				<source type="string">Gnome</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on all Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma saving throws against magic.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Decrease (already applied)</name>
				<source type="string">Cliff Gnome</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your Intelligence score decreases by 1.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tunneler</name>
				<source type="string">Cliff Gnome</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You know the earth shot cantrip. Intelligence is your spellcasting ability for it.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00001@Incarnate-Engine">Earth Shot</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cliff Jumper</name>
				<source type="string">Cliff Gnome</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain advantage on strength (Athletic) checks made for jumping and rope climbing.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mountaineer</name>
				<source type="string">Cliff Gnome</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain advantage on dexterity checks to tie and secure ropes.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00005>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Quarterstaff</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00005</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">40 lb.</weight>
	</character>
</root>
