<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:3">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">-1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">9</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">4</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
				<save type="number">4</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">18</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">12</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">50</age>
		<alignment type="string">Chaotic Good</alignment>
		<appearance type="string">Leatherbeaten from years of living on the perimeter. I attract no attention as I look like someone people would go out of their way to avoid as if I were a diseased vagabond. My distrust of outsiders is strong and can be overwhelming and out of bounds.</appearance>
		<background type="string">Outlander</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>reference.backgrounddata.outlander@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">My bond is to my friends. I know nothing of clan or tribe nor to be a part. My friends are my life blood as if they were my charges to protect and look after and care for. To die for if warranted.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">0</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d10</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<name type="string">Fighter</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.fighter@DD Xanathar's Guide to Everything Players</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">99</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">104</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">EP</name>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">112</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">0</armor>
				<disstealth type="number">0</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">14</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">60</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">120</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">360</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">108.201</load>
			<max type="number">180</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">456</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">500</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wanderer</name>
				<source type="string">Outlander</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have an excellent memory for maps and geography, and you can always recall the general layout of terrain, settlements, and other features around you. In addition, you can find food and fresh water for yourself and up to five other people each day, provided that the land offers berries, small game, water, and so forth.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style 'Archery'</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You adopt a particular style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the following options. You can't take a Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.</p>
					<p><b>Archery</b></p>
					<p>You gain a +2 bonus to attack rolls you make with ranged weapons.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00413@Incarnate-Engine">Fighting Style - Archery</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Defense</b></p>
					<p>While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00411@Incarnate-Engine">Fighting Style - Defense</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Dueling</b></p>
					<p>When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00414@Incarnate-Engine">Fighting Style - Dueling</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Great Weapon Fighting</b></p>
					<p>When you roll a 1 or 2 on a damage die for an attack you make with a melee weapon that you are wielding with two hands, you can reroll the die and must use the new roll, even if the new roll is a 1 or a 2. The weapon must have the two-handed or versatile property for you to gain this benefit.</p>
					<p><b>Protection</b></p>
					<p>When a creature you can see attacks a target other than you that is within 5 feet of you, you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on the attack roll. You must be wielding a shield.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00415@Incarnate-Engine">Fighting Style - Protection</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Two-Weapon Fighting</b></p>
					<p>When you engage in two-weapon fighting, you can add your ability modifier to the damage of the second attack.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Second Wind</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00416@Incarnate-Engine">Second Wind</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You have a limited well of stamina that you can draw on to protect yourself from harm. On your turn, you can use a bonus action to regain hit points equal to 1d10 + your fighter level. Once you use this feature, you must finish a short or long rest before you can use it again.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Action Surge</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can push yourself beyond your normal limits for a moment. On your turn, you can take one additional action on top of your regular action and a possible bonus action.</p>
					<p>Once you use this feature, you must finish a short or long rest before you can use it again. Starting at 17th level, you can use it twice before a rest, but only once on the same turn.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Arcane Archer</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>An Arcane Archer studies a unique elven method of archery that weaves magic into attacks to produce supernatural effects. Arcane Archers are some of the most elite warriors among the elves. They stand watch over the fringes of elven domains, keeping a keen eye out for trespassers and using magic-infused arrows to defeat monsters and invaders before they can reach elven settlements. Over the centuries, the methods of these elf archers have been learned by members of other races who can also balance arcane aptitude with archery.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="imagewindow" recordname="reference.imagedata.img_arcanearcher_jpg@*"><b>Image: </b></link>Arcane Archer</linklist>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.arcanearcherlore3@*">Arcane Archer Lore</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.arcaneshot3@*">Arcane Shot</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.magicarrow7@*">Magic Arrow</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.curvingshot7@*">Curving Shot</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.ever_readyshot15@*">Ever-Ready Shot</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Arcane Archer Lore</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specialization type="string">Arcane Archer</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level, you learn magical theory or some of the secrets of nature-typical for practitioners of this elven martial tradition. You choose to gain proficiency in either the Arcana or the Nature skill, and you choose to learn either the <i>prestidigitation </i>or the <i>druidcraft </i>cantrip.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.prestidigitation@*"><b>Cantrip: </b></link>Prestidigitation</linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.druidcraft@*"><b>Cantrip: </b></link>Druidcraft
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Arcane Shot - Bursting, Enfeebling</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specialization type="string">Arcane Archer</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level, you learn to unleash special magical effects with some of your shots. When you gain this feature, you learn two Arcane Shot options of your choice (see &#34;Arcane Shot Options&#34; below).</p>
					<p>Once per turn when you fire an arrow from a shortbow or longbow as part of the Attack action, you can apply one of your Arcane Shot options to that arrow. You decide to use the option when the arrow hits a creature, unless the option doesn't involve an attack roll. You have two uses of this ability, and you regain all expended uses of it when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>You gain an additional Arcane Shot option of your choice when you reach certain levels in this class: 7th, 10th, 15th, and 18th level. Each option also improves when you become an 18th-level fighter.</p>
					<h>Arcane Shot Options</h>
					<p>The Arcane Shot feature lets you choose options for it at certain levels. The options are presented here in alphabetical order. They are all magical effects, and each one is associated with one of the schools of magic.</p>
					<p>If an option requires a saving throw, your Arcane Shot save DC equals 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Intelligence modifier.</p>
					<p><b><i>Banishing Arrow. </i></b>You use abjuration magic to try to temporarily banish your target to a harmless location in the Feywild. The creature hit by the arrow must also succeed on a Charisma saving throw or be banished. While banished in this way, the target's speed is 0, and it is incapacitated. At the end of its next turn, the target reappears in the space it vacated or in the nearest unoccupied space if that space is occupied.</p>
					<p>After you reach 18th level in this class, a target also takes 2d6 force damage when the arrow hits it.</p>
					<p><b><i>Beguiling Arrow. </i></b>Your enchantment magic causes this arrow to temporarily beguile its target. The creature hit by the arrow takes an extra 2d6 psychic damage, and choose one of your allies within 30 feet of the target. The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw, or it is charmed by the chosen ally until the start of your next turn. This effect ends early if the chosen ally attacks the charmed target, deals damage to it, or forces it to make a saving throw.</p>
					<p>The psychic damage increases to 4d6 when you reach 18th level in this class.</p>
					<p><b><i>Bursting Arrow. </i></b>You imbue your arrow with force energy drawn from the school of evocation. The energy detonates after your attack. Immediately after the arrow hits the creature, the target and all other creatures within 10 feet of it take 2d6 force damage each.</p>
					<p>The force damage increases to 4d6 when you reach 18th level in this class.</p>
					<p><b><i>Enfeebling Arrow. </i></b>You weave necromantic magic into your arrow. The creature hit by the arrow takes an extra 2d6 necrotic damage. The target must also succeed on a Constitution saving throw, or the damage dealt by its weapon attacks is halved until the start of your next turn.</p>
					<p>The necrotic damage increases to 4d6 when you reach 18th level in this class.</p>
					<p><b><i>Grasping Arrow. </i></b>When this arrow strikes its target, conjuration magic creates grasping, poisonous brambles, which wrap around the target. The creature hit by the arrow takes an extra 2d6 poison damage, its speed is reduced by 10 feet, and it takes 2d6 slashing damage the first time on each turn it moves 1 foot or more without teleporting. The target or any creature that can reach it can use its action to remove the brambles with a successful Strength (Athletics) check against your Arcane Shot save DC. Otherwise, the brambles last for 1 minute or until you use this option again.</p>
					<p>The poison damage and slashing damage both increase to 4d6 when you reach 18th level in this class.</p>
					<p><b><i>Piercing Arrow. </i></b>You use transmutation magic to give your arrow an ethereal quality. When you use this option, you don't make an attack roll for the attack. Instead, the arrow shoots forward in a line, which is 1 foot wide and 30 feet long, before disappearing. The arrow passes harmlessly through objects, ignoring cover. Each creature in that line must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, a creature takes damage as if it were hit by the arrow, plus an extra 1d6 piercing damage. On a successful save, a target takes half as much damage.</p>
					<p>The piercing damage increases to 2d6 when you reach 18th level in this class.</p>
					<p><b><i>Seeking Arrow. </i></b>Using divination magic, you grant your arrow the ability to seek out a target. When you use this option, you don't make an attack roll for the attack. Instead, choose one creature you have seen in the past minute. The arrow flies toward that creature, moving around corners if necessary and ignoring three-quarters cover and half cover. If the target is within the weapon's range and there is a path large enough for the arrow to travel to the target, the target must make a Dexterity saving throw. Otherwise, the arrow disappears after traveling as far as it can. On a failed save, the target takes damage as if it were hit by the arrow, plus an extra 1d6 force damage, and you learn the target's current location. On a successful save, the target takes half as much damage, and you don't learn its location.</p>
					<p>The force damage increases to 2d6 when you reach 18th level in this class.</p>
					<p><b><i>Shadow Arrow. </i></b>You weave illusion magic into your arrow, causing it to occlude your foe's vision with shadows. The creature hit by the arrow takes an extra 2d6 psychic damage, and it must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be unable to see anything farther than 5 feet away until the start of your next turn.</p>
					<p>The psychic damage increases to 4d6 when you reach 18th level in this class.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 6th, 8th, 12th, 14th, 16th, and 19th levels, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score by 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">Caution is indeed thrown to the wind when I percieve danger to friends. I'll almost instinctively put myself in danger even if not actually warranted due to my own perception of the situation. This loyalty to friends and the inner need to do good outweighs my strong erge to survive even though I believe I always will endure and live life as a reckless youth often does.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">6 '</height>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">36</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">FREEDOM! Freedom to do what I want. When I want to. I won't be tied down. I won't interfere with what others want or what they believe. My ideals are my own and they don't need to be shared with others. I must do good in life by others although more importantly for myself. If I'm told to do something the results may seem unpleasant for the one doing &#34;the telling&#34; although eventually I'll do the thing in my own time and in my own way. FREEDOM!</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">4</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<name type="string">Quiver</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">50 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 piercing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Longbow</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Longbow</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A well oiled longbow.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Ammunition (range 150/600), heavy, two-handed</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Ranged Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<ac type="number">11</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The breastplate and shoulder protectors of this armor are made of leather that has been stiffened by being boiled in oil. The rest of the armor is made of softer and more flexible materials.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">Yes</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Leather</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Leather Armor</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Some well-crafted leather armor.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">common</rarity>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Light Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">20</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Quiver</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Arrow</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Arrow</nonid_name>
				<subtype type="string">Ammunition</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">0.05</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 slashing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Scimitar</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Scimitar</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A sharp scimitar.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">priceless</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00503@Incarnate-Engine">Heartstone</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>By concentrating on this stone for 1 minute you are teleported into the Nexus, a place of safety for most adventurers. (It is your ticket back, so guard it with your life.)</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heartstone</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Heartstone</nonid_name>
				<rarity type="string">legendary</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1000 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This ring may be attuned to two creatures at a time, one primary, one secondary. To bind as a primary you must make a competing wisdom save against the current primary owner. If you attune and do not win the competition then you bind to the secondary slot. You cannot choose to unatune it, but someone else may attune to it taking over the secondary slot. You may only attempt to take primary ownership during an equinox.</p>
					<p><b>Binding of Engagement:</b></p>
					<p>This ring is attached to your life essence. It magically shrinks to perfectly fit one of your fingers. No one but the primary binding can remove it from you. If you loose the finger/hand/arm then the ring detaches itself and flies to seek out your life essence and reattach itself to you.</p>
					<p><b>Farwatching: </b>the primary individual can see true vision through the ring for 30 ft.</p>
					<p><b>Farspeaking: </b>the primary individual can speak telepathically to the secondary binding.</p>
					<p><b>Prestige 0:</b></p>
					<p>Insight + 2</p>
					<p><b>Prestige 1:</b></p>
					<p>Persuasion Check: +2</p>
					<p><b>Prestige 2:</b></p>
					<p>Wisdom + 4 while wearing the ring.</p>
					<p><b>Prestige 3:</b></p>
					<p>Can see through a solid surface no thicker than 12 inches and with no lead within 20 feet of you.</p>
					<p><b>Prestige 4:</b></p>
					<p>Truesight 30 ft.</p>
					<p></p>
					<p>Add:</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ring of Athena - Prestige 0</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Ring of the Maiden</nonid_name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.001</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00033">Ishepdump - Plant</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ishepdump</name>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">3</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<name type="string">Ash Stake</name>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2,700 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you use an action to toss one of these stones into the air, the stone orbits your head at a distance of 1d3 feet and confers a benefit to you. Thereafter, another creature must use an action to grasp or net the stone to separate it from you, either by making a successful attack roll against AC 24 or a successful DC 24 Dexterity (Acrobatics) check. You can use an action to seize and stow the stone, ending its effect.</p>
					<p>A stone has AC 24, 10 hit points, and resistance to all damage. It is considered to be an object that is being worn while it orbits your head.</p>
					<p><b>Agility (Very Rare) </b>. Your Dexterity score increases by 2, to a maximum of 20, while this deep red sphere orbits your head.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Magic Stone from a Forgotten Time (Agility)</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">an old stone with strange writing in a forgotten language</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">-</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Very Rare (requires attunement)</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">-</subtype>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Contact poison,</p>
					<p>Does 2d8 acid damge. Will corrode any metal it touches after 1 minute. (-1 to attack or AC)</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">0</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Vial of Spifier Poison</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Vial of Spifier Poison</nonid_name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00014>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hammer</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Using a crowbar grants advantage to Strength checks where the crowbar's leverage can be applied.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Crowbar</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Piton</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.25</weight>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Traveler's</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>An arcane focus is a special item - an orb, a crystal, a rod, a specially constructed staff, a wand-like length of wood, or some similar item - designed to channel the power of arcane spells. A sorcerer, warlock, or wizard can use such an item as a spellcasting focus.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Staff</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Staff</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A magical quarterstaff.</nonidentified>
				<subtype type="string">Arcane Focus</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00026>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you use your action to set it, this trap forms a saw-toothed steal ring that snaps shut when a creature steps on a pressure plate in the center. the trap is affixed by a heavy chain to an immobile object, such as a tree or a spike driven into the ground. A creature that steps on the plate must succeed on a DC 13 Dexterity saving throw or take 1d4 piercing damage and stop moving. Thereafter until the creature breaks free of the trap, its movement is limited by the length of the chain (typically 3 feet long). A creature can use its action to make a DC 13 Strength check, freeing itself or another creature within its reach on a success. each failed check deals 1 piercing damage to the trapped creature.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hunting Trap</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">15</weight>
			</id-00026>
			<id-00027>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">priceless... but only to you</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="table" recordname="tables.id-01878@Incarnate-Engine">Random Trophy</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">0</locked>
				<name type="string">Trophy (beholder's eyeball)</name>
				<rarity type="string">Rare</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00027>
			<id-00028>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tiny leather pouch is perfect for keeping your coins close at hand. Just watch out for someone trying to cut it off of your belt.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Coin Pouch - Small</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00028>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Elvish</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Undercommon</name>
			</id-00003>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">4</level>
		<name type="string">Cadavers</name>
		<notes type="string">I never knew my homeland nor my people. I was brought up and edified with whomever would have me. It was my good fortune (or misfortune) to learn of my race and heritage from a group of loving, happy go lucky Wood Elves who always seemed to find tasty mushrooms that's effect was that of pleasant dreams that unfolded before my awakened eyes. My first memories were of these Wood Elves. They taught me what seemed right and good. \n\nThe only items that I have always carried came from where I do not yet know. A pouch which holds a small Beholders eye hard as stone. On the outside of the pouch is an inscrition, &#34;Death makes angels of us all and gives us wings where we had shoulders smooth as Ravens claws&#34; with the letters &#34;J.D.M.&#34; \n\nI do not know of the beholder eye, held securely in my pouch. I have no memory of it. The eye has remained the same and unchanged all these years and I can't help but wander what meaning, perhaps even use; this curious item may possess.</notes>
		<perception type="number">12</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">My actions almost always coincide (or are based off) what my friends are doing (situational). I will rush into danger to help/protect my friends including taking a hit for them. I'm always trying to take advantage of a situation if the action will support my friends/the task at hand. I'm weary of strangers although once a bond is formed from experience/friendship, I would gladly give my life for them. I care nothing for praise or recognition.</personalitytraits>
		<powerdisplaymode type="string">action</powerdisplaymode>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Effect</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Powers</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">POWERS</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<name type="string">Daily Effect Click start of session</name>
			</id-00005>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">combat</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can push yourself beyond your normal limits for a moment. On your turn, you can take one additional action on top of your regular action and a possible bonus action.</p>
					<p>Once you use this feature, you must finish a short or long rest before you can use it again. Starting at 17th level, you can use it twice before a rest, but only once on the same turn.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Action Surge</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell is a minor magical trick that novice spellcasters use for practice. You create one of the following magical effects within range:</p>
					<list>
						<li>You create an instantaneous, harmless sensory effect, such as a shower of sparks, a puff of wind, faint musical notes, or an odd odor.</li>
						<li>You instantaneously light or snuff out a candle, a torch, or a small campfire.</li>
						<li>You instantaneously clean or soil an object no larger than 1 cubic foot.</li>
						<li>You chill, warm, or flavor up to 1 cubic foot of nonliving material for 1 hour.</li>
						<li>You make a color, a small mark, or a symbol appear on an object or a surface for 1 hour.</li>
						<li>You create a nonmagical trinket or an illusory image that can fit in your hand and that lasts until the end of your next turn.</li>
					</list>
					<p>If you cast this spell multiple times, you can have up to three of its non-instantaneous effects active at a time, and you can dismiss such an effect as an action.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Prestidigitation</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Whispering to the spirits of nature, you create one of the following effects within range:</p>
					<list>
						<li>You create a tiny, harmless sensory effect that predicts what the weather will be at your location for the next 24 hours. The effect might manifest as a golden orb for clear skies, a cloud for rain, falling snowflakes for snow, and so on. This effect persists for 1 round.</li>
						<li>You instantly make a flower blossom, a seed pod open, or a leaf bud bloom.</li>
						<li>You create an instantaneous, harmless sensory effect, such as falling leaves, a puff of wind, the sound of a small animal, or the faint odor of skunk. The effect must fit in a -foot cube.</li>
						<li>You instantly light or snuff out a candle, a torch, or a small campfire.</li>
					</list>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Druidcraft</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">day</durunit>
						<label type="string">Fighting Style - Archer; ATK: 2 ranged</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain a +2 bonus to attack rolls you make with ranged weapons.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Daily Effect Click start of session</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style - Archery</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Enfeebling Arrow; Half Damage</label>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00012>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">force</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00012>
					<id-00013>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Enfeebling Arrow; DMG: 2d6 necrotic</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00013>
					<id-00014>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">ability</savedcbase>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savedcstat type="string">intelligence</savedcstat>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00014>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level, you learn to unleash special magical effects with some of your shots. When you gain this feature, you learn two Arcane Shot options of your choice (see &#34;Arcane Shot Options&#34; below).</p>
					<p>Once per turn when you fire an arrow from a shortbow or longbow as part of the Attack action, you can apply one of your Arcane Shot options to that arrow. You decide to use the option when the arrow hits a creature, unless the option doesn't involve an attack roll. You have two uses of this ability, and you regain all expended uses of it when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>You gain an additional Arcane Shot option of your choice when you reach certain levels in this class: 7th, 10th, 15th, and 18th level. Each option also improves when you become an 18th-level fighter.</p>
					<h>Arcane Shot Options</h>
					<p>The Arcane Shot feature lets you choose options for it at certain levels. The options are presented here in alphabetical order. They are all magical effects, and each one is associated with one of the schools of magic.</p>
					<p>If an option requires a saving throw, your Arcane Shot save DC equals 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Intelligence modifier.</p>
					<p><b><i>Banishing Arrow. </i></b>You use abjuration magic to try to temporarily banish your target to a harmless location in the Feywild. The creature hit by the arrow must also succeed on a Charisma saving throw or be banished. While banished in this way, the target's speed is 0, and it is incapacitated. At the end of its next turn, the target reappears in the space it vacated or in the nearest unoccupied space if that space is occupied.</p>
					<p>After you reach 18th level in this class, a target also takes 2d6 force damage when the arrow hits it.</p>
					<p><b><i>Beguiling Arrow. </i></b>Your enchantment magic causes this arrow to temporarily beguile its target. The creature hit by the arrow takes an extra 2d6 psychic damage, and choose one of your allies within 30 feet of the target. The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw, or it is charmed by the chosen ally until the start of your next turn. This effect ends early if the chosen ally attacks the charmed target, deals damage to it, or forces it to make a saving throw.</p>
					<p>The psychic damage increases to 4d6 when you reach 18th level in this class.</p>
					<p><b><i>Bursting Arrow. </i></b>You imbue your arrow with force energy drawn from the school of evocation. The energy detonates after your attack. Immediately after the arrow hits the creature, the target and all other creatures within 10 feet of it take 2d6 force damage each.</p>
					<p>The force damage increases to 4d6 when you reach 18th level in this class.</p>
					<p><b><i>Enfeebling Arrow. </i></b>You weave necromantic magic into your arrow. The creature hit by the arrow takes an extra 2d6 necrotic damage. The target must also succeed on a Constitution saving throw, or the damage dealt by its weapon attacks is halved until the start of your next turn.</p>
					<p>The necrotic damage increases to 4d6 when you reach 18th level in this class.</p>
					<p><b><i>Grasping Arrow. </i></b>When this arrow strikes its target, conjuration magic creates grasping, poisonous brambles, which wrap around the target. The creature hit by the arrow takes an extra 2d6 poison damage, its speed is reduced by 10 feet, and it takes 2d6 slashing damage the first time on each turn it moves 1 foot or more without teleporting. The target or any creature that can reach it can use its action to remove the brambles with a successful Strength (Athletics) check against your Arcane Shot save DC. Otherwise, the brambles last for 1 minute or until you use this option again.</p>
					<p>The poison damage and slashing damage both increase to 4d6 when you reach 18th level in this class.</p>
					<p><b><i>Piercing Arrow. </i></b>You use transmutation magic to give your arrow an ethereal quality. When you use this option, you don't make an attack roll for the attack. Instead, the arrow shoots forward in a line, which is 1 foot wide and 30 feet long, before disappearing. The arrow passes harmlessly through objects, ignoring cover. Each creature in that line must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, a creature takes damage as if it were hit by the arrow, plus an extra 1d6 piercing damage. On a successful save, a target takes half as much damage.</p>
					<p>The piercing damage increases to 2d6 when you reach 18th level in this class.</p>
					<p><b><i>Seeking Arrow. </i></b>Using divination magic, you grant your arrow the ability to seek out a target. When you use this option, you don't make an attack roll for the attack. Instead, choose one creature you have seen in the past minute. The arrow flies toward that creature, moving around corners if necessary and ignoring three-quarters cover and half cover. If the target is within the weapon's range and there is a path large enough for the arrow to travel to the target, the target must make a Dexterity saving throw. Otherwise, the arrow disappears after traveling as far as it can. On a failed save, the target takes damage as if it were hit by the arrow, plus an extra 1d6 force damage, and you learn the target's current location. On a successful save, the target takes half as much damage, and you don't learn its location.</p>
					<p>The force damage increases to 2d6 when you reach 18th level in this class.</p>
					<p><b><i>Shadow Arrow. </i></b>You weave illusion magic into your arrow, causing it to occlude your foe's vision with shadows. The creature hit by the arrow takes an extra 2d6 psychic damage, and it must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be unable to see anything farther than 5 feet away until the start of your next turn.</p>
					<p>The psychic damage increases to 4d6 when you reach 18th level in this class.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Arcane Shot (bursting, enfeebling)</name>
				<prepared type="number">2</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specialization type="string">Arcane Archer</specialization>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10</dice>
								<stat type="string">fighter</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.profighter.features.id-00035@Incarnate-Engine">Second Wind</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Second Wind</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a bit of phosphorus or wychwood, or a glowworm)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create up to four torch-sized lights within range, making them appear as torches, lanterns, or glowing orbs that hover in the air for the duration. You can also combine the four lights into one glowing vaguely humanoid form of Medium size. Whichever form you choose, each light sheds dim light in a 10-foot radius.</p>
					<p>As a bonus action on your turn, you can move the lights up to 60 feet to a new spot within range. A light must be within 20 feet of another light created by this spell, and a light winks out if it exceeds the spell's range.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dancing Lights</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against being charmed, and magic can't put you to sleep.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fey Ancestry</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">GRANTADVATK; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Each object in a 20-foot cube within range is outlined in blue, green, or violet light (your choice). Any creature in the area when the spell is cast is also outlined in light if it fails a Dexterity saving throw. For the duration, objects and affected creatures shed dim light in a 10-foot radius. Any attack roll against an affected creature or object has advantage if the attacker can see it, and the affected creature or object can't benefit from being invisible.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">0</locked>
				<name type="string">Faerie Fire</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid</source>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">DODGE</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You focus entirely on avoiding attacks. Until the end of your next turn, any attack roll made against you has disadvantage if you can see the attacker, and you make Dexterity saving throws with advantage. You lose this benefit if you are incapacitated or if your speed drops to 0.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">POWERS</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dodge</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00010>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">2</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: Flute</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple weapons, martial weapons</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Armor: All armor, shields</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Weapon: rapiers, shortswords and hand crossbows.</name>
			</id-00004>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Dark Elf (Drow)</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.elf@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<senses type="string">Superior Darkvision 120</senses>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">2</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00004_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Trance</name>
				<source type="string">Elf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Elves don't need to sleep. Instead, they meditate deeply, remaining semiconscious, for 4 hours a day. (The Common word for such meditation is &#34;trance.&#34;) While meditating, you can dream after a fashion; such dreams are actually mental exercises that have become reflexive through years of practice. After resting in this way, you gain the same benefit that a human does from 8 hours of sleep.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Keen Senses</name>
				<source type="string">Elf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have proficiency in the Perception skill.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fey Ancestry</name>
				<source type="string">Elf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against being charmed, and magic can't put you to sleep.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sunlight Sensitivity</name>
				<source type="string">Dark Elf (Drow)</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have disadvantage on attack rolls and on Wisdom (Perception) checks that rely on sight when you, the target of your attack, or whatever you are trying to perceive is in direct sunlight.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<locked type="number">0</locked>
				<name type="string">Drow Weapon Training</name>
				<source type="string">Dark Elf (Drow)</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have proficiency with rapiers, shortswords and hand crossbows.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Drow Magic</name>
				<source type="string">Dark Elf (Drow)</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You know the dancing lights cantrip. When you reach 3rd level, you can cast the faerie fire spell once per day (after completion of a long rest). When you reach 5th level, you can also cast the darkness spell once per day. Charisma is your spellcasting ability for these spells.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00006>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<ammo type="number">0</ammo>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">20</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Longbow</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Ammunition (range 150/600), heavy, two-handed</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00002</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">1</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
						<type type="string">slashing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Scimitar</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00005</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attackbonus type="number">-1</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
						<type type="string">slashing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Scimitar (offhand)</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class></class>
					<recordname></recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00003>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">175</weight>
	</character>
</root>
