<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:3">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">1</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">4</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">1</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">1</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">15</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">1</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">8</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">1</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">8</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
				<save type="number">8</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">1</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">18</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">30</age>
		<alignment type="string">Lawful Good</alignment>
		<appearance type="string">Im not a man sum girls think of as handsum. But I aint no hideosity either. Shur I dont got big ripplin musles. And I never been able to gain wate. But Im wiry as heck.</appearance>
		<background type="string">Horse Trainer</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>background.id-00045@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">Shor wish I culd get back home. But wile Im here, wherever here is, I'll do what I wuldnt be ashamed to tell my momma wen I get home. Til then, I lik being around animals as much or more than most peeple.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d8</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">7</level>
				<name type="string">Druid</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>class.prodruid@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">801</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">302</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">EP</name>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">283</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">1</armor>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">13</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<deity type="string">Wats this mean? There aint but one God</deity>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">40</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">80</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">240</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">65.6</load>
			<max type="number">120</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">748</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">800</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Concentrated Training</name>
				<source type="string">Horse Trainer</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can train your mount based on your specialty.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Specialty</td>
							<td>Effect on Mount</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Calm in Combat</td>
							<td>IMMUNE: frightened</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Mounts do tricks</td>
							<td>proficiency in performance</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Arial mounts</td>
							<td>+10 fly speed (only if it already has a fly speed)</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Night Manuevers</td>
							<td>Darkvision 60 ft.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Speed</td>
							<td>+20 ft. walking speed</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Endurance</td>
							<td>+2 constitution, and +10 hp</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bardic Inspiration</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<p>Almost everyone will just play this one by hand with the bardic inspiration die rolled and then added manually, but you may use this varient if you want coding that rolls the inspiration die on the next check, attack roll, or saving throw.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.bardicinspiration@Incarnate-Engine">Bardic Inspiration</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You can inspire others through stirring words or music. To do so, you use a bonus action on your turn to choose one creature other than yourself within 60 feet of you who can hear you. That creature gains one Bardic Inspiration die, a d6.</p>
					<p>Once within the next 10 minutes, the creature can roll the die and add the number rolled to one ability check, attack roll, or saving throw that it just made. The creature can wait until after it rolls the d20, before deciding to use the Bardic Inspiration die but must must decide before the GM says whether the roll succeeds or fails. Once the Bardic Inspiration die is rolled, it is lost. A creature can have only one Bardic Inspiration die at a time.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Charisma modifier (a minimum of once). You regain any expended uses when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>Your Bardic Inspiration die changes when you reach certain levels in this class. The die becomes a d8 at 5th level, a d10 at 10th level, and a d12 at 15th level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Drawing on the divine essence of nature itself, you can cast spells to shape that essence to your will.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="lists.spells.druid@Incarnate-Engine">Druid Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you know two cantrips of your choice from the druid spell list. You learn additional druid cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Druid table.</p>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Druid table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these druid spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of druid spells that are available for you to cast, choosing from the druid spelllist. When you do so, choose a number of druid spells equal to your Wisdom modifier + your druid level (minumum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you are, a 3rd level druid, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With a Wisdom of 16, your list of prepared spells can include six spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination. If you prepare the 1st-Level spell cure wounds, you can cast it using a 1st-level or 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can also change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of druid spells requires time spent in prayer and meditation: at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Wisdom is your spellcasting ability for your druid spells, since your magic draws upon your devotion and attunement to nature. You use your Wisdom whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Wisdom modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a druid spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p><b>Spell Save DC </b>= 8 + your Wisdom modifier + your proficiency bonus</p>
					<p><b>Spell Attack Bonus </b>= your Wisdom modifier + your proficiency bonus</p>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast a druid spell as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag and you have the spell prepared.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a druidic focus as a spellcasting focus for your druid spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Druidic</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You know Druidic, the secret language of druids. You can speak the language and use it to leave hidden messages. You and others who know this language automatically spot such a message. Others spot the message's presence with a successful DC 15 Wisdom (Perception) check but can't decipher it without magic.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Circle of Life</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>&#147;Peace, my child. Though his wounds are great, his spirit still lingers,&#148; said the totem-draped shaman. The glade filled with a sudden burst of sunlight and the great chieftain&#146;s ragged breathing smoothed and calmed.</p>
					<p>Some say life is the first Circle, the birthright of all druids, but few still practice all its tenets. Druids in this circle draw on positive energy to achieve their goals, granting them remarkable healing powers and the ability to restore the land. These druids, though few in number, are the ones most likely to be seen in villages and on the edge of settlements, rather than tucked away in the deep forest.</p>
					<p>2</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.id-00003.features.id-00006@Incarnate-Engine">Circle of Life - Spells</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.id-00003.features.id-00007@Incarnate-Engine">Life Energy Recovery</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>6</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.id-00003.features.id-00008@Incarnate-Engine">Cleanse the Blight</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>10</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.id-00003.features.id-00009@Incarnate-Engine">New Life, New Growth</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>14</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.id-00003.features.id-00010@Incarnate-Engine">Cradle of Life</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Circle of Life - Spells</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of Life</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level and above, your connection to positive energy grants access to certain spells. You automatically know and prepare these spells as they become available at the appropriate levels. The spells do not count against any limit of spells known or prepared per day and you gain access to them even if they would not normally appear on the druid spell list.</p>
					<p>Life:</p>
					<p>3rd lesser restoration, healing word</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.lesserrestoration@Incarnate-Engine">Lesser Restoration</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.healingword@Incarnate-Engine">Healing Word</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>5th beacon of hope, revivify</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.beaconofhope@Incarnate-Engine">Beacon of Hope</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.revivify@Incarnate-Engine">Revivify</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>7th death ward, mass healing word</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.deathward@Incarnate-Engine">Death Ward</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.masshealingword@Incarnate-Engine">Mass Healing Word</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>9th mass cure wounds, raise dead</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.masscurewounds@Incarnate-Engine">Mass Cure Wounds</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.raisedead@Incarnate-Engine">Raise Dead</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">0</locked>
				<name type="string">Wild Shape</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.id-00092@Incarnate-Battles">Wolf</link>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.id-00056@Incarnate-Battles">Giant Wolf Spider</link>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.id-00030@Incarnate-Battles">Giant Badger</link>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.id-00023@Incarnate-Battles">Draft Horse</link>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.id-00007@Incarnate-Battles">Axe Beak</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can use your action to magically assume the shape of a beast. You can use this feature twice, and you regain expended uses when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>Your druid level determines the beasts you can transform into, as shown in the Beast Shapes table. At 2nd level, for example, you can transform into any beast that has a Challenge Rating of 1/4 or lower that doesn't have a fly or swim speed.</p>
					<p><b>Beast Shapes</b></p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Level</b></td>
							<td><b>Max. CR</b></td>
							<td><b>Limitations</b></td>
							<td><b>Example</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2nd</td>
							<td>1/4</td>
							<td>No flying or swimming speed</td>
							<td>Wolf</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4th</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
							<td>No fying speed</td>
							<td>Crocodile</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8th</td>
							<td>1</td>
							<td>-</td>
							<td>Giant eagle</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>You can stay in a beast shape for a number of hours equal to half your druid level (rounded down). You then revert to your normal form unless you expend another use of this feature. You can revert to your normal form earlier by using a bonus action on your turn. You automatically revert to your normal form if you fall unconscious, drop to 0 hit points, or die.</p>
					<p>While you are transformed, the following rules apply:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Your game statistics are replaced by the statistics of the beast, but you retain your alignment and your Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma scores. You also retain all of your skill and saving throw proficiencies, in addition to gaining those of the creature. If both you and the creature have the same proficiency, use only the higher bonus.</li>
						<li>When you transform, you assume the beast's hit points. When you revert to your normal form, you return to the number of hit points you had before you transformed. If you revert as a result of dropping to 0 hit points, however, any excess damage carries over to your normal form. For example, if you take 10 damage in animal form and have only 1 hit point left, you revert to your normal form and take 9 damage.</li>
						<li>You can't cast spells, speak, or take any action that requires hands. Transforming doesn't break your concentration on a spell you've already cast, however, or prevent you from taking actions that are part of a spell you've already cast, such as call lightning.</li>
						<li>You retain the benefit of any feature from your class, race, or other source and can use them if the new form is physically capable of doing so. However, you can't use any of your special senses, such as darkvision, unless your new form also has that sense.</li>
						<li>You choose whether your equipment falls to the ground in your space, merges into your new form, or is worn by it. Worn equipment functions as normal, but the DM decides whether it is practical for the new form to wear a piece of equioment, based on the creature's shape or size. Your equipment doesn't change size or shape to match the new form, and any equipment that the new form can't wear must either fall to the ground or merge with it. Equipment that merges with the form has no effect until you leave the form.</li>
					</list>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">0</locked>
				<name type="string">Life Energy Recovery</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of Life</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Once per day when you finish a short rest, you can choose expended spell slots to recover. The spell slots can have a combined level that is equal to or less than half your Druid level (rounded up), and none of the slots can be 6th level or higher.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting (Bard)</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have learned to untangle and reshape the fabric of reality in harmony with your wishes and music. Your spells are part of your vast repertoire, magic that you can tune to different situations.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="lists.spells.bard@Incarnate-Engine">Bard Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>You know two cantrips of your choice from the bard spell list. You learn additional bard cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Bard table.</p>
					<p><b>Spell Slots</b></p>
					<p>The Bard table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You must finish along rest to regain any expended spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you know the 1st-level spell cure wounds and have a 1st-level and a 2nd-level spell slot available, you can cast cure wounds using either slot.</p>
					<p><b>Spells Known of 1st Level and Higher</b></p>
					<p>You know four 1st-level spells of your choice from the bard spell list.</p>
					<p>The Spells Known column of the Bard table shows when you learn more bard spells of your choice. Each of these spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots, as shown on the table. For instance, when you reach 3rd level in this class, you can learn one new spell of 1st or 2nd level.</p>
					<p>Additionally, when you gain a level in this class, you can choose one of the spells you know and replace it with another spell from the bard spell list, which also must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Charisma is your spellcasting ability for your bard spells, since the power of your magic comes from the heart and soul you pour into the performance of your music or oration. You use your Charisma whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Charisma modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a bard spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p><b>Spell Save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spell Attack modifier </b>= your your proficiency bonus + Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast any bard spell you know as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a musical instrument as a spellcasting focus for your bard spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<level type="number">6</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cleanse the Blight</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of Life</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 6th level, you can disrupt the strength of creatures animated by negative energy and bolster your allies against harmful conditions. A number of times per day equal to half your druid level, rounded up, you can utilize one of the following effects as a reaction:</p>
					<p>When an undead creature within 30 feet attacks a target other than you, you may impose disadvantage on the attack roll.</p>
					<p>You grant an ally within 30 feet advantage on saving throws against one of the following conditions: frightened, paralyzed, or poisoned.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00011>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">Never got the chance for no book larning. Smart guys mak me feel uncomfortable. I kinda withdraw if I feel that way.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">6 feet</height>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">67</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">My momma told me to do wats rite even if its hard. Thats what Im gonna do. I may not no a lot of fancy things, but Gods given me an extra share of common sens. I'll use it to do rite.</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">2</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<damage type="string">1d4 bludgeoning</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Club</name>
				<properties type="string">Light</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">7</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack (Empty)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tin box contains a cup and simple cutlery. The box clamps together, and one side can be used as a cooking pan and the other as a plate or shallow bowl.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mess Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Equipment Kits</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<ac type="number">11</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Made from supple and thin materials, light armor favors agile adventurers since it offers some protection without sacrificing mobility. If you wear light armor, you add your Dexterity modifier to the base number from your armor type to determine your Armor Class.</p>
					<p>The breastplate and shoulder protectors of this armor are made of leather that has been stiffened by being boiled in oil. The rest of the armor is made of softer and more flexible materials.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">Yes</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Leather</name>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Light Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A druidic focus might be a sprig of mistletoe or holly, a wand or scepter made of yew or another special wood, a staff drawn whole out of a living tree, or a totem object incorporating feathers, fur, bones, and teeth from sacred animals. A druid can use such an object as a spellcasting focus.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Yew Wand</name>
				<subtype type="string">Druidic Focus</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">15 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Fine</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This short oak stick has a bundle of tiny tassels at the end making it so that you can hit the horse to encourage it to move, yet not do any damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Horse Whip</name>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tiny leather pouch is perfect for keeping your coins close at hand. Just watch out for someone trying to cut it off of your belt.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Coin Pouch - Small</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">101 - 500 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>While this polished agate is on your person, you gain a +1 bonus to ability checks and saving throws.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Stone of Good Luck (Luckstone) - attuned</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Carved Stone</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A gray stone carved into the likeness of a cat's head with one eye socket containing a green sparkling gem.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon (Requires Attunement)</rarity>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">29 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.animalfriendship@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: Animal Friendship</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>This <u>spell scroll </u>bears the words of a single spell, <i>Animal Friendship </i>, written in a mystical cipher. If the spell is on your class's spell list, you can read the scroll and cast its spell without providing any material components. Otherwise, the scroll is unintelligible. Casting the spell by reading the scroll requires the spell's normal casting time. Once the spell is cast, the words on the scroll fade, and it crumbles to dust. If the casting is interrupted, the scroll is not lost.</p>
					<p>If the spell is on your class's spell list but of a higher level than you can normally cast, you must make an ability check using your spellcasting ability to determine whether you cast it successfully. The DC equals 10 + the spell's level. On a failed check, the spell disappears from the scroll with no other effect.</p>
					<p>Once the spell is cast, the words on the scroll fade, and the scroll itself crumbles to dust.</p>
					<p>This spell scroll's saving throw DC 13 and attack bonus +5.</p>
					<p>A wizard spell on a <i>spell scroll </i>can be copied just as spells in spellbooks can be copied. When a spell is copied from a <i>spell scroll </i>, the copier must succeed on an Intelligence (Arcana) check with a DC equal to 10 + the spell's level. If the check succeeds, the spell is successfully copied. Whether the check succeeds or fails, the <i>spell scroll </i>is destroyed.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Scroll of Animal Friendship</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Fine Scroll</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">The parchment of this scroll is of the finest quality and the writing is careful and delicate.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<spells>
					<id-00001>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class>reference_spell</class>
							<recordname>reference.spelldata.animalfriendship@*</recordname>
						</link>
						<name type="string">Animal Friendship</name>
					</id-00001>
				</spells>
				<type type="string">Scroll</type>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">300 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.id-00034@Incarnate-Battles">NPC: Giant Constrictor Snake</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>You can use an action to speak this staff's command word and throw the staff on the ground within 10 feet of you. The staff becomes a giant constrictor snake under your control and acts on its own initiative count. By using a bonus action to speak the command word again, you return the staff to its normal form in a space formerly occupied by the snake.</p>
					<p>On your turn, you can mentally command the snake if it is within 60 feet of you and you aren't incapacitated. You decide what action the snake takes and where it moves during its next turn, or you can issue it a general command, such as to attack your enemies or guard a location.</p>
					<p>If the snake is reduced to 0 hit points, it dies and reverts to its staff form. The staff then shatters and is destroyed. If the snake reverts to staff form before losing all its hit points, it regains all of them.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Staff of the Python</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Staff</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A magical staff.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">uncommon (requires attunement by a cleric, druid, or warlock)</rarity>
				<type type="string">Staff</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">900 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have resistance to one damage type while wearing this ring.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.typeresistancelightning@Incarnate-Engine">Type Resistance (Lightning)</link>
					</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>5</td>
							<td>Lightning</td>
							<td>Citrine</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ring of Lightning Resistance</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Ring</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A citrine ring.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">rare (requires attunement)</rarity>
				<type type="string">Ring</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">priceless</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.heartstone@Incarnate-Engine">Heartstone</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>By concentrating on this stone for 1 minute you are teleported into the Nexus, a place of saftey for most adventurers. (It is your ticket back, so guard it with your life.)</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heartstone</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Heartstone</nonid_name>
				<rarity type="string">legendary</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 piercing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Javelin</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Javelin</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A strong javelin.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Thrown (range 30/120)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<name type="string">Apple</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2,700 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you use an action to toss one of these stones into the air, the stone orbits your head at a distance of 1d3 feet and confers a benefit to you. Thereafter, another creature must use an action to grasp or net the stone to separate it from you, either by making a successful attack roll against AC 24 or a successful DC 24 Dexterity (Acrobatics) check. You can use an action to seize and stow the stone, ending its effect.</p>
					<p>A stone has AC 24, 10 hit points, and resistance to all damage. It is considered to be an object that is being worn while it orbits your head.</p>
					<p><b>Agility (Very Rare) </b>. Your Dexterity score increases by 2, to a maximum of 20, while this deep red sphere orbits your head.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Magic Stone from a Forgotten Time (Agility)</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">an old stone with strange writing in a forgotten language</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">-</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Very Rare (requires attunement)</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">-</subtype>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1,200 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 piercing, magic</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
					<p>Mithral weapons are light weight and strong. (reduce their weight by half of the normal weight)</p>
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.humanoidslayer@Incarnate-Engine">Humanoid Slayer</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</p>
					<p>When you hit an Humanoid with it, the creature takes an extra 2d6 damage of the weapon's type and must succeed on a DC 15 Strength saving throw or fall prone. For the purpose of this weapon, &#34;Humanoid&#34; refers to any creature with the Humanoid type.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mithral Javelin of Humanoid Slaying</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Javelin</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A strong javelin.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Thrown (range 30/120)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">100 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.potionofgreaterhealing@Incarnate-Engine">Potion of Greater Healing</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You regain hit points when you drink this potion.</p>
					<p>The number of hit points depends on the potion's rarity, as shown in the Potions of Healing table. Whatever its potency, the potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</p>
					<h>Potions of Healing</h>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Potion of .</td>
							<td>Rarity</td>
							<td>HP Regained</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Greater healing</td>
							<td>Uncommon</td>
							<td>4d4 + 4</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Potion of Greater Healing</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Dim Potion</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">The potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Potion</type>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00024>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Draconic</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Elvish</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Sylvan</name>
			</id-00004>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">7</level>
		<name type="string">Corbon</name>
		<perception type="number">18</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I try reel hard to be friendly to folk, but some dont lik me cause I dont no much about the world. But I can tell what peeple think about me reel well. If there mean, I dont have anything to do with them. If there nice, I'll do anything for them. I dont jump into truble, but if my friends in truble, I'll wade rit in to help him.</personalitytraits>
		<powerdisplaymode type="string">action</powerdisplaymode>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">4</prepared>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00003>
				<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<atkstat type="string">wisdom</atkstat>
				<name type="string">Circle of Life Spells (Level 1)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<savemod type="number">0</savemod>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<savestat type="string">wisdom</savestat>
				<uses type="number">0</uses>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Circle of Life Spells (Level 2)</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<name type="string">Effect</name>
			</id-00005>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">4</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">1</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">combat</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">ability</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atkstat type="string">wisdom</atkstat>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning, magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<atkbase type="string">ability</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">0</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning, magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00004>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (mistletoe, a shamrock leaf, and a club or quarterstaff)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The wood of a club or quarterstaff you are holding is imbued with nature's power. For the duration, you can use your spellcasting ability instead of Strength for the attack and damage rolls of melee attacks using that weapon, and the weapon's damage die becomes a d8. The weapon also becomes magical, if it isn't already. The spell ends if you cast it again or if you let go of the weapon.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shillelagh</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">thunder</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A wave of thunderous force sweeps out from you. Each creature in a 15-foot cube originating from you must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, a creature takes 2d8 thunder damage and is pushed 10 feet away from you. On a successful save, the creature takes half as much damage and isn't pushed.</p>
					<p>In addition, unsecured objects that are completely within the area of effect are automatically pushed 10 feet away from you by the spell's effect, and the spell emits a thunderous boom audible out to 300 feet.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Thunderwave</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self (15-foot cube)</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature and can end either one disease or one condition afflicting it. The condition can be blinded, deafened, paralyzed, or poisoned.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Circle of Life Spells (Level 2)</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lesser Restoration</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature of your choice that you can see within range regains hit points equal to 1d4 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d4 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Circle of Life Spells (Level 1)</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Healing Word</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="ref_ability" recordname="....featurelist.id-00008">Life Energy Recovery</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Life Energy Recovery</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="ref_ability" recordname="....featurelist.id-00007">Wild Shape</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wild Shape</name>
				<prepared type="number">2</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Fey Ancestry; ADVSAV</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">day</durunit>
						<label type="string">Fey Ancestry; IMMUNE: unconscious</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="ref_ability" recordname="....traitlist.id-00003">Fey Ancestry</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fey Ancestry</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a caterpillar cocoon)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell transforms a creature that you can see within range into a new form. An unwilling creature must make a Wisdom saving throw to avoid the effect. The spell has no effect on a shapechanger or a creature with 0 hit points. The transformation lasts for the duration, or until the target drops to 0 hit points or dies. The new form can be any beast whose challenge rating is equal to or less than the target's (or the target's level, if it doesn't have a challenge rating). The target's game statistics, including mental ability scores, are replaced by the statistics of the chosen beast. It retains its alignment and personality. The target assumes the hit points of its new form. When it reverts to its normal form, the creature returns to the number of hit points it had before it transformed. If it reverts as a result of dropping to 0 hit points, any excess damage carries over to its normal form. As long as the excess damage doesn't reduce the creature's normal form to 0 hit points, it isn't knocked unconscious. The creature is limited in the actions it can perform by the nature of its new form, and it can't speak, cast spells, or take any other action that requires hands or speech. The target's gear melds into the new form. The creature can't activate, use, wield, or otherwise benefit from any of its equipment.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Polymorph</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8,d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch regains a number of hit points equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cure Wounds</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d12,d12</dice>
								<type type="string">poison</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You extend your hand toward a creature you can see within range and project a puff of noxious gas from your palm. The creature must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or take 1d12 poison damage.</p>
					<p>This spell's damage increases by 1d12 when you reach 5th level (2d12), 11th level (3d12), and 17th level (4d12).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Poison Spray</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch one willing creature. Once before the spell ends, the target can roll a d4 and add the number rolled to one ability check of its choice. It can roll the die before or after making the ability check. The spell then ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Guidance</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a drop of water if creating water or a few grains of sand if destroying it)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You either create or destroy water. Create Water. You create up to 10 gallons of clean water within range in an open container. Alternatively, the water falls as rain in a 30-foot cube within range, extinguishing exposed flames in the area.</p>
					<p><b>Destroy Water. </b>You destroy up to 10 gallons of water in an open container within range. Alternatively, you destroy fog in a 30-foot cube within range.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you create or destroy 10 additional gallons of water, or the size of the cube increases by 5 feet, for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Create or Destroy Water</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Charmed</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You attempt to charm a humanoid you can see within range. It must make a Wisdom saving throw, and does so with advantage if you or your companions are fighting it. If it fails the saving throw, it is charmed by you until the spell ends or until you or your companions do anything harmful to it. The charmed creature regards you as a friendly acquaintance. When the spell ends, the creature knows it was charmed by you.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st. The creatures must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Charm Person</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">24</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Charmed</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a morsel of food)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell lets you convince a beast that you mean it no harm. Choose a beast that you can see within range. It must see and hear you. If the beast's Intelligence is 4 or higher, the spell fails. Otherwise, the beast must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be charmed by you for the spell's duration. If you or one of your companions harms the target, the spells ends.</p>
					<p><b><i>At Higher Levels. </i></b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can affect one additional beast for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">24 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Animal Friendship</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any.</p>
					<p>The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Magic</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a yew leaf)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you can sense the presence and location of poisons, poisonous creatures, and diseases within 30 feet of you. You also identify the kind of poison, poisonous creature, or disease in each case. The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Poison and Disease</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Restrained; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Grasping weeds and vines sprout from the ground in a 20-foot square starting from a point within range. For the duration, these plants turn the ground in the area into difficult terrain.</p>
					<p>A creature in the area when you cast the spell must succeed on a Strength saving throw or be restrained by the entangling plants until the spell ends. A creature restrained by the plants can use its action to make a Strength check against your spell save DC. On a success, it frees itself.</p>
					<p>When the spell ends, the conjured plants wilt away.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Entangle</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">90 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">GRANTADVATK; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Each object in a 20-foot cube within range is outlined in blue, green, or violet light (your choice). Any creature in the area when the spell is cast is also outlined in light if it fails a Dexterity saving throw. For the duration, objects and affected creatures shed dim light in a 10-foot radius. Any attack roll against an affected creature or object has advantage if the attacker can see it, and the affected creature or object can't benefit from being invisible.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Faerie Fire</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid</source>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create a 20-foot-radius sphere of fog centered on a point within range. The sphere spreads around corners, and its area is heavily obscured. It lasts for the duration or until a wind of moderate or greater speed (at least 10 miles per hour) disperses it.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the radius of the fog increases by 20 feet for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fog Cloud</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a sprig of mistletoe)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Up to ten berries appear in your hand and are infused with magic for the duration. A creature can use its action to eat one berry. Eating a berry restores 1 hit point, and the berry provides enough nourishment to sustain a creature for one day.</p>
					<p>The berries lose their potency if they have not been consumed within 24 hours of the casting of this spell.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Goodberry</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a grasshopper's hind leg)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature. The creature's jump distance is tripled until the spell ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Jump</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of dirt)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature. The target's speed increases by 10 feet until the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Longstrider</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger, Wizard</source>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>All nonmagical food and drink within a5-foot-radius sphere centered on a point of your choice within range is purified and rendered free of poison and disease.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Purify Food and Drink</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin</source>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain the ability to comprehend and verbally communicate with beasts for the duration. The knowledge and awareness of many beasts is limited by their intelligence, but at minimum, beasts can give you information about nearby locations and monsters, including whatever they can perceive or have perceived within the past day. You might be able to persuade a beast to perform a small favor for you, at the GM's discretion.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Speak with Animals</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00025>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a morsel of food)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>By means of this spell, you use an animal to deliver a message. Choose a Tiny beast you can see within range, such as a squirrel, a blue jay, or a bat. You specify a location, which you must have visited, and a recipient who matches a general description, such as &#34;a man or woman dressed in the uniform of the town guard&#34; or &#34;a red-haired dwarf wearing a pointed hat.&#34; You also speak a message of up to twenty-five words. The target beast travels for the duration of the spell toward the specified location, covering about 50 miles per 24 hours for a flying messenger, or 25 miles for other animals.</p>
					<p>When the messenger arrives, it delivers your message to the creature that you described, replicating the sound of your voice. The messenger speaks only to a creature matching the description you gave. If the messenger doesn't reach its destination before the spell ends, the message is lost, and the beast makes its way back to where you cast this spell.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>If you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the duration of the spell increases by 48 hours for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">24 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Animal Messenger</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00025>
			<id-00026>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a handful of oak bark)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a willing creature. Until the spell ends, the target's skin has a rough, bark-like appearance, and the target's AC can't be less than 16, regardless of what kind of armor it is wearing.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Barkskin</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00026>
			<id-00027>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (either a pinch of dried carrot or an agate)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a willing creature to grant it the ability to see in the dark. For the duration, that creature has darkvision out to a range of 60 feet.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Darkvision</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00027>
			<id-00028>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: constitution; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: strength; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: dexterity; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
					<id-00005>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: charisma; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">5</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00005>
					<id-00006>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: intelligence; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">6</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00006>
					<id-00007>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: wisdom; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">7</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00007>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (fur or a feather from a beast)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature and bestow upon it a magical enhancement. Choose one of the following effects; the target gains that effect until the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>Bear's Endurance. </b>The target has advantage on Constitution checks. It also gains 2d6 temporary hit points, which are lost when the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>Bull's Strength. </b>The target has advantage on Strength checks, and his or her carrying capacity doubles.</p>
					<p><b>Cat's Grace. </b>The target has advantage on Dexterity checks. It also doesn't take damage from falling 20 feet or less if it isn't incapacitated.</p>
					<p><b>Eagle's Splendor. </b>The target has advantage on Charisma checks.</p>
					<p><b>Fox's Cunning. </b>The target has advantage on Intelligence checks.</p>
					<p><b>Owl's Wisdom </b>. The target has advantage on Wisdom checks.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour.</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Enhance Ability</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Sorcerer</source>
			</id-00028>
			<id-00029>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You sense the presence of any trap within range that is within line of sight. A trap, for the purpose of this spell, includes anything that would inflict a sudden or unexpected effect you consider harmful or undesirable, which was specifically intended as such by its creator.</p>
					<p>Thus, the spell would sense an area affected by the alarm spell, a glyph of warding, or a mechanical pit trap, but it would not reveal a natural weakness in the floor, an unstable ceiling, or a hidden sinkhole.</p>
					<p>This spell merely reveals that a trap is present. You don't learn the location of each trap, but you do learn the general nature of the danger posed by a trap you sense.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Find Traps</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00029>
			<id-00030>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (leaf of sumac)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You evoke a fiery blade in your free hand. The blade is similar in size and shape to a scimitar, and it lasts for the duration. If you let go of the blade, it disappears, but you can evoke the blade again as a bonus action. You can use your action to make a melee spell attack with the fiery blade. On a hit, the target takes 3d6 fire damage.</p>
					<p>The flaming blade sheds bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for every two slot levels above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Flame Blade</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00030>
			<id-00031>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a bit of tallow, a pinch of brimstone, and a dusting of powdered iron)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A 5-foot-diameter sphere of fire appears in an unoccupied space of your choice within range and lasts for the duration. Any creature that ends its turn within 5 feet of the sphere must make a Dexterity saving throw.</p>
					<p>The creature takes 2d6 fire damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.</p>
					<p>As a bonus action, you can move the sphere up to 30 feet. If you ram the sphere into a creature, that creature must make the saving throw against the sphere's damage, and the sphere stops moving this turn.</p>
					<p>When you move the sphere, you can direct it over barriers up to 5 feet tall and jump it across pits up to 10 feet wide. The sphere ignites flammable objects not being worn or carried, and it sheds bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Flaming Sphere</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Wizard</source>
			</id-00031>
			<id-00032>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a legume seed)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A line of strong wind 60 feet long and 10 feet wide blasts from you in a direction you choose for the spell's duration. Each creature that starts its turn in the line must succeed on a Strength saving throw or be pushed 15 feet away from you in a direction following the line. Any creature in the line must spend 2 feet of movement for every 1 foot it moves when moving closer to you.</p>
					<p>The gust disperses gas or vapor, and it extinguishes candles, torches, and similar unprotected flames in the area. It causes protected flames, such as those of lanterns, to dance wildly and has a 50 percent chance to extinguish them.</p>
					<p>As a bonus action on each of your turns before the spell ends, you can change the direction in which the line blasts from you.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Gust of Wind</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self (60-foot line)</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00032>
			<id-00033>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a piece of iron and a flame)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose a manufactured metal object, such as a metal weapon or a suit of heavy or medium metal armor, that you can see within range. You cause the object to glow red-hot. Any creature in physical contact with the object takes 2d8 fire damage when you cast the spell. Until the spell ends, you can use a bonus action on each of your subsequent turns to cause this damage again.</p>
					<p>If a creature is holding or wearing the object and takes the damage from it, the creature must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or drop the object if it can. If it doesn't drop the object, it has disadvantage on attack rolls and ability checks until the start of your next turn.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heat Metal</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid</source>
			</id-00033>
			<id-00034>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Paralyzed; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a small, straight piece of iron)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose a humanoid that you can see within range.</p>
					<p>The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be paralyzed for the duration. At the end of each of its turns, the target can make another Wisdom saving throw. On a success, the spell ends on the target.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you can target one additional humanoid for each slot level above 2nd. The humanoids must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hold Person</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00034>
			<id-00035>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8,d8,d8,d8,d8,d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">necrotic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Necromantic energy washes over a creature of your choice that you can see within range, draining moisture and vitality from it. The target must make a Constitution saving throw. The target takes 8d8 necrotic damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs. If you target a plant creature or a magical plant, it makes the saving throw with disadvantage, and the spell deals maximum damage to it. If you target a nonmagical plant that isn't a creature, such as a tree or shrub, it doesn't make a saving throw; it simply withers and dies.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 5th level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 4th.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Blight</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Necromancy</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00035>
			<id-00036>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a bit of fur from a bloodhound)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Describe or name a specific kind of beast or plant. Concentrating on the voice of nature in your surroundings, you learn the direction and distance to the closest creature or plant of that kind within 5 miles, if any are present.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Locate Animals or Plants</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00036>
			<id-00037>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a forked twig)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Describe or name an object that is familiar to you. You sense the direction to the object's location, as long as that object is within 1,000 feet of you. If the object is in motion, you know the direction of its movement.</p>
					<p>The spell can locate a specific object known to you, as long as you have seen it up close-within 30 feet-at least once. Alternatively, the spell can locate the nearest object of a particular kind, such as a certain kind of apparel, jewelry, furniture, tool, or weapon.</p>
					<p>This spell can't locate an object if any thickness of lead, even a thin sheet, blocks a direct path between you and the object.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Locate Object</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger, Wizard</source>
			</id-00037>
			<id-00038>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (three nut shells)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell assaults and twists creatures' minds, spawning delusions and provoking uncontrolled action. Each creature in a 10-foot-radius sphere centered on a point you choose within range must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw when you cast this spell or be affected by it. An affected target can't take reactions and must roll a d10 at the start of each of its turns to determine its behavior for that turn.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>d10</b></td>
							<td><b>Behavior</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>1</td>
							<td>The creature uses all its movement to move in a random direction. To determine the direction, roll a d8 and assign a direction to each die face. The creature doesn't take an action this turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2-6</td>
							<td>The creature doesn't move or take actions this turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>7-8</td>
							<td>The creature uses its action to make a melee attack against a randomly determined creature within its reach. If there is no creature within its reach, the creature does nothing this turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>9-10</td>
							<td>The creature can act and move normally.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>At the end of each of its turns, an affected target can make a Wisdom saving throw. If it succeeds, this effect ends for that target.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 5th level or higher, the radius of the sphere increases by 5 feet for each slot level above 4th.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Confusion</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">90 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00038>
			<id-00039>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVSAV: poisoned; RESIST: poison</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature. If it is poisoned, you neutralize the poison. If more than one poison afflicts the target, you neutralize one poison that you know is present, or you neutralize one at random.</p>
					<p>For the duration, the target has advantage on saving throws against being poisoned, and it has resistance to poison damage.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Protection from Poison</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00039>
			<id-00040>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
								<type type="string">piercing,magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (seven sharp thorns or seven small twigs, each sharpened to a point)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The ground in a 20-foot radius centered on a point within range twists and sprouts hard spikes and thorns. The area becomes difficult terrain for the duration. When a creature moves into or within the area, it takes 2d4 piercing damage for every 5 feet it travels. The transformation o f the ground is camouflaged to look natural. Any creature that can't see the area at the time the spell is cast must make a Wisdom (Perception) check against your spell save DC to recognize the terrain as hazardous before entering it.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spike Growth</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">150 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00040>
			<id-00041>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You summon fey spirits that take the form of beasts and appear in unoccupied spaces that you can see within range. Choose one of the following options for what appears:</p>
					<list>
						<li>One beast of challenge rating 2 or lower</li>
						<li>Two beasts of challenge rating 1 or lower</li>
						<li>Four beasts of challenge rating 1/2 or lower</li>
						<li>Eight beasts of challenge rating 1/4 or lower</li>
					</list>
					<p>Each beast is also considered fey, and it disappears when it drops to 0 hit points or when the spell ends. The summoned creatures are friendly to you and your companions. Roll initiative for the summoned creatures as a group, which has its own turns. They obey any verbal commands that you issue to them (no action required by you). If you don't issue any commands to them, they defend themselves from hostile creatures, but otherwise take no actions. The GM has the creatures' statistics.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using certain higher-level spell slots, you choose one of the summoning options above, and more creatures appear: twice as many with a 5th-level slot, three times as many with a 7th-level slot, and four times as many with a 9th-level slot.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Conjure Animals</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00041>
			<id-00042>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A 60-foot-radius sphere of light spreads out from a point you choose within range. The sphere is bright light and sheds dim light for an additional 60 feet. If you chose a point on an object you are holding or one that isn't being worn or carried, the light shines from the object and moves with it. Completely covering the affected object with an opaque object, such as a bowl or a helm, blocks the light. If any of this spell's area overlaps with an area of darkness created by a spell of 3rd level or lower, the spell that created the darkness is dispelled.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Daylight</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer</source>
			</id-00042>
			<id-00043>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose one creature, object, or magical effect within range. Any spell of 3rd level or lower on the target ends. For each spell of 4th level or higher on the target, make an ability check using your spellcasting ability. The DC equals 10 + the spell's level. On a successful check, the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher, you automatically end the effects of a spell on the target if the spell's level is equal to or less than the level of the spell slot you used.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dispel Magic</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00043>
			<id-00044>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10,d10</dice>
								<type type="string">lightning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Call Lightning; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A storm cloud appears in the shape of a cylinder that is 10 feet tall with a 60-foot radius, centered on a point you can see 100 feet directly above you. The spell fails if you can't see a point in the air where the storm cloud could appear (for example, if you are in a room that can't accommodate the cloud). When you cast the spell, choose a point you can see within range. A bolt of lightning flashes down from the cloud to that point. Each creature within 5 feet of that point must make a Dexterity saving throw. A creature takes 3d10 lightning damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. On each of your turns until the spell ends, you can use your action to call down lightning in this way again, targeting the same point or a different one. If you are outdoors in stormy conditions when you cast this spell, the spell gives you control over the existing storm instead of creating a new one. Under such conditions, the spell's damage increases by 1d10.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th or higher level, the damage increases by 1d10 for each slot level above 3rd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Call Lightning</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00044>
			<id-00045>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6,d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning,magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">50</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning,magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You step into a stone object or surface large enough to fully contain your body, melding yourself and all the equipment you carry with the stone for the duration. Using your movement, you step into the stone at a point you can touch. Nothing of your presence remains visible or otherwise detectable by nonmagical senses. While merged with the stone, you can't see what occurs outside it, and any Wisdom (Perception) checks you make to hear sounds outside it are made with disadvantage. You remain aware of the passage of time and can cast spells on yourself while merged in the stone. You can use your movement to leave the stone where you entered it, which ends the spell. You otherwise can't move. Minor physical damage to the stone doesn't harm you, but its partial destruction or a change in its shape (to the extent that you no longer fit within it) expels you and deals 6d6 bludgeoning damage to you. The stone's complete destruction (or transmutation into a different substance) expels you and deals 50 bludgeoning damage to you. If expelled, you fall prone in an unoccupied space closest to where you first entered.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Meld into Stone</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00045>
			<id-00046>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action or 8 hours</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell channels vitality into plants within a specific area. There are two possible uses for the spell, granting either immediate or long-term benefits. If you cast this spell using 1 action, choose a point within range. All normal plants in a 100-foot radius centered on that point become thick and overgrown. A creature moving through the area must spend 4 feet of movement for every 1 foot it moves. You can exclude one or more areas of any size within the spell's area from being affected. If you cast this spell over 8 hours, you enrich the land. All plants in a half-mile radius centered on a point within range become enriched for 1 year. The plants yield twice the normal amount of food when harvested. Poison</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Plant Growth</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">150 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00046>
			<id-00047>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">RESIST: acid; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">RESIST: cold; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">RESIST: fire; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">RESIST: lightning; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
					<id-00005>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">RESIST: thunder; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">5</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00005>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, the willing creature you touch has resistance to one damage type of your choice: acid, cold, fire, lightning, or thunder.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Protection from Energy</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00047>
			<id-00048>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of dust and a few drops of water)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Until the spell ends, freezing rain and sleet fall in a 20-foot-tall cylinder with a 40-foot radius centered on a point you choose within range. The area is heavily obscured, and exposed flames in the area are doused. The ground in the area is covered with slick ice, making it difficult terrain. When a creature enters the spell's area for the first time on a turn or starts its turn there, it must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, it falls prone. If a creature is concentrating in the spell's area, the creature must make a successful Constitution saving throw against your spell save DC or lose concentration.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sleet Storm</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">150 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00048>
			<id-00049>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You imbue plants within 30 feet of you with limited sentience and animation, giving them the ability to communicate with you and follow your simple commands. You can question plants about events in the spell's area within the past day, gaining information about creatures that have passed, weather, and other circumstances. You can also turn difficult terrain caused by plant growth (such as thickets and undergrowth) into ordinary terrain that lasts for the duration. Or you can turn ordinary terrain where plants are present into difficult terrain that lasts for the duration, causing vines and branches to hinder pursuers, for example. Plants might be able to perform other tasks on your behalf, at the GM's discretion. The spell doesn't enable plants to uproot themselves and move about, but they can freely move branches, tendrils, and stalks. If a plant creature is in the area, you can communicate with it as if you shared a common language, but you gain no magical ability to influence it. This spell can cause the plants created by the entangle spell to release a restrained creature.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Speak with Plants</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self (30-foot radius)</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00049>
			<id-00050>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a short reed or piece of straw)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell grants up to ten willing creatures you can see within range the ability to breathe underwater until the spell ends. Affected creatures also retain their normal mode of respiration.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">24 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Water Breathing</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00050>
			<id-00051>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a piece of cork)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell grants the ability to move across any liquid surface-such as water, acid, mud, snow, quicksand, or lava-as if it were harmless solid ground (creatures crossing molten lava can still take damage from the heat). Up to ten willing creatures you can see within range gain this ability for the duration. If you target a creature submerged in a liquid, the spell carries the target to the surface of the liquid at a rate of 60 feet per round.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Water Walk</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer</source>
			</id-00051>
			<id-00052>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10</dice>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Moonbeam; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">DISSAV</label>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (several seeds of any moonseed plant and a piece of opalescent feldspar)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A silvery beam of pale light shines down in a 5-foot- radius, 40-foot-high cylinder centered on a point within range. Until the spell ends, dim light fills the cylinder. When a creature enters the spell's area for the first time on a turn or starts its turn there, it is engulfed in ghostly flames that cause searing pain, and it must make a Constitution saving throw. It takes 2d10 radiant damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. A shapechanger makes its saving throw with disadvantage. If it fails, it also instantly reverts to its original form and can't assume a different form until it leaves the spell's light. On each of your turns after you cast this spell, you can use an action to move the beam 60 feet in any direction.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d10 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Moonbeam</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00052>
			<id-00053>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 6th level, you can disrupt the strength of creatures animated by negative energy and bolster your allies against harmful conditions. A number of times per day equal to half your druid level, rounded up, you can utilize one of the following effects as a reaction:</p>
					<p>When an undead creature within 30 feet attacks a target other than you, you may impose disadvantage on the attack roll.</p>
					<p>You grant an ally within 30 feet advantage on saving throws against one of the following conditions: frightened, paralyzed, or poisoned.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cleanse the Blight</name>
				<prepared type="number">4</prepared>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of Life</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00053>
			<id-00054>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Pass without Trace; SKILL: 10, stealth; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (ashes from a burned leaf of mistletoe and a sprig of spruce)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A veil of shadows and silence radiates from you, masking you and your companions from detection. For the duration, each creature you choose within 30 feet of you (including you) has a +10 bonus to Dexterity (Stealth) checks and can't be tracked except by magical means. A creature that receives this bonus leaves behind no tracks or other traces of its passage.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Pass without Trace</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00054>
			<id-00055>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 minute</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You summon elementals that appear in unoccupied spaces that you can see within range. You choose one the following options for what appears:</p>
					<list>
						<li>One elemental of challenge rating 2 or lower</li>
						<li>Two elementals of challenge rating 1 or lower</li>
						<li>Four elementals of challenge rating 1/2 or lower</li>
						<li>Eight elementals of challenge rating 1/4 or lower.</li>
					</list>
					<p>An elemental summoned by this spell disappears when it drops to 0 hit points or when the spell ends. The summoned creatures are friendly to you and your companions. Roll initiative for the summoned creatures as a group, which has its own turns. They obey any verbal commands that you issue to them (no action required by you). If you don't issue any commands to them, they defend themselves from hostile creatures, but otherwise take no actions. The GM has the creatures' statistics.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using certain higher-level spell slots, you choose one of the summoning options above, and more creatures appear: twice as many with a 6th-level slot and three times as many with an 8th-level slot.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Conjure Minor Elementals</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">90 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Wizard</source>
			</id-00055>
			<id-00056>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (one holly berry per creature summoned)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You summon fey creatures that appear in unoccupied spaces that you can see within range. Choose one of the following options for what appears:</p>
					<list>
						<li>One fey creature of challenge rating 2 or lower</li>
						<li>Two fey creatures of challenge rating 1 or lower</li>
						<li>Four fey creatures of challenge rating 1/2 or lower</li>
						<li>Eight fey creatures of challenge rating 1/4 or lower</li>
					</list>
					<p>A summoned creature disappears when it drops to 0 hit points or when the spell ends. The summoned creatures are friendly to you and your companions. Roll initiative for the summoned creatures as a group, which have their own turns. They obey any verbal commands that you issue to them (no action required by you). If you don't issue any commands to them, they defend themselves from hostile creatures, but otherwise take no actions. The GM has the creatures' statistics.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using certain higher-level spell slots, you choose one of the summoning options above, and more creatures appear: twice as many with a 6th-level slot and three times as many with an 8th-level slot.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Conjure Woodland Beings</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00056>
			<id-00057>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning,magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning,magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S , M (a drop of water and a pinch of dust)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Until the spell ends, you control any freestanding water inside an area you choose that is a cube up to 100 feet on a side. You can choose from any of the following effects when you cast this spell. As an action on your turn, you can repeat the same effect or choose a different one.</p>
					<p><b>Flood </b>. You cause the water level of all standing water in the area to rise by as much as 20 feet. If the area includes a shore, the flooding water spills over onto dry land. If you choose an area in a large body of water, you instead create a 20-foot tall wave that travels from one side of the area to the other and then crashes down. Any Huge or smaller vehicles in the wave's path are carried with it to the other side. Any Huge or smaller vehicles struck by the wave have a 25 percent chance of capsizing. The water level remains elevated until the spell ends or you choose a different effect. If this effect produced a wave, the wave repeats on the start of your next turn while the flood effect lasts.</p>
					<p><b>Part Water </b>. You cause water in the area to move apart and create a trench. The trench extends across the spell's area, and the separated water forms a wall to either side. The trench remains until the spell ends or you choose a different effect. The water then slowly fills in the trench over the course of the next round until the normal water level is restored.</p>
					<p><b>Redirect Flow </b>. You cause flowing water in the area to move in a direction you choose, even if the water has to flow over obstacles, up walls, or in other unlikely directions. The water in the area moves as you direct it, but once it moves beyond the spell's area, it resumes its flow based on the terrain conditions. The water continues to move in the direction you chose until the spell ends or you choose a different effect.</p>
					<p><b>Whirlpool </b>. This effect requires a body of water at least 50 feet square and 25 feet deep. You cause a whirlpool to form in the center of the area. The whirlpool forms a vortex that is 5 feet wide at the base, up to 50 feet wide at the top, and 25 feet tall. Any creature or object in the water and within 25 feet of the vortex is pulled 10 feet toward it. A creature can swim away from the vortex by making a Strength (Athletics) check against your spell save DC. When a creature enters the vortex for the first time on a turn or starts its turn there, it must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, the creature takes 2d8 bludgeoning damage and is caught in the vortex until the spell ends. On a successful save, the creature takes half damage, and isn't caught in the vortex. A creature caught in the vortex can use its action to try to swim away from the vortex as described above, but has disadvantage on the Strength (Athletics) check to do so. The first time each turn that an object enters the vortex, the object takes 2d8 bludgeoning damage; this damage occurs each round it remains in the vortex.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Control Water</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">300 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Wizard</source>
			</id-00057>
			<id-00058>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Charmed; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Charmed; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You attempt to beguile a beast that you can see within range. It must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be charmed by you for the duration. If you or creatures that are friendly to you are fighting it, it has advantage on the saving throw. While the beast is charmed, you have a telepathic link with it as long as the two of you are on the same plane of existence. You can use this telepathic link to issue commands to the creature while you are conscious (no action required), which it does its best to obey. You can specify a simple and general course of action, such as &#34;Attack that creature,&#34; &#34;Run over there,&#34; or &#34;Fetch that object.&#34; If the creature completes the order and doesn't receive further direction from you, it defends and preserves itself to the best of its ability. You can use your action to take total and precise control of the target. Until the end of your next turn, the creature takes only the actions you choose, and doesn't do anything that you don't allow it to do. During this time, you can also cause the creature to use a reaction, but this requires you to use your own reaction as well. Each time the target takes damage, it makes a new Wisdom saving throw against the spell. If the saving throw succeeds, the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell with a 5th-level spell slot, the duration is concentration, up to 10 minutes. When you use a 6th-level spell slot, the duration is concentration, up to 1 hour. When you use a spell slot of 7th level or higher, the duration is concentration, up to 8 hours.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dominate Beast</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Sorcerer</source>
			</id-00058>
			<id-00059>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a leather strap, bound around the arm or a similar appendage)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a willing creature. For the duration, the target's movement is unaffected by difficult terrain, and spells and other magical effects can neither reduce the target's speed nor cause the target to be paralyzed or restrained. The target can also spend 5 feet of movement to automatically escape from nonmagical restraints, such as manacles or a creature that has it grappled. Finally, being underwater imposes no penalties on the target's movement or attacks.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Freedom of Movement</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00059>
			<id-00060>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You transform up to ten centipedes, three spiders, five wasps, or one scorpion within range into giant versions of their natural forms for the duration. A centipede becomes a giant centipede, a spider becomes a giant spider, a wasp becomes a giant wasp, and a scorpion becomes a giant scorpion. Each creature obeys your verbal commands, and in combat, they act on your turn each round. The GM has the statistics for these creatures and resolves their actions and movement. A creature remains in its giant size for the duration, until it drops to 0 hit points, or until you use an action to dismiss the effect on it. The GM might allow you to choose different targets. For example, if you transform a bee, its giant version might have the same statistics as a giant wasp.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Giant Insect</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00060>
			<id-00061>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">10 minutes</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a stone, a twig, and a bit of green plant)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You make natural terrain in a 150-foot cube in range look, sound, and smell like some other sort of natural terrain. Thus, open fields or a road can be made to resemble a swamp, hill, crevasse, or some other difficult or impassable terrain. A pond can be made to seem like a grassy meadow, a precipice like a gentle slope, or a rock-strewn gully like a wide and smooth road. Manufactured structures, equipment, and creatures within the area aren't changed in appearance. The tactile characteristics of the terrain are unchanged, so creatures entering the area are likely to see through the illusion. If the difference isn't obvious by touch, a creature carefully examining the illusion can attempt an Intelligence (Investigation) check against your spell save DC to disbelieve it. A creature who discerns the illusion for what it is, sees it as a vague image superimposed on the terrain.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">24 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hallucinatory Terrain</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">300 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00061>
			<id-00062>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning,magic</type>
							</id-00001>
							<id-00002>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">cold,magic</type>
							</id-00002>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of dust and a few drops of water)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A hail of rock-hard ice pounds to the ground in a 20- foot-radius, 40-foot-high cylinder centered on a point within range. Each creature in the cylinder must make a Dexterity saving throw. A creature takes 2d8 bludgeoning damage and 4d6 cold damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. Hailstones turn the storm's area of effect into difficult terrain until the end of your next turn.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 5th level or higher, the bludgeoning damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 4th.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ice Storm</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">300 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00062>
			<id-00063>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a bit of fur from a bloodhound)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Describe or name a creature that is familiar to you. You sense the direction to the creature's location, as long as that creature is within 1,000 feet of you. If the creature is moving, you know the direction of its movement. The spell can locate a specific creature known to you, or the nearest creature of a specific kind (such as a human or a unicorn), so long as you have seen such a creature up close-within 30 feet-at least once. If the creature you described or named is in a different form, such as being under the effects of a polymorph spell, this spell doesn't locate the creature. This spell can't locate a creature if running water at least 10 feet wide blocks a direct path between you and the creature.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Locate Creature</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger, Wizard</source>
			</id-00063>
			<id-00064>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (soft clay, which must be worked into roughly the desired shape o f the stone object)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a stone object of Medium size or smaller or a section of stone no more than 5 feet in any dimension and form it into any shape that suits your purpose. So, for example, you could shape a large rock into a weapon, idol, or coffer, or make a small passage through a wall, as long as the wall is less than 5 feet thick. You could also shape a stone door or its frame to seal the door shut. The object you create can have up to two hinges and a latch, but finer mechanical detail isn't possible.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Stone Shape</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Wizard</source>
			</id-00064>
			<id-00065>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (diamond dust worth 100 GP, which the spell consumes)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell turns the flesh of a willing creature you touch as hard as stone. Until the spell ends, the target has resistance to nonmagical bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing damage.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Stoneskin</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00065>
			<id-00066>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8,d8,d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8,d8,d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a small piece of phosphorus)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create a wall of fire on a solid surface within range. You can make the wall up to 60 feet long, 20 feet high, and 1 foot thick, or a ringed wall up to 20 feet in diameter, 20 feet high, and 1 foot thick. The wall is opaque and lasts for the duration. When the wall appears, each creature within its area must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, a creature takes 5d8 fire damage, or half as much damage on a successful save. One side of the wall, selected by you when you cast this spell, deals 5d8 fire damage to each creature that ends its turn within 10 feet of that side or inside the wall. A creature takes the same damage when it enters the wall for the first time on a turn or ends its turn there. The other side of the wall deals no damage.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 5th level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 4th.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wall of Fire</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00066>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">3</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: Mount (horse)</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Clubs, daggers, darts, javelins, maces, quarterstaffs, scimitars, sickles, slings, spears</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Tool: Herbalism kit</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Armor: light armor, medium armor, shields (druids will not wear armor or use shields made of metal)</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<name type="string">Armor: Light armor</name>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<name type="string">Tool: One musical instrument of your choice</name>
			</id-00006>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Half-Elf (Half-Human)</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>race.id-00007@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<senses type="string">Darkvision 60</senses>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">8</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">8</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">8</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">8</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00005_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fey Ancestry</name>
				<source type="string">Half-Elf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against being charmed, and magic can't put you to sleep.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00003>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Javelin</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00020</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Club</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00002</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">2</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Javelin</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00020</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<attackbonus type="number">1</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing,magic</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Mithral Javelin of Humanoid Slaying</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00023</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<attackbonus type="number">1</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing,magic</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">1</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Mithral Javelin of Humanoid Slaying</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00023</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00005>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">160 pounds</weight>
	</character>
</root>
