<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:4">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">11</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">6</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">11</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">6</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">17</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">11</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">185</age>
		<appearance type="string">Pale Blue Grey Skin, Bone white hair, black eyes,</appearance>
		<background type="string">Blacksmith</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>background.id-00026@Incarnate-5eExpansion</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">My forgers hammer is a relic from a long lost age. There is nothing else its equal and it has been in my family for as long as they can remember.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">0</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d10</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">6</level>
				<name type="string">Fighter</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.fighter@DD Xanathar's Guide to Everything</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">1023</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">104</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">57</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">EP</name>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">68</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">8</armor>
				<dexbonus type="string">no</dexbonus>
				<disstealth type="number">1</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">2</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">20</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">85</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">170</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">510</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">147.6</load>
			<max type="number">255</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">613</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">800</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 6th, 8th, 12th, 14th, 16th, and 19th levels, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score by 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Forger's Fire</name>
				<source type="string">Blacksmith</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have spent your whole life with the forge. When you roll for creating an item in a forge you have an advantage.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00018@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Forging Items</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style: Two-Weapon</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You adopt a particular style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the following options. You can't take a Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.</p>
					<p><b>Archery</b></p>
					<p>You gain a +2 bonus to attack rolls you make with ranged weapons.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.fightingstylearchery@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Fighting Style - Archery</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Defense</b></p>
					<p>While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.fightingstyledefense@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Fighting Style - Defense</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Dueling</b></p>
					<p>When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.fightingstyledueling@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Fighting Style - Dueling</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Great Weapon Fighting</b></p>
					<p>When you roll a 1 or 2 on a damage die for an attack you make with a melee weapon that you are wielding with two hands, you can re-roll the die and must use the new roll, even if the new roll is a 1 or a 2. The weapon must have the two-handed or versatile property for you to gain this benefit.</p>
					<p><b>Protection</b></p>
					<p>When a creature you can see attacks a target other than you that is within 5 feet of you, you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on the attack roll. You must be wielding a shield.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.fightingstyleprotection@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Fighting Style - Protection</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Two-Weapon Fighting</b></p>
					<p>When you engage in two-weapon fighting, you can add your ability modifier to the damage of the second attack.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Second Wind</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Action Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.secondwind@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Second Wind</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You have a limited well of stamina that you can draw on to protect yourself from harm. On your turn, you can use a bonus action to regain hit points equal to 1d10 + your fighter level. Once you use this feature, you must finish a short or long rest before you can use it again.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">5</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Extra Attack</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning at 5th level, you can attack twice, instead of once, whenever you take the Attack action on your turn.</p>
					<p>The number of attacks increases to three when you reach 11th level in this class and to four when you reach 20th level in this class.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Action Surge</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can push yourself beyond your normal limits for a moment. On your turn, you can take one additional action on top of your regular action and a possible bonus action.</p>
					<p>Once you use this feature, you must finish a short or long rest before you can use it again. Starting at 17th level, you can use it twice before a rest, but only once on the same turn.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Battle Master</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Those who emulate the archetypal Battle Master employ martial techniques passed down through generations. To a Battle Master, combat is an academic field, sometimes including subjects beyond battle such as weapon smithing and calligraphy. Not every fighter absorbs the lessons of history, theory, and artistry that are reflected in the Battle Master archetype, but those who do are well-rounded fighters of great skill and knowledge.</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.combatsuperiority3@DD PHB Deluxe">Combat Superiority</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.studentofwar3@DD PHB Deluxe">Student of War</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.knowyourenemy7@DD PHB Deluxe">Know Your Enemy</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.improvedcombatsuperiority10@DD PHB Deluxe">Improved Combat Superiority</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.relentless15@DD PHB Deluxe">Relentless</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Student of War</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specialization type="string">Battle Master</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level, you gain proficiency with one type of artisan's tools of your choice.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Combat Superiority</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specialization type="string">Battle Master</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you choose this archetype at 3rd level, you learn maneuvers that are fueled by special dice called superiority dice.</p>
					<p><b>Maneuvers. </b>You learn three maneuvers of your choice, which are detailed under &#34;Maneuvers&#34; below. Many maneuvers enhance an attack in some way. You can use only one maneuver per attack.</p>
					<p>You learn two additional maneuvers of your choice at 7th, 10th, and 15th level. Each time you learn new maneuvers, you can also replace one maneuver you know with a different one.</p>
					<p><b>Maneuvers</b></p>
					<p>The maneuvers are presented in alphabetical order.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Maneuver</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"><b>Description</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Commander's Strike</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you take the Attack action on your turn, you can forgo one of your attacks and use a bonus action to direct one of your companions to strike. When you do so, choose a friendly creature who can see or hear you and expend one superiority die. That creature can immediately use its reaction to make one weapon attack, adding the superiority die to the attack's damage roll.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Disarming Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to disarm the target, forcing it to drop one item of your choice that it's holding. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and the target must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, it drops the object you choose. The object lands at its feet.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Distracting Strike</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to distract the creature, giving your allies an opening. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll. The next attack roll against the target by an attacker other than you has advantage if the attack is made before the start of your next turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Evasive Footwork</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you move, you can expend one superiority die, rolling the die and adding the number rolled to your AC until you stop moving.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Feinting Attack.</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">You can expend one superiority die and use a bonus action on your turn to feint, choosing one creature within 5 feet of you as your target. You have advantage on your next attack roll against that creature. If that attack hits, add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll. The advantage is lost if not used on the turn you gain it.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Goading Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to goad the target into attacking you. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and the target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, the target has disadvantage on all attack rolls against targets other than you until the end of your next turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Lunging Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you make a melee weapon attack on your turn, you can expend one superiority die to increase your reach for that attack by 5 feet. If you hit, you add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Maneuvering Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to maneuver one of your comrades into a more advantageous position. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and you choose a friendly creature who can see or hear you. That creature can use its reaction to move up to half its speed without provoking opportunity attacks from the target of your attack.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Menacing Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to frighten the target. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and the target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, it is frightened of you until the end of your next turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Parry</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When another creature damages you with a melee attack, you can use your reaction and expend one superiority die to reduce the damage by the number you roll on your superiority die + your Dexterity modifier.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Precision Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you make a weapon attack roll against a creature, you can expend one superiority die to add it to the roll. You can use this maneuver before or after making the attack roll, but before any effects of the attack are applied.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Pushing Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to drive the target back. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and if the target is Large or smaller, it must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, you push the target up to 15 feet away from you.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Rally</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">On your turn, you can use a bonus action and expend one superiority die to bolster the resolve of one of your companions. When you do so, choose a friendly creature who can see or hear you. That creature gains temporary hit points equal to the superiority die roll + your Charisma modifier.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Riposte</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When a creature misses you with a melee attack, you can use your reaction and expend one superiority die to make a melee weapon attack against the creature. If you hit, you add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Sweeping Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to damage another creature with the same attack. Choose another creature within 5 feet of the original target and within your reach. If the original attack roll would hit the second creature, it takes damage equal to the number you roll on your superiority die. The damage is of the same type dealt by the original attack.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Trip Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to knock the target down. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and if the target is Large or smaller, it must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, you knock the target prone.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p><b>Superiority Dice. </b>You have four superiority dice, which are d8s. A superiority die is expended when you use it. You regain all of your expended superiority dice when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>You gain another superiority die at 7th level and one more at 15th level.</p>
					<p><b>Saving Throws. </b>Some of your maneuvers require your target to make a saving throw to resist the maneuver's effects. The saving throw DC is calculated as follows:</p>
					<p><b>Maneuver save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Strength or Dexterity modifier (your choice)</p>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<level type="number">6</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement (lvl 6)</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 6th, 8th, 12th, 14th, 16th, and 19th levels, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score by 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00010>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I love the challenge of an assignment and will work for free if they have interesting metals or designs for me to try out.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">4'2&#34;</height>
		<hero type="number">0</hero>
		<herodice type="string">d6</herodice>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">52</total>
			<wounds type="number">21</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Power - With greater weapons comes greater power. As I get better I will fashion an army and all will fear me. (Evil) Discipline - I work hard and whatever I set out to do I accomplish. From the forge to life I excell at everything I try. (Any)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">2</total>
		</initiative>
		<inspiration type="number">0</inspiration>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">20 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Skill Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_skill" recordname="skill.id-00253@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Smith's Tools</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>Two Metal Files (fine and rough), Three Metal Hammers (1 lb, 2 lb, 3lb), a Small Vial of Oil.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00019@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Rules for Using Smith's Tools</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Smith's Tools</name>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Artisan's Tool</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tool</type>
				<weight type="number">8</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">3 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This set of clothing has small burns all across it where frequent sparks have landed.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Torso</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Singed Common</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tiny leather pouch is perfect for keeping your coins close at hand. Just watch out for someone trying to cut it off of your belt.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Leather Belt</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Coin Pouch - Small</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hammer</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Knowledge of leatherworking extends to lore concerning animal hides and their properties. It also confers knowledge of leather armor and similar goods. Leatherworker's tools include a knife, a small mallet, an edger, a hole punch, thread, and leather scraps.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Leatherworker's Tools</name>
				<subtype type="string">Artisan's Tools</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Handy Haversack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Giant Poisonous Snake head</name>
				<weight type="number">25</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Leather Belt</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Using a crowbar grants advantage to Strength checks where the crowbar's leverage can be applied.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Crowbar</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">900 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This backpack has a central pouch and two side pouches, each of which is an extra-dimensional space.</p>
					<p>Each side pouch can hold up to 20 pounds of material, not exceeding a volume of 2 cubic feet. The large central pouch can hold up to 8 cubic feet or 80 pounds of material. The backpack always weighs 5 pounds, regardless of its contents.</p>
					<p>Placing an object in the haversack follows the normal rules for interacting with objects. Retrieving an item from the haversack requires you to use an action. When you reach into the haversack for a specific item, the item is always magically on top.</p>
					<p>The haversack has a few limitations. If it is overloaded, or if a sharp object pierces it or tears it, the haversack ruptures and is destroyed. If the haversack is destroyed, its contents are lost forever, although an artifact always turns up again somewhere. If the haversack is turned inside out, its contents spill forth, unharmed, and the haversack must be put right before it can be used again. If a breathing creature is placed within the haversack, the creature can survive for up to 10 minutes, after which time it begins to suffocate.</p>
					<p>Placing the haversack inside an extra-dimensional space created by a bag of holding, portable hole, or similar item instantly destroys both items and opens a gate to the Astral Plane. The gate originates where the one item was placed inside the other. Any creature within 10 feet of the gate is sucked through it and deposited in a random location on the Astral Plane. The gate then closes. The gate is one--way only and can't be reopened.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Back</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Handy Haversack</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Backpack</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">-</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Rare</rarity>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">100 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Action Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.potionofgreaterhealing@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Potion of Greater Healing</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You regain hit points when you drink this potion.</p>
					<p>The number of hit points depends on the potion's rarity, as shown in the Potions of Healing table. Whatever its potency, the potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</p>
					<h>Potions of Healing</h>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Potion of .</td>
							<td>Rarity</td>
							<td>HP Regained</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Greater healing</td>
							<td>Uncommon</td>
							<td>4d4 + 4</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Greater Potion of Healing</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Dim Potion</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">The potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Potion</type>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<ac type="number">18</ac>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">1,500 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Plate consists of shaped, interlocking metal plates that cover the entire body. A suit of plate includes gauntlets, heavy leather boots, a visored helmet, and thick layers of padding underneath the armor. Buckles and straps distribute the weight over the body.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<location type="string">Torso</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Plate Armor</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Plate Armor</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Some well-crafted plate armor.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Rare</rarity>
				<stealth type="string">Disadvantage</stealth>
				<strength type="string">Str 15</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Heavy Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">65</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<ac type="number">16</ac>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">75 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Of all the armor categories, heavy armor offers the best protection. These suits of armor cover the entire body and are designed to stop a wide range of attacks. Only proficient warriors can manage their weight and bulk.</p>
					<p>Made of interlocking metal rings, chain mail includes a layer of quilted fabric worn underneath the mail to prevent chafing and to cushion the impact of blows. The suit includes gauntlets.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Torso</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Chain Mail</name>
				<stealth type="string">Disadvantage</stealth>
				<strength type="string">Str 13</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Heavy Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">55</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 slashing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Hands</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Battleaxe</name>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string">Body</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<location type="string">Body</location>
				<name type="string">Back</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<location type="string">Body</location>
				<name type="string">Torso</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<location type="string">Waist</location>
				<name type="string">Leather Belt</name>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<location type="string">Body</location>
				<name type="string">Waist</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">15 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 bludgeoning</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<location type="string">Hands</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Warhammer</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Warhammer</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">When a skull needs bashed, try the mighty warhammer.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Melee Weapon</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00025>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<location type="string">Body</location>
				<name type="string">Hands</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00025>
			<id-00026>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Hands</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Shield</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A well crafted shield.</nonidentified>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Shield</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00026>
			<id-00027>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1410 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 slashing, magic</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Mithril weapons are light weight and strong. (reduce their weight by half of the normal weight)</p>
					<p>If this reduces the weight to less than or equal to 3 pounds and is one handed then it gains the finesse property.</p>
					<h>Action Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.elementalslayer@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Elemental Slayer</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</p>
					<p>When you hit an elemental with it, the creature takes an extra 2d6 damage of the weapon's type and must succeed on a DC 15 Strength saving throw or fall prone. For the purpose of this weapon, &#34;elemental&#34; refers to any creature with the elemental type.</p>
					<p>This blade is specially treated to be immune to rust, including that from a rust monster.</p>
					<p>You have a bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. The bonus is determined by the weapon's rarity.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mithril Battleaxe of Elemental Slaying</name>
				<nonidentified type="string">ERROR</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10), finesse</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00027>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Dwarvish</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Undercommon</name>
			</id-00003>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">6</level>
		<name type="string">Duldar Thurgram</name>
		<notes type="string">Heraldic Sign: A skull with a dagger through it, representing the doom you bring to your enemies\nInstructors: Tribal Warrior. Your instructor grew up in a tribe, where fighting for one's life was practically an every day occurrence.\nSignature Style: Brutal. Your attacks rain down like hammer blows, meant to splinter bone or send blood flying.\nSkill Level: Excellent (tier 5)\nSpecialties: Scimitar, Spear, Longsword, Glaive</notes>
		<pc_label_hero type="string">Hero Point</pc_label_hero>
		<perception type="number">10</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">You do not like being disturbed from a task and tend to lash out against whoever disturbed you. Sometimes you even hit them before realizing they are a friend.</personalitytraits>
		<powerdisplaymode type="string">action</powerdisplaymode>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Racial Traits</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Class Features</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">BattleMaster</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Crafting</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<name type="string">Standard Actions</name>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00007>
				<name type="string">Consumables</name>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00009>
				<name type="string">Consumables</name>
			</id-00009>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">combat</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">NOTE: Enlarged; ADVCHK: strength; ADVSAV: strength; DMG: 1d4; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">NOTE: Reduced; DISCHK: strength; DISSAV: strength; DMG: -1d4; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of powdered iron)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Sound</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="url" recordname="syrinscape-fantasy:elements/ZXpyZW4tbWFsZS13aXphcmQ6OmVubGFyZ2UtcGVyc29u/play/">Syrinscape: Enlarge - Wizard Spells E</link>
						<link class="url" recordname="syrinscape-fantasy:elements/ZXpyZW4tbWFsZS13aXphcmQ6OnJlZHVjZS1wZXJzb24tYQ/play/">Syrinscape: Reduce - Wizard Spells E</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You cause a creature or an object you can see within range to grow larger or smaller for the duration. Choose either a creature or an object that is neither worn nor carried. If the target is unwilling, it can make a Constitution saving throw. On a success, the spell has no effect. If the target is a creature, everything it is wearing and carrying changes size with it. Any item dropped by an affected creature returns to normal size at once.</p>
					<p><b>Enlarge </b>. The target's size doubles in all dimensions, and its weight is multiplied by eight. This growth increases its size by one category- from Medium to Large, for example. If there isn't enough room for the target to double its size, the creature or object attains the maximum possible size in the space available. Until the spell ends, the target also has advantage on Strength checks and Strength saving throws. The target's weapons also grow to match its new size. While these weapons are enlarged, the target's attacks with them deal 1d4 extra damage.</p>
					<p><b>Reduce </b>. The target's size is halved in all dimensions, and its weight is reduced to one-eighth of normal. This reduction decreases its size by one category-from Medium to Small, for example. Until the spell ends, the target also has disadvantage on Strength checks and Strength saving throws. The target's weapons also shrink to match its new size. While these weapons are reduced, the target's attacks with them deal 1d4 less damage (this can't reduce the damage below 1).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Racial Traits</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Enlarge/Reduce</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4,d4,d4</dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">1</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Item Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00392@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Greater Potion of Healing</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Consumables</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Greater Potion of Healing</name>
				<prepared type="number">2</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Item - Action Code</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<label type="string">Frightened</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you choose this archetype at 3rd level, you learn maneuvers that are fueled by special dice called superiority dice.</p>
					<p><b>Maneuvers. </b>You learn three maneuvers of your choice, which are detailed under &#34;Maneuvers&#34; below. Many maneuvers enhance an attack in some way. You can use only one maneuver per attack.</p>
					<p>You learn two additional maneuvers of your choice at 7th, 10th, and 15th level. Each time you learn new maneuvers, you can also replace one maneuver you know with a different one.</p>
					<p><b>Maneuvers</b></p>
					<p>The maneuvers are presented in alphabetical order.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Maneuver</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"><b>Description</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Commander's Strike</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you take the Attack action on your turn, you can forgo one of your attacks and use a bonus action to direct one of your companions to strike. When you do so, choose a friendly creature who can see or hear you and expend one superiority die. That creature can immediately use its reaction to make one weapon attack, adding the superiority die to the attack's damage roll.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Disarming Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to disarm the target, forcing it to drop one item of your choice that it's holding. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and the target must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, it drops the object you choose. The object lands at its feet.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Distracting Strike</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to distract the creature, giving your allies an opening. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll. The next attack roll against the target by an attacker other than you has advantage if the attack is made before the start of your next turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Evasive Footwork</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you move, you can expend one superiority die, rolling the die and adding the number rolled to your AC until you stop moving.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Feinting Attack.</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">You can expend one superiority die and use a bonus action on your turn to feint, choosing one creature within 5 feet of you as your target. You have advantage on your next attack roll against that creature. If that attack hits, add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll. The advantage is lost if not used on the turn you gain it.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Goading Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to goad the target into attacking you. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and the target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, the target has disadvantage on all attack rolls against targets other than you until the end of your next turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Lunging Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you make a melee weapon attack on your turn, you can expend one superiority die to increase your reach for that attack by 5 feet. If you hit, you add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Maneuvering Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to maneuver one of your comrades into a more advantageous position. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and you choose a friendly creature who can see or hear you. That creature can use its reaction to move up to half its speed without provoking opportunity attacks from the target of your attack.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Menacing Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to frighten the target. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and the target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, it is frightened of you until the end of your next turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Parry</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When another creature damages you with a melee attack, you can use your reaction and expend one superiority die to reduce the damage by the number you roll on your superiority die + your Dexterity modifier.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Precision Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you make a weapon attack roll against a creature, you can expend one superiority die to add it to the roll. You can use this maneuver before or after making the attack roll, but before any effects of the attack are applied.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Pushing Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to drive the target back. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and if the target is Large or smaller, it must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, you push the target up to 15 feet away from you.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Rally</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">On your turn, you can use a bonus action and expend one superiority die to bolster the resolve of one of your companions. When you do so, choose a friendly creature who can see or hear you. That creature gains temporary hit points equal to the superiority die roll + your Charisma modifier.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Riposte</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When a creature misses you with a melee attack, you can use your reaction and expend one superiority die to make a melee weapon attack against the creature. If you hit, you add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Sweeping Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to damage another creature with the same attack. Choose another creature within 5 feet of the original target and within your reach. If the original attack roll would hit the second creature, it takes damage equal to the number you roll on your superiority die. The damage is of the same type dealt by the original attack.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Trip Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to knock the target down. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and if the target is Large or smaller, it must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, you knock the target prone.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p><b>Superiority Dice. </b>You have four superiority dice, which are d8s. A superiority die is expended when you use it. You regain all of your expended superiority dice when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>You gain another superiority die at 7th level and one more at 15th level.</p>
					<p><b>Saving Throws. </b>Some of your maneuvers require your target to make a saving throw to resist the maneuver's effects. The saving throw DC is calculated as follows:</p>
					<p><b>Maneuver save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Strength or Dexterity modifier (your choice)</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">BattleMaster</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Combat Superiority</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<specialization type="string">Battle Master</specialization>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Dwarven Resilience; RESIST: poison; Advantage on saving throws vs. poison</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against poison, and you have resistance against poison damage (explained in chapter 9).</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Racial Traits</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dwarf: Dwarven Resilience</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Racial</school>
				<source type="string">Dwarf</source>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">action</apply>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Stonecunning; SKILL: [2PRF] history</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Whenever you make an Intelligence (History) check related to the origin of stonework, you are considered proficient in the History skill and add double your proficiency bonus to the check, instead of your normal proficiency bonus.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Racial Traits</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dwarf: Stonecunning</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Racial</school>
				<source type="string">Dwarf</source>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Duergar Resilience; Advantage against illusions, charmed, and paralyzed</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against illusions and against being charmed or paralyzed.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Racial Traits</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dwarf: Duergar Resilience</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Racial</school>
				<source type="string">Gray Dwarf (Duergar)</source>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Sunlight Sensitivity; DISATK; DISSKILL: perception</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have disadvantage on attack rolls and on Wisdom (Perception) checks that rely on sight when you, the target of your attack, or whatever you are trying to perceive is in direct sunlight.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Racial Traits</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dwarf: Sunlight Sensitivity</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Racial</school>
				<source type="string">Gray Dwarf (Duergar)</source>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 3rd level, you can cast the enlarge/reduce spell on yourself once with this trait, using only the spell's enlarge option. When you reach 5th level, you can cast the invisibility spell on yourself once with this trait. You don't need material components for either spell, and you can't cast them while you're in direct sunlight, although sunlight has no effect on them once cast. You regain the ability to cast these spells with this trait when you finish a long rest. Intelligence is your spellcasting ability for these spells.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.enlarge_reduce@*">Spell: Enlarge/Reduce</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Racial Traits</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dwarf: Duergar Magic</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Racial</school>
				<source type="string">Gray Dwarf (Duergar)</source>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Trip Attack; prone</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<apply type="string">action</apply>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Trip Attack; DMG:1d8</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<group type="string">BattleMaster</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Trip Attack</name>
				<prepared type="number">4</prepared>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">1</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can push yourself beyond your normal limits for a moment. On your turn, you can take one additional action on top of your regular action and a possible bonus action.</p>
					<p>Once you use this feature, you must finish a short or long rest before you can use it again. Starting at 17th level, you can use it twice before a rest, but only once on the same turn.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class Features</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighter: Action Surge</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Class</school>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">action</apply>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Maneuvering Attack; DMG: 1d8</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<group type="string">BattleMaster</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Maneuvering Attack</name>
				<prepared type="number">4</prepared>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
					<id-00002>
						<apply type="string">action</apply>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Disarming Strike; DMG: 1d8</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Disarming Strike - item dropped;</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<group type="string">BattleMaster</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Disarming Attack</name>
				<prepared type="number">4</prepared>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10</dice>
								<stat type="string">fighter</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">1</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.profighter.features.id-00035@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Second Wind</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class Features</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Second Wind</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Fighter - Class Ability</source>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Crafting</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Forger's Fire</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<shortdescription type="string">You have spent your whole life with the forge. When you roll for creating an item in a forge you have an advantage.\n</shortdescription>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">ADVSAV: dexterity;GRANTDISATK</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You focus entirely on avoiding attacks. Until the end of your next turn, any attack roll made against you has disadvantage if you can see the attacker, and you make Dexterity saving throws with advantage. You lose this benefit if you are incapacitated or if your speed drops to 0.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="referencemanualpage" recordname="referencemanual2.SRD_PRO_00071@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Actions in Combat</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Standard Actions</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dodge</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">5e Rule Coding</source>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Help - check; ADVCHK</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Help - attack; ADVATK</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can lend your aid to another creature in the completion of a task. When you take the Help action, the creature you aid gains advantage on the next ability check it makes to perform the task you are helping with, provided that it makes the check before the start of your next turn.</p>
					<p>Alternatively, you can aid a friendly creature in attacking a creature within 5 feet of you. You feint, distract the target, or in some other way team up to make your ally's attack more effective. If your ally attacks the target beforre your next turn, the first attack roll is made with advantage.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="referencemanualpage" recordname="referencemanual2.SRD_PRO_00071@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Actions in Combat</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Standard Actions</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Help</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">5e Rule Coding</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Hide</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<group type="string">Standard Actions</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hide</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Ready</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<group type="string">Standard Actions</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ready</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
			</id-00018>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">3</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: Smith's Tools, Leatherworker's Tools</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: battleaxe, handaxe, light hammer, and warhammer</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple weapons, martial weapons</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Armor: All armor, shields</name>
			</id-00004>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Dwarf (Duergar)</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.dwarf@DD Mordenkainen's Tome of Foes</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<senses type="string">Superior Darkvision 120</senses>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Smith's Tools</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Leatherworker's Tools</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00020>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">25</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">25</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00002_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dwarven Resilience</name>
				<source type="string">Dwarf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against poison, and you have resistance against poison damage (explained in chapter 9).</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Stonecunning</name>
				<source type="string">Dwarf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Whenever you make an Intelligence (History) check related to the origin of stonework, you are considered proficient in the History skill and add double your proficiency bonus to the check, instead of your normal proficiency bonus.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dwarven Combat Training</name>
				<source type="string">Dwarf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have proficiency with the battleaxe, handaxe, light hammer, and warhammer.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tool Proficiency</name>
				<source type="string">Dwarf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain proficiency with the artisan's tools of your choice: smith's tools, brewer's supplies, or mason's tools.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Duergar Resilience</name>
				<source type="string">Duergar</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against illusions and against being charmed or paralyzed.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sunlight Sensitivity</name>
				<source type="string">Duergar</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have disadvantage on attack rolls and on Wisdom (Perception) checks that rely on sight when you, the target of your attack, or whatever you are trying to perceive is in direct sunlight.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Duergar Magic</name>
				<source type="string">Duergar</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 3rd level, you can cast the <i>enlarge/reduce </i>spell on yourself once with this trait, using only the spell's enlarge option. When you reach 5th level, you can cast the <i>invisibility </i>spell on yourself once with this trait. You don't need material components for either spell, and you can't cast them while you're in direct sunlight, although sunlight has no effect on them once cast. You regain the ability to cast these spells with this trait when you finish a long rest. Intelligence is your spellcasting ability for these spells.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.enlarge_reduce@*"><b>Spell: </b></link>enlarge/Reduce</linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.invisibility@*"><b>Spell: </b></link>Invisibility
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00007>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">1</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">slashing,magic</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<handling type="number">0</handling>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Mithril Battleaxe of Elemental Slaying</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10), finesse</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00027</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">slashing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<handling type="number">1</handling>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Battleaxe</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00018</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">strength</stat>
						<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
						<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<handling type="number">1</handling>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Warhammer</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00024</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00003>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">200lbs</weight>
	</character>
</root>
