<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:3">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">5</save>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">-1</save>
				<score type="number">8</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">8</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<age type="string">45</age>
		<alignment type="string">Lawful Good</alignment>
		<appearance type="string">I've got that rough, soldier sort of look. Plenty of scars. But not bad overall.</appearance>
		<background type="string">Battlesmith</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>background.id-00005@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">I am still bound by loyalty and oath to my lord. If he calls me back, I will go.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">2</casterlevelinvmult>
				<hddie type="dice">d10</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<name type="string">Paladin</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>class.propaladin@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">15</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">EP</name>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">6</armor>
				<dexbonus type="string">no</dexbonus>
				<disstealth type="number">1</disstealth>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">2</shield>
				<total type="number">18</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">80</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">160</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">480</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">147.71</load>
			<max type="number">240</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lay on Hands</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00424@Incarnate-Engine">Lay on Hands</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>Your blessed touch can heal wounds. You have a pool of healing power that replenishes when you take a long rest. With that pool, you can restore a total number of hit points equal to your paladin level x5.</p>
					<p>As an action, you can touch a creature and draw power from the pool to restore a number of hit points to that creature, up to the maximum amount remaining in your pool.</p>
					<p>Alternatively, you can expend 5 hit points from your pool of healing to cure the target of one disease or neutralize one poison affecting it. You can cure multiple diseases and neutralize multiple poisons with a single use of Lay on Hands, expending hit points separately for each one.</p>
					<p>This feature has no effect on undead and constructs.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Sense</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>The presence of strong evil registers on your senses like a noxious odor, and powerful good rings like heavenly music in your ears. As an action, you can open your awareness to detect such forces. Until the end of your next turn, you know the location of any celestial, fiend, or undead within 60 feet of you that is not behind total cover. You know the type (celestial, fiend, or undead) of any being whose presence you sense, but not its identity (the vampire Count Strahd von Zarovich, for instance).</p>
					<p>Within the same radius, you also detect the presence of any place or object that has been consecrated or desecrated, as with the hallow spell.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to 1 + your Charisma modifier. When you finish a long rest, you regain all expended uses.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00004>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Champion</name>
				<source type="string">Battlesmith</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You are or were, the champion of a patron, (likely a noble dwarven clan) and a known battlesmith. Your patron may come to you with demands or requests; enemies of your patron may try to buy, manipulate, or kill you; and you will likely have made some enemies of your own during your career. The life of a battlesmith can be busy, hectic, and complicated, even long after retirement or expulsion. Work with your GM to flesh out your patron, their enemies, and your personal enemies if you have any.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Smite</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00425@Incarnate-Engine">Divine Smite</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, when you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one spell slot to deal radiant damage to the target, in addition to the weapon's damage. The extra damage is 2d8 for a 1st-level spell slot, plus 1d8 for each spell level higher than 1st, to a maximum of 5d8. The damage increases by 1d8 if the target is an undead or a fiend.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>By 2nd level, you have learned to draw on divine magic through meditation and prayer to cast spells as a cleric does.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="lists.spells.paladin@Incarnate-Engine">Paladin Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Paladin table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells. To cast one of your paladin spells of 1st level or higher, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of paladin spells that are available for you to cast, choosing from the paladin spell list. When you do so, choose a number of paladin spells equal to your Charisma modifier + half your paladin level, rounded down (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you are a 5th-level paladin, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With a Charisma of 14, your list of prepared spells can include four spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination. If you prepare the 1st-level spell cure wounds, you can cast it using a 1st-level or a 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of paladin spells requires time spent in prayer and meditation: at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Charisma is your spellcasting ability for your paladin spells, since their power derives from the strength of your convictions. You use your Charisma whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Charisma modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a paladin spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a holy symbol as a spellcasting focus for your paladin spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you adopt a style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the following options. You can't take a Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.</p>
					<p><b>Defense</b></p>
					<p>While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00428@Incarnate-Engine">Fighting Style - Defense</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Dueling</b></p>
					<p>When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00427@Incarnate-Engine">Fighting Style - Dueling</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Great Weapon Fighting</b></p>
					<p>When you roll a 1 or 2 on a damage die for an attack you make with a melee weapon that you are wielding with two hands, you can reroll the die and must use the new roll. The weapon must have the two-handed or versatile property for you to gain this benefit.</p>
					<p><b>Protection</b></p>
					<p>When a creature you can see attacks a target other than you that is within 5 feet of you, you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on the attack roll. You must be wielding a shield.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00426@Incarnate-Engine">Fighting Style - Protection</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Oath of Devotion</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>The Oath of Devotion binds a paladin to the loftiest ideals of justice, virtue, and order. Sometimes called cavaliers, white knights, or holy warriors, these paladins meet the ideal of the knight in shining armor, acting with honor in pursuit of justice and the greater good. They hold themselves to the highest standards of conduct, and some, for better or worse, hold the rest of the world to the same standards. Many who swear this oath are devoted to gods of law and good and use their gods' tenets as the measure of their devotion. They hold angels-the perfect servants of good-as their ideals, and incorporate images of angelic wings into their helmets or coats of arms.</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00026@Incarnate-Engine">Tenets of Devotion</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00022@Incarnate-Engine">Oath Spells (Devotion)</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00012@Incarnate-Engine">Channel Divinity (Devotion)</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00009@Incarnate-Engine">Aura of Devotion</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00023@Incarnate-Engine">Purity of Spirit</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00019@Incarnate-Engine">Holy Nimbus</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tenets of Devotion</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specialization type="string">Oath of Devotion</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Though the exact words and strictures of the Oath of Devotion vary, paladins of this oath share these tenets.</p>
					<p><b>Honesty. </b>Don't lie or cheat. Let your word be your promise.</p>
					<p><b>Courage. </b>Never fear to act, though caution is wise.</p>
					<p><b>Compassion. </b>Aid others, protect the weak, and punish those who threaten them. Show mercy to your foes, but temper it with wisdom.</p>
					<p><b>Honor. </b>Treat others with fairness, and let your honorable deeds be an example to them. Do as much good as possible while causing the least amount of harm.</p>
					<p><b>Duty. </b>Be responsible for your actions and their consequences, protect those entrusted to your care, and obey those who have just authority over you.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Channel Divinity (Devotion)</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specialization type="string">Oath of Devotion</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you take this oath at 3rd level, you gain the following two Channel Divinity options.</p>
					<p><b>Sacred Weapon. </b>As an action, you can imbue one weapon that you are holding with positive energy, using your Channel Divinity. For 1 minute, you add your Charisma modifier to attack rolls made with that weapon (with a minimum bonus of +1). The weapon also emits bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light 20 feet beyond that. If the weapon is not already magical, it becomes magical for the duration.</p>
					<p>You can end this effect on your turn as part of any other action. If you are no longer holding or carrying this weapon, or if you fall unconscious, this effect ends.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00429@Incarnate-Engine">Sacred Weapon</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Turn the Unholy. </b>As an action, you present your holy symbol and speak a prayer censuring fiends and undead, using your Channel Divinity. Each fiend or undead that can see or hear you within 30 feet of you must make a Wisdom saving throw. If the creature fails its saving throw, it is turned for 1 minute or until it takes damage.</p>
					<p>A turned creature must spend its turns trying to move as far away from you as it can, and it can't willingly move to a space within 30 feet of you. It also can't take reactions. For its action, it can use only the Dash action or try to escape from an effect that prevents it from moving. If there's nowhere to move, the creature can use the Dodge action.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00430@Incarnate-Engine">Turn the Unholy</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Health</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00431@Incarnate-Engine">Divine Health</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>By 3rd level, the divine magic flowing through you makes you immune to disease.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Oath Spells (Devotion)</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specialization type="string">Oath of Devotion</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain oath spells at the paladin levels listed.</p>
					<h>Oath of Devotion Spells</h>
					<p><b>Paladin Level - Spell</b></p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00228@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 3rd - Protection from Evil and Good</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00244@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 3rd - Sanctuary</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00172@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 5th - Lesser Restoration</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00030@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 9th - Beacon of Hope</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00088@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 9th - Dispel Magic</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00128@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 13th - Freedom of Movement</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00140@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 13th - Guardian of Faith</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00051@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 17th - Commune</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00119@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 17th - Flame Strike</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00012>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I realize that some claim that half-orcs may align with good. But I'm unconvinced. I'll definitely test every supposedly good one with Divine Sense.  If they're evil, it's time for battle.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">6 ft 1 inch</height>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">31</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">I fight for what's right and keep my oath of honesty, honor, and duty.</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<total type="number">0</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This letter is from your patron. If your patron is powerful and you are on a plane where they have influence then this letter may allow you to get into meetings with powerful people. If you try to use the letter to influence an enemy of your patron it very well may end with your impronment or death.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Letter from patron</name>
				<rarity type="string">Rare</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A chain has 10 hit points. It can be burst with a successful DC 20 Strength check.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Chain (5 Feet)</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Common</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hammer</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This metal flask is perfect for toting around a precious liquid. Whether alcohol, medicine, or a rare magical elixer, this flask will give it some protection against dropping and spilling the liquid.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Metal Flask</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tiny leather pouch is perfect for keeping your coins close at hand. Just watch out for someone trying to cut it off of your belt.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Coin Pouch - Small</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Oil usually comes in a clay flask that holds 1 pint. As an action, you can splash the oil in this flask onto a creature within 5 feet of you or throw it up to 20 feet, shattering it on impact. Make a ranged attack against a target creature or object, treating the oil as an improvised weapon. On a hit, the target is covered in oil. If the target takes any fire damage before the oil dries (after 1 minute), the target takes an additional 5 fire damage from the burning oil. You can also pour a flask of oil on the ground to cover a 5-foot-square area, provided that the surface is level. If lit, the oil burns for 2 rounds and deals 5 fire damage to any creature that enters the area or ends its turn in the area. A creature can take this damage only once per turn.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Oil (Flask)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This badge can be worn to publicly declare who you serve. In friendly places this earns you respect, but be careful of the enemies it may bring with it.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Badge showing patron's crest</name>
				<rarity type="string">Rare</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Whetstone</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">15 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 slashing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Longsword</name>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<ac type="number">2</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A shield is made from wood or metal and is carried in one hand. Wielding a shield increases your Armor Class by 2. You can benefit from only one shield at a time.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield (Wooden)</name>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Shield</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">5</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 piercing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Javelin</name>
				<properties type="string">Thrown (range 30/120)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">7</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack (Empty)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tin box contains a cup and simple cutlery. The box clamps together, and one side can be used as a cooking pan and the other as a plate or shallow bowl.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mess Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Equipment Kits</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<ac type="number">16</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">75 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Of all the armor categories, heavy armor offers the best protection. These suits of armor cover the entire body and are designed to stop a wide range of attacks. Only proficient warriors can manage their weight and bulk.</p>
					<p>Made of interlocking metal rings, chain mail includes a layer of quilted fabric worn underneath the mail to prevent chafing and to cushion the impact of blows. The suit includes gauntlets.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Chain Mail</name>
				<stealth type="string">Disadvantage</stealth>
				<strength type="string">Str 13</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Heavy Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">55</weight>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A holy symbol is a representation of a god or pantheon. It might be an amulet depicting a symbol representing a deity, the same symbol carefully engraved or inlaid as an emblem on a shield, or a tiny box holding a fragment of a sacred relic. Appendix B lists the symbols commonly associated with many gods in the multiverse. A cleric or paladin can use a holy symbol as a spellcasting focus. To use the symbol in this way, the caster must hold it in hand, wear it visibly, or bear it on a shield.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Amulet</name>
				<subtype type="string">Holy Symbol</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00022>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Elvish</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Dwarvish</name>
			</id-00003>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">3</level>
		<name type="string">Eldor</name>
		<perception type="number">11</perception>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I live to vanquish evil. Unfortunately, my lord's realm has had an extended time of peace and prosperity where the need to battle comes very seldom. He knew of my discontent with a sedentary life and gave me leave to go battle in other regions where evil creatures oppress the populace.</personalitytraits>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">4</prepared>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
			</id-00001>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">3</max>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">combat</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch regains a number of hit points equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cure Wounds</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">DMG: 1d4 radiant; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your prayer empowers you with divine radiance. Until the spell ends, your weapon attacks deal an extra 1d4 radiant damage on a hit.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Favor</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">AC: 2; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a small parchment with a bit of holy text written on it)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A shimmering field appears and surrounds a creature of your choice within range, granting it a +2 bonus to AC for the duration.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield of Faith</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Paladin</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">ATK: 1d4; SAVE: 1d4; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a sprinkling of holy water)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You bless up to three creatures of your choice within range. Whenever a target makes an attack roll or a saving throw before the spell ends, the target can roll a d4 and add the number rolled to the attack roll or saving throw.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bless</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Paladin</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">single</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">ATK: 1; DMGTYPE: magic</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>As an action, you can imbue one weapon that you are holding with positive energy, using your Channel Divinity. For 1 minute, you add your Charisma modifier to attack rolls made with that weapon (with a minimum bonus of +1). The weapon also emits bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light 20 feet beyond that. If the weapon is not already magical, it becomes magical for the duration.You can end this effect on your turn as part of any other action. If you are no longer holding or carrying this weapon, or if you fall unconscious, this effect ends.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sacred Weapon - Channel Div</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">paladin</stat>
							</id-00001>
							<id-00002>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">paladin</stat>
							</id-00002>
							<id-00003>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">paladin</stat>
							</id-00003>
							<id-00004>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">paladin</stat>
							</id-00004>
							<id-00005>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">paladin</stat>
							</id-00005>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">5</bonus>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00424@Incarnate-Engine">Lay on Hands</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>Your blessed touch can heal wounds. You have a pool of healing power that replenishes when you take a long rest. With that pool, you can restore a total number of hit points equal to your paladin level x5.</p>
					<p>As an action, you can touch a creature and draw power from the pool to restore a number of hit points to that creature, up to the maximum amount remaining in your pool.</p>
					<p>Alternatively, you can expend 5 hit points from your pool of healing to cure the target of one disease or neutralize one poison affecting it. You can cure multiple diseases and neutralize multiple poisons with a single use of Lay on Hands, expending hit points separately for each one.</p>
					<p>This feature has no effect on undead and constructs.</p>
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lay on Hands</name>
				<prepared type="number">15</prepared>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The presence of strong evil registers on your senses like a noxious odor, and powerful good rings like heavenly music in your ears. As an action, you can open your awareness to detect such forces. Until the end of your next turn, you know the location of any celestial, fiend, or undead within 60 feet of you that is not behind total cover. You know the type (celestial, fiend, or undead) of any being whose presence you sense, but not its identity (the vampire Count Strahd von Zarovich, for instance).</p>
					<p>Within the same radius, you also detect the presence of any place or object that has been consecrated or desecrated, as with the hallow spell.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to 1 + your Charisma modifier. When you finish a long rest, you regain all expended uses.</p>
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Sense</name>
				<prepared type="number">4</prepared>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">day</durunit>
						<label type="string">Fighting Style - Dueling; DMG: 2, melee</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style - Dueling</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">IFT: TYPE(aberration, celestial, elemental, fey, fiend, undead); GRANTDISATK; IMMUNE: charmed,frightened,possessed; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (holy water or powdered silver and iron, which the spell consumes)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Until the spell ends, one willing creature you touch is protected against certain types of creatures: aberrations, celestials, elementals, fey, fiends, and undead.</p>
					<p>The protection grants several benefits. Creatures of those types have disadvantage on attack rolls against the target. The target also can't be charmed, frightened, or possessed by them. If the target is already charmed, frightened, or possessed by such a creature, the target has advantage on any new saving throw against the relevant effect.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">1-Protection from Evil and Good - Oath</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Paladin, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">NOTE: Sanctuary</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a small silver mirror)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You ward a creature within range against attack. Until the spell ends, any creature who targets the warded creature with an attack or a harmful spell must first make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, the creature must choose a new target or lose the attack or spell. This spell doesn't protect the warded creature from area effects, such as the explosion of a fireball. If the warded creature makes an attack or casts a spell that affects an enemy creature, this spell ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">2-Sanctuary - Oath</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You speak a one-word command to a creature you can see within range. The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or follow the command on its next turn. The spell has no effect if the target is undead, if it doesn't understand your language, or if your command is directly harmful to it.</p>
					<p>Some typical commands and their effects follow. You might issue a command other than one described here. If you do so, the GM determines how the target behaves. If the target can't follow your command, the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>Approach. </b>The target moves toward you by the shortest and most direct route, ending its turn if it moves within 5 feet of you.</p>
					<p><b>Drop. </b>The target drops whatever it is holding and then ends its turn.</p>
					<p><b>Flee. </b>The target spends its turn moving away from you by the fastest available means.</p>
					<p><b>Grovel. </b>The target falls prone and then ends its turn.</p>
					<p><b>Halt. </b>The target doesn't move and takes no actions. A flying creature stays aloft, provided that it is able to do so. If it must move to stay aloft, it flies the minimum distance needed to remain in the air.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can affect one additional creature for each slot level above 1st. The creatures must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Command</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Paladin</source>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you know if there is an aberration, celestial, elemental, fey, fiend, or undead within 30 feet of you, as well as where the creature is located. Similarly, you know if there is a place or object within 30 feet of you that has been magically consecrated or desecrated.</p>
					<p>The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Evil and Good</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Paladin</source>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any.</p>
					<p>The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Magic</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a yew leaf)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you can sense the presence and location of poisons, poisonous creatures, and diseases within 30 feet of you. You also identify the kind of poison, poisonous creature, or disease in each case. The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Poison and Disease</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A willing creature you touch is imbued with bravery.</p>
					<p>Until the spell ends, the creature is immune to being frightened and gains temporary hit points equal to your spellcasting ability modifier at the start of each of its turns. When the spell ends, the target loses any remaining temporary hit points from this spell.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heroism</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Paladin</source>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>All nonmagical food and drink within a5-foot-radius sphere centered on a point of your choice within range is purified and rendered free of poison and disease.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Purify Food and Drink</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin</source>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">ability</savedcbase>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savedcstat type="string">charisma</savedcstat>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Turned</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>As an action, you present your holy symbol and speak a prayer censuring fiends and undead, using your Channel Divinity. Each fiend or undead that can see or hear you within 30 feet of you must make a Wisdom saving throw. If the creature fails its saving throw, it is turned for 1 minute or until it takes damage.A turned creature must spend its turns trying to move as far away from you as it can, and it can't willingly move to a space within 30 feet of you. It also can't take reactions. For its action, it can use only the Dash action or try to escape from an effect that prevents it from moving. If there's nowhere to move, the creature can use the Dodge action.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Turn the Unholy - Channel Div</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<name type="string">Channel Divinity</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00023>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Divine Smite; DMG: 2d8 radiant</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, when you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one spell slot to deal radiant damage to the target, in addition to the weapon's damage. The extra damage is 2d8 for a 1st-level spell slot, plus 1d8 for each spell level higher than 1st, to a maximum of 5d8. The damage increases by 1d8 if the target is an undead or a fiend.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Smite</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00023>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">2</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple weapons, martial weapons</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Armor: All armor, shields</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Tool: Smith's Tools, Mason's Tools</name>
			</id-00003>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Half-Elf</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>race.id-00007@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<senses type="string">Darkvision 60</senses>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Skill Versatility</name>
				<source type="string">Half-Elf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain proficiency in two skills of your choice.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fey Ancestry</name>
				<source type="string">Half-Elf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against being charmed, and magic can't put you to sleep.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">slashing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<name type="string">Longsword</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00010</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<name type="string">Javelin</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00012</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<name type="string">Javelin</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00012</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00003>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">220</weight>
	</character>
</root>
