<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:3">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">6</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">17</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">4</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">13</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">15</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">11</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">43</age>
		<alignment type="string">Chaotic Neutral</alignment>
		<appearance type="string">Feldis is a tall female Antilonoid with features akin to that of a goat. Her usual attire is a short blouse, cut off to show her midriff, a red vest with white frills, and a short pleated skirt. She worked in a Speakeasy, where she found that a knack for deception was a necessary job skill. She used her charm to get what she wanted. But after an incident with one of the patrons, she decided to venture forth into the world, in search of the person who protected her that day.</appearance>
		<background type="string">Barmaid</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>background.id-00004@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">I will never forget the name of the adventurer who saved me from a cruel fate.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d6</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">5</level>
				<name type="string">Sorcerer</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.sorcerer@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">146</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">6</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">8</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">25</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">0</armor>
				<disstealth type="number">0</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">12</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<deity type="string">Aphrodite</deity>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">50</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">100</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">300</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">48.78</load>
			<max type="number">150</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">570</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">600</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Plastered Persuasion</name>
				<source type="string">Barmaid</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>After spending years tending to the regular drunkards and new faces in the establishment you work in, you have become an expert at getting what you want from the drunk, the tipsy and the plastered.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wild Magic</name>
				<source type="string">Sorcerer</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your innate magic comes from the wild forces of chaos that underlie the order of creation. You might have endured exposure to some form of raw magic, perhaps through a planar portal leading to Limbo, the Elemental Planes, or the mysterious Far Realm. Perhaps you were blessed by a powerful fey creature or marked by a demon. Or your magic could be a fluke of your birth, with no apparent cause or reason. However it came to be, this chaotic magic churns within you, waiting for any outlet.</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.sorcerer.features.wildmagicsurge1@DD PHB Deluxe">Wild Magic Surge</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.sorcerer.features.tidesofchaos1@DD PHB Deluxe">Tides of Chaos</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.sorcerer.features.bendluck6@DD PHB Deluxe">Bend Luck</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.sorcerer.features.controlledchaos14@DD PHB Deluxe">Controlled Chaos</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.sorcerer.features.spellbombardment18@DD PHB Deluxe">Spell Bombardment</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Sorcerer</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>An event in your past, or in the life of a parent or ancestor, left an indelible mark on you, infusing you with arcane magic. This font of magic, whatever its origin, fuels your spells.</p>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you know four cantrips of your choice from the sorcerer spell list. You learn additional sorcerer cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Sorcerer table.</p>
					<p><b>Spell Slots</b></p>
					<p>The Sorcerer table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these sorcerer spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>For example, if you know the 1st-level spell <i>burning hands </i>and have a 1st-level and a 2nd-level spell slot available, you can cast <i>burning hands </i>using either slot.</p>
					<p><b>Spells Known of 1st Level and Higher</b></p>
					<p>You know two 1st-level spells of your choice from the sorcerer spell list.</p>
					<p>The Spells Known column of the Sorcerer table shows when you learn more sorcerer spells of your choice. Each of these spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots. For instance, when you reach 3rd level in this class, you can learn one new spell of 1st or 2nd level.</p>
					<p>Additionally, when you gain a level in this class, you can choose one of the sorcerer spells you know and replace it with another spell from the sorcerer spell list, which also must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Charisma is your spellcasting ability for your sorcerer spells, since the power of your magic relies on your ability to project your will into the world. You use your Charisma whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Charisma modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a sorcerer spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use an arcane focus as a spellcasting focus for your sorcerer spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wild Magic Surge</name>
				<source type="string">Sorcerer</source>
				<specialization type="string">Wild Magic</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting when you choose this origin at 1st level, your spellcasting can unleash surges of untamed magic.</p>
					<p>Immediately after you cast a sorcerer spell of 1st level or higher, the DM can have you roll a d20. If you roll a 1, roll on the Wild Magic Surge table to create a random magical effect. If a Wild Magic effect is a spell, it's too wild to be affected by Metamagic. If it normally requires concentration, it doesn't require concentration in this case; the spell lasts for its full duration.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="table" recordname="tables.tab_wildmagicsurge@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Table: </b></link>Wild Magic Surge Table</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tides of Chaos</name>
				<source type="string">Sorcerer</source>
				<specialization type="string">Wild Magic</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 1st level, you can manipulate the forces of chance and chaos to gain advantage on one attack roll, ability check, or saving throw. Once you do so, you must finish a long rest before you can use this feature again. Any time before you regain the use of this feature, the DM can have you roll on the Wild Magic Surge table immediately after you cast a sorcerer spell of 1st level or higher. You then regain the use of this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Font of Magic</name>
				<source type="string">Sorcerer</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you tap into a deep wellspring of magic within yourself. This wellspring is represented by sorcery points, which allow you to create a variety of magical effects.</p>
					<p><b>Sorcery Points</b></p>
					<p>You have 2 sorcery points, and you gain more as you reach higher levels, as shown in the Sorcery Points column of the Sorcerer table. You can never have more sorcery points than shown on the table for your level. You regain all spent sorcery points when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p><b>Flexible Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can use your sorcery points to gain additional spell slots, or sacrifice spell slots to gain additional sorcery points. You learn other ways to use your sorcery points as you reach higher levels. The created spell slots vanish at the end of a long rest.</p>
					<p><b>Creating Spell Slots. </b>You can transform unexpended sorcery points into one spell slot as a bonus action on your turn. The Creating Spell Slots table shows the cost of creating a spell slot of a given level. You can create spell slots no higher in level than 5th.</p>
					<p><b>Creating Spell Slots</b></p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Spell Slot Sorcery Level</b></td>
							<td><b>Point Cost</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>1st</td>
							<td>2</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2nd</td>
							<td>3</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>3rd</td>
							<td>5</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4th</td>
							<td>6</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>5th</td>
							<td>7</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>Converting a Spell Slot to Sorcery Points. As a bonus action on your turn, you can expend one spell slot and gain a number of sorcery points equal to the slot's level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Metamagic</name>
				<source type="string">Sorcerer</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level, you gain the ability to twist your spells to suit your needs. You gain two of the following Metamagic options of your choice. You gain another one at 10th and 17th level.</p>
					<p>You can use only one Metamagic option on a spell when you cast it, unless otherwise noted.</p>
					<p><b>Careful Spell</b></p>
					<p>When you cast a spell that forces other creatures to make a saving throw, you can protect some of those creatures from the spell's full force. To do so, you spend 1 sorcery point and choose a number of those creatures up to your Charisma modifier (minimum of one creature). A chosen creature automatically succeeds on its saving throw against the spell.</p>
					<p><b>Distant Spell</b></p>
					<p>When you cast a spell that has a range of 5 feet or greater, you can spend 1 sorcery point to double the range of the spell.</p>
					<p>When you cast a spell that has a range of touch, you can spend 1 sorcery point to make the range of the spell 30 feet.</p>
					<p><b>Empowered Spell</b></p>
					<p>When you roll damage for a spell, you can spend 1 sorcery point to reroll a number of the damage dice up to your Charisma modifier (minimum of one). You must use the new rolls.</p>
					<p>You can use Empowered Spell even if you have already used a different Metamagic option during the casting of the spell.</p>
					<p><b>Extended Spell</b></p>
					<p>When you cast a spell that has a duration of 1 minute or longer, you can spend 1 sorcery point to double its duration, to a maximum duration of 24 hours.</p>
					<p><b>Heightened Spell</b></p>
					<p>When you cast a spell that forces a creature to make a saving throw to resist its effects, you can spend 3 sorcery points to give one target of the spell disadvantage on its first saving throw made against the spell.</p>
					<p><b>Quickened Spell</b></p>
					<p>When you cast a spell that has a casting time of 1 action, you can spend 2 sorcery points to change the casting time to 1 bonus action for this casting.</p>
					<p><b>Subtle Spell</b></p>
					<p>When you cast a spell, you can spend 1 sorcery point to cast it without any somatic or verbal components.</p>
					<p><b>Twinned Spell</b></p>
					<p>When you cast a spell that targets only one creature and doesn't have a range of self, you can spend a number of sorcery points equal to the spell's level to target a second creature in range with the same spell (1 sorcery point if the spell is a cantrip). To be eligible for Twinned Spell, a spell must be incapable of targeting more than one creature at the spell's current level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<source type="string">Sorcerer</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I'm willing to try anything I think will be a good time.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Female</gender>
		<height type="string">6' 4&#34;</height>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">27</total>
			<wounds type="number">15</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Fickle - My time is worth whoever is paying me. (Chaotic)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">2</total>
		</initiative>
		<inspiration type="number">0</inspiration>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Flask</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Flask</location>
				<name type="string">Ale</name>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A hand written note from your defender.</p>
					<p><i>Leave this place.</i></p>
					<p><i>Find your way in the world.</i></p>
					<p><i>Let your skills be the only boundary you have.</i></p>
					<p><i>Live.</i></p>
					<p><i>-Gripe Ten-Arm</i></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Pouch</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Defender's Note</name>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<count type="number">3</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Component Pouch</location>
				<name type="string">Poisonous berries</name>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Belt</location>
				<name type="string">Pouch</name>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A component pouch is a small, watertight leather belt pouch that has compartments to hold all the material components and other special items you need to cast your spells, except for those components that have a specific cost (as indicated in a spell's description).</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Belt</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Component Pouch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Piton</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.25</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">0</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Pouch</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Belt</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hammer</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">0</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Using a crowbar grants advantage to Strength checks where the crowbar's leverage can be applied.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Crowbar</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<damage type="string">1d4 piercing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Belt</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shortbow</name>
				<properties type="string">Ammunition (range 80/320), two-handed</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Ranged Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Shortbow</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Arrows (20)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Ammunition</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d4 bludgeoning</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A short leather-wrapped iron weight</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Belt</location>
				<locked type="number">0</locked>
				<name type="string">Blackjack</name>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A tail cut from a common lizard.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Component Pouch</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lizard tail</name>
				<weight type="number">0.02</weight>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<count type="number">3</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Component Pouch</location>
				<name type="string">Healthy-looking berries</name>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<count type="number">3</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Component Pouch</location>
				<name type="string">Gut-ache berries</name>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<count type="number">3</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Component Pouch</location>
				<name type="string">Sleepy berries</name>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">50 GV</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Pouch</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Small Pearl</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00025>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">44 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00184@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: Magic Missile</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>This <u>spell scroll </u>bears the words of a single spell, <i>Magic Missile </i>, written in a mystical cipher. If the spell is on your class's spell list, you can read the scroll and cast its spell without providing any material components. Otherwise, the scroll is unintelligible. Casting the spell by reading the scroll requires the spell's normal casting time. Once the spell is cast, the words on the scroll fade, and it crumbles to dust. If the casting is interrupted, the scroll is not lost.</p>
					<p>If the spell is on your class's spell list but of a higher level than you can normally cast, you must make an ability check using your spellcasting ability to determine whether you cast it successfully. The DC equals 10 + the spell's level. On a failed check, the spell disappears from the scroll with no other effect.</p>
					<p>Once the spell is cast, the words on the scroll fade, and the scroll itself crumbles to dust.</p>
					<p>This spell scroll's saving throw DC 13 and attack bonus +5.</p>
					<p>A wizard spell on a <i>spell scroll </i>can be copied just as spells in spellbooks can be copied. When a spell is copied from a <i>spell scroll </i>, the copier must succeed on an Intelligence (Arcana) check with a DC equal to 10 + the spell's level. If the check succeeds, the spell is successfully copied. Whether the check succeeds or fails, the <i>spell scroll </i>is destroyed.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Scroll of Magic Missile</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Fine Scroll</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">The parchment of this scroll is of the finest quality and the writing is careful and delicate.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<spells>
					<id-00001>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class>reference_spell</class>
							<recordname>reference.spelldata.magicmissile@*</recordname>
						</link>
						<name type="string">Magic Missile</name>
					</id-00001>
				</spells>
				<type type="string">Scroll</type>
				<weight type="number">0.02</weight>
			</id-00025>
			<id-00026>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Barmaid Outfit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00026>
			<id-00027>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">902 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d4 piercing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
					<p>Adamantine weapons were designed to be unbreakable. This strange allow puts up with so much abuse, that their wielders can let loose. They can swing harder at inanimate objects without fearing destroying their blades, and so they do. You get an automatic critical against any inanimate object when using an adamantine weapon.</p>
					<p>Was stolen from the dwarves, they are looking for it.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<location type="string">Lead Box</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Adamantine Dagger</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Dagger</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A finely crafted dagger.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Finesse light thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00027>
			<id-00029>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<name type="string">Lead Box</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00029>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Plainstongue</name>
			</id-00002>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">5</level>
		<name type="string">Feldis Harlequin</name>
		<notes type="string">Check mystery berries\n__- Poison = NW 5-5\n__- Regular = NW 5-51\n__- Sleep = C 5-6\n__- Ache = C 5-6</notes>
		<perception type="number">10</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I understand that sometimes a little bit of flirting goes a long way.\nSleazebag pervert is one bad comment away from a slap.</personalitytraits>
		<powerdisplaymode type="string">action</powerdisplaymode>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<savemod type="number">0</savemod>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<uses type="number">0</uses>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Effect</name>
			</id-00002>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">4</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">1</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">2</max>
				<used type="number">1</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">standard</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">ability</savedcbase>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savedcstat type="string">strength</savedcstat>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
								<stat type="string">constitution</stat>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can use your action to headbutt a creature within 10 feet of you. Your target makes a Dexterity saving throw. The dc for this saving throw equals 8 + your strength modifier + your proficiency bonus. On a failure, the target takes bludgeoning damage equal to 1d6 + your Constitution modifier and is knocked five feet away from you. You automatically move to their previous position. On a success, they take no damage and can make an opportunity attack.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Horns (Antilonoid)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: charisma; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">S, M (a small amount of makeup applied to the face as this spell is cast)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you have advantage on all Charisma checks directed at one creature of your choice that isn't hostile toward you. When the spell ends, the creature realizes that you used magic to influence its mood and becomes hostile toward you. A creature prone to violence might attack you. Another creature might seek retribution in other ways (at the DM's discretion), depending on the nature of your interaction with it.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Friends</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<type type="string">lightning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Lightning springs from your hand to deliver a shock to a creature you try to touch. Make a melee spell attack against the target. You have advantage on the attack roll if the target is wearing armor made of metal. On a hit, the target takes 1d8 lightning damage, and it can't take reactions until the start of its next turn.</p>
					<p>The spell's damage increases by 1d8 when you reach 5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shocking Grasp</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell is a minor magical trick that novice spellcasters use for practice. You create one of the following magical effects within range:</p>
					<list>
						<li>You create an instantaneous, harmless sensory effect, such as a shower of sparks, a puff of wind, faint musical notes, or an odd odor.</li>
						<li>You instantaneously light or snuff out a candle, a torch, or a small campfire.</li>
						<li>You instantaneously clean or soil an object no larger than 1 cubic foot.</li>
						<li>You chill, warm, or flavor up to 1 cubic foot of nonliving material for 1 hour.</li>
						<li>You make a color, a small mark, or a symbol appear on an object or a surface for 1 hour.</li>
						<li>You create a nonmagical trinket or an illusory image that can fit in your hand and that lasts until the end of your next turn.</li>
					</list>
					<p>If you cast this spell multiple times, you can have up to three of its non-instantaneous effects active at a time, and you can dismiss such an effect as an action.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Prestidigitation</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d12</dice>
								<type type="string">poison</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You extend your hand toward a creature you can see within range and project a puff of noxious gas from your palm. The creature must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or take 1d12 poison damage.</p>
					<p>This spell's damage increases by 1d12 when you reach 5th level (2d12), 11th level (3d12), and 17th level (4d12).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Poison Spray</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a bit of phosphorus or wychwood, or a glowworm)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create up to four torch-sized lights within range, making them appear as torches, lanterns, or glowing orbs that hover in the air for the duration. You can also combine the four lights into one glowing vaguely humanoid form of Medium size. Whichever form you choose, each light sheds dim light in a 10-foot radius.</p>
					<p>As a bonus action on your turn, you can move the lights up to 60 feet to a new spot within range. A light must be within 20 feet of another light created by this spell, and a light winks out if it exceeds the spell's range.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dancing Lights</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">ability</savedcbase>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savedcstat type="string">charisma</savedcstat>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Charmed</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You attempt to charm a humanoid you can see within range. It must make a Wisdom saving throw, and does so with advantage if you or your companions are fighting it. If it fails the saving throw, it is charmed by you until the spell ends or until you or your companions do anything harmful to it. The charmed creature regards you as a friendly acquaintance. When the spell ends, the creature knows it was charmed by you.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st. The creatures must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Charm Person</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Trickery Domain, Druid, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you cast a spell that forces a creature to make a saving throw to resist its effects, you can spend 3 sorcery points to give one target of the spell disadvantage on its first saving throw made against the spell.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heightened Spell (3SP)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00002>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">ADVATK</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 1st level, you can manipulate the forces of chance and chaos to gain advantage on one attack roll, ability check, or saving throw. Once you do so, you must finish a long rest before you can use this feature again. Any time before you regain the use of this feature, the DM can have you roll on the Wild Magic Surge table immediately after you cast a sorcerer spell of 1st level or higher. You then regain the use of this feature.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tides of Chaos</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Sorcerer</source>
				<specialization type="string">Wild Magic</specialization>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you cast a spell, you can spend 1 sorcery point to cast it without any somatic or verbal components.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Subtle Spell (1SP)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">8</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">AC: 3</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a piece of cured leather)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a willing creature who isn't wearing armor, and a protective magical force surrounds it until the spell ends. The target's base AC becomes 13 + its Dexterity modifier. The spell ends if the target dons armor or if you dismiss the spell as an action.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mage Armor</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Eldritch Invocations, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">ability</savedcbase>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savedcstat type="string">charisma</savedcstat>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, M (a snake's tongue and either a bit of honeycomb or a drop of sweet oil)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You suggest a course of activity (limited to a sentence or two) and magically influence a creature you can see within range that can hear and understand you.</p>
					<p>Creatures that can't be charmed are immune to this effect. The suggestion must be worded in such a manner as to make the course of action sound reasonable.</p>
					<p>Asking the creature to stab itself, throw itself onto a spear, immolate itself, or do some other obviously harmful act ends the spell.</p>
					<p>The target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, it pursues the course of action you described to the best of its ability. The suggested course of action can continue for the entire duration. If the suggested activity can be completed in a shorter time, the spell ends when the subject finishes what it was asked to do. You can also specify conditions that will trigger a special activity during the duration. For example, you might suggest that a knight give her warhorse to the first beggar she meets. If the condition isn't met before the spell expires, the activity isn't performed.</p>
					<p>If you or any of your companions damage the target, the spell ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Suggestion</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Knowledge Domain, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a copper piece)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you can read the thoughts of certain creatures. When you cast the spell and as your action on each turn until the spell ends, you can focus your mind on any one creature that you can see within 30 feet of you. If the creature you choose has an Intelligence of 3 or lower or doesn't speak any language, the creature is unaffected.</p>
					<p>You initially learn the surface thoughts of the creature-what is most on its mind in that moment. As an action, you can either shift your attention to another creature's thoughts or attempt to probe deeper into the same creature's mind. If you probe deeper, the target must make a Wisdom saving throw. If it fails, you gain insight into its reasoning (if any), its emotional state, and something that looms large in its mind (such as something it worries over, loves, or hates). If it succeeds, the spell ends. Either way, the target knows that you are probing into its mind, and unless you shift your attention to another creature's thoughts, the creature can use its action on its turn to make an Intelligence check contested by your Intelligence check; if it succeeds, the spell ends.</p>
					<p>Questions verbally directed at the target creature naturally shape the course of its thoughts, so this spell is particularly effective as part of an interrogation. You can also use this spell to detect the presence of thinking creatures you can't see. When you cast the spell or as your action during the duration, you can search for thoughts within 30 feet of you. The spell can penetrate barriers, but 2 feet of rock, 2 inches of any metal other than lead, or a thin sheet of lead blocks you. You can't detect a creature with an Intelligence of 3 or lower or one that doesn't speak any language.</p>
					<p>Once you detect the presence of a creature in this way, you can read its thoughts for the rest of the duration as described above, even if you can't see it, but it must still be within range.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Thoughts</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Warlock (Great Old One), Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<label type="string">DMG: [-DEX]</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">*Offhand</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Dodge</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">*Dodge</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Incapacitated; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">S, M (a glowing stick of incense or a crystal vial filled with phosphorescent material)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create a twisting pattern of colors that weaves through the air inside a 30-foot cube within range. The pattern appears for a moment and vanishes. Each creature in the area who sees the pattern must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, the creature becomes charmed for the duration. While charmed by this spell, the creature is incapacitated and has a speed of 0.</p>
					<p>The spell ends for an affected creature if it takes any damage or if someone else uses an action to shake the creature out of its stupor.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hypnotic Pattern</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<label type="string">Musk; SAVE: [-PRF]</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">*Musk</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">poison</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<label type="string">Poisoned</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A ray of sickening greenish energy lashes out toward a creature within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes 2d8 poison damage and must make a Constitution saving throw.</p>
					<p>On a failed save, it is also poisoned until the end of your next turn.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ray of Sickness</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Necromancy</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00019>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">3</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Daggers, darts, slings, quarterstaffs, light crossbows</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00007>
				<name type="string">Tool: Brewer's Supplies</name>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<name type="string">Tool: Dice Set</name>
			</id-00008>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Antilonoid (Old Ways)</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>race.id-00002@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion &#38; Intimidation &#38; Deception &#38; Performance with opposite gender</name>
				<prof type="number">2</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">9</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Brewer's Supplies</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00022>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Dice Set</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00022>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">40</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">40</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00007_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Enhanced Senses</name>
				<source type="string">Antilonoid</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on perception checks that rely on hearing and smell. You also have darkvision out to thirty feet, but can not discern color in darkness.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Horns</name>
				<source type="string">Antilonoid</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.id-00362@Incarnate-Engine">Horns (Antilonoid)</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You can use your action to headbutt a creature within 10 feet of you. Your target makes a Dexterity saving throw. The dc for this saving throw equals 8 + your strength modifier + your proficiency bonus. On a failure, the target takes bludgeoning damage equal to 1d6 + your Constitution modifier and is knocked five feet away from you. You automatically move to their previous position. On a success, they take no damage and can make an opportunity attack.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Subraces</name>
				<source type="string">Antilonoid</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_subrace" recordname="race.id-00002.subraces.id-00002@Incarnate-Engine">Integrated</link>
						<link class="reference_subrace" recordname="race.id-00002.subraces.id-00001@Incarnate-Engine">Old Ways</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Experienced Forager</name>
				<source type="string">Old Ways</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain proficiency in the Survival skill.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Musk</name>
				<source type="string">Old Ways</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>A sweet scent hangs around you that is intoxicating to humanoids of the opposite gender. You add twice your proficiency bonus to charisma checks against such creatures. Beasts have advantage on Wisdom checks to notice you.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00005>
		</traitlist>
		<weapon>
			<critdicebonus>
				<melee type="number">0</melee>
				<ranged type="number">0</ranged>
			</critdicebonus>
			<critrange>
				<melee type="number">20</melee>
				<ranged type="number">20</ranged>
			</critrange>
		</weapon>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00016</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">2</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00016</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<ammo type="number">0</ammo>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">20</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Shortbow</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00017</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">1</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Adamantine Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00027</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Blackjack</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00019</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
						<dice type="dice"></dice>
						<stat type="string">strength</stat>
						<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Unarmed strike</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class></class>
					<recordname></recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00006>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">160</weight>
	</character>
</root>
