<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:4">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">5</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">5</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">-1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">8</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Adventure 1; I awoke in a arena, lots of monsters all around, it was quite weird... then some millapeadian humanoid starting attacking the only other human bringing him down with a single swing, then a attacked a mushroom... the rest of the monsters attacked the millathingy and we dispatched post haste. we ended up in a colliseam and meet a wonderfully splended mouse name Simond who showed us our way out... one of the group asked for payment and the mouse handed out some copper,</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Adventure 2; we worke the next morning after traveling to town and going to a inn, we found and quest board and decided to attemp to pick up some ale from whear creatures in the woods, seems like a weird place to get ale but hey this is apparently a weird world. I just might fit in here...along the road we were attacked by a T-Rex and then ambushed by something controling some giant boars..</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
			</id-00003>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">17</age>
		<alignment type="string">CG</alignment>
		<appearance type="string">Gentalmen Jack wears a elegent in fasion black leather long coat, with a dark green Vest, black shirt and red tie, along with black leather soft heal boots and black leather pants, he carrys a Cane and a always seen wearing a top hat</appearance>
		<background type="string">Charlatan</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>reference.backgrounddata.charlatan@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">I fleeced the wrong person and must work to ensure that this individual never crosses paths with me or those I care about.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d8</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">1</hdused>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<name type="string">Bard</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.bard@DD Xanathar's Guide to Everything</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">72</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">30</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">5</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">1</armor>
				<disstealth type="number">0</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">14</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">40</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">80</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">240</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">70.18</load>
			<max type="number">120</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">416</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">0</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">False Identity</name>
				<source type="string">Charlatan</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have created a second identity that includes documentation, established acquaintances, and disguises that allow you to assume that persona.</p>
					<p>Additionally, you can forge documents including official papers and personal letters, as long as you have seen an example of the kind of document or the handwriting you are trying to copy.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have learned to untangle and reshape the fabric of reality in harmony with your wishes and music. Your spells are part of your vast repertoire, magic that you can tune to different situations. See chapter 10 for the general rules of spellcasting and chapter 11 for the bard spell list.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="reference.spelllists.bard@DD PHB Deluxe">Bard Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>You know two cantrips of your choice from the bard spell list. You learn additional bard cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Bard table.</p>
					<p><b>Spell Slots</b></p>
					<p>The Bard table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your bard spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You must finish a long rest to regain any expended spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you know the 1st-level spell cure wounds and have a 1st-level and a 2nd-level spell slot available, you can cast cure wounds using either slot.</p>
					<p><b>Spells Known of 1st Level and Higher</b></p>
					<p>You know four 1st-level spells of your choice from the bard spell list.</p>
					<p>The Spells Known column of the Bard table shows when you learn more bard spells of your choice. Each of these spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots, as shown on the table. For instance, when you reach 3rd level in this class, you can learn one new spell of 1st or 2nd level.</p>
					<p>Additionally, when you gain a level in this class, you can choose one of the spells you know and replace it with another spell from the bard spell list, which must be of a level for which you have spell slots, as shown on the table.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Charisma is your spellcasting ability for your bard spells, since the power of your magic comes from the heart and soul you pour into the performance of your music or oration. You use your Charisma whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Charisma modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a bard spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p><b>Spell Save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spell Attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast any bard spell you know as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag. To cast a spell as a ritual, you must add 10 minutes to the spell's casting time, as normal.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a musical instrument as the material component for a bard spell, as described in chapter 10.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bardic Inspiration</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can inspire others through stirring words or music. To do so, you use a bonus action on your turn to choose one creature other than yourself within 60 feet of you who can hear you. That creature gains one Bardic Inspiration die, a d6.</p>
					<p>Once within the next 10 minutes, the creature can roll the die and add the number rolled to one ability check, attack roll, or saving throw that it just made. The creature can wait until after it rolls the die for the ability check, attack roll, or saving throw, but before the DM says whether or not it succeeds or fails before deciding to use the Bardic Inspiration die. Once the Bardic Inspiration die is rolled, it is lost. A creature can have only one Bardic Inspiration die at a time.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Charisma modifier (a minimum of once). You regain any expended uses when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>Your Bardic Inspiration die changes when you reach certain levels in this class. The die becomes a d8 at 5th level, a d10 at 10th level, and a d12 at 15th level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Song of Rest</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning at 2nd level, you can use soothing music or oration to help revitalize your wounded allies during a short rest. If you or any friendly creature who can hear your performance regains any hit points during the short rest, that creature regains 1d6 extra hit points at the end of the rest. A creature regains the extra hit points only if it spends one or more Hit Dice at the end of the short rest.</p>
					<p>The extra hit points increase when you reach certain levels in this class: 1d8 at 9th level, 1d10 at 13th level, and 1d12 at 17th level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Jack of All Trades</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can add half your proficiency bonus, rounded down, to any ability check you make that doesn't already include that bonus.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">College of Whispers</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Most folk are happy to welcome a bard into their midst. Bards of the College of Whispers use this to their advantage. They appear to be like other bards, sharing news, singing songs, and telling tales to the audiences they gather.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="imagewindow" recordname="reference.imagedata.img_whisperbard_jpg@DD Xanathar's Guide to Everything"><b>Image: </b></link>Bard of the College of Whispers</linklist>
					<p>In truth, the College of Whispers teaches its students that they are wolves among sheep. These bards use their knowledge and magic to uncover secrets and turn them against others through extortion and threats.</p>
					<p>Many other bards hate the College of Whispers, viewing it as a parasite that uses a bard's reputation to acquire wealth and power.</p>
					<p>For this reason, members of this college rarely reveal their true nature. They typically claim to follow some other college, or they keep their actual calling secret in order to infiltrate and exploit royal courts and other settings of power.</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.bard.features.psychicblades3@DD Xanathar's Guide to Everything">Psychic Blades</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.bard.features.wordsofterror3@DD Xanathar's Guide to Everything">Words of Terror</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.bard.features.mantleofwhispers6@DD Xanathar's Guide to Everything">Mantle of Whispers</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.bard.features.shadowlore14@DD Xanathar's Guide to Everything">Shadow Lore</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Expertise</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level, choose two of your skill proficiencies. Your proficiency bonus is doubled for any ability check you make that involves one of the chosen proficiencies.</p>
					<p>At 10th level, you can choose another two skill proficiencies to gain this benefit.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Psychic Blades</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<specialization type="string">College of Whispers</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you join the College of Whispers at 3rd level, you gain the ability to make your weapon attacks magically toxic to a creature's mind.</p>
					<p>When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one use of your Bardic Inspiration to deal an extra 2d6 psychic damage to that target. You can do so only once per round on your turn.</p>
					<p>The psychic damage increases when you reach certain levels in this class, increasing to 3d6 at 5th level, 5d6 at 10th level, and 8d6 at 15th level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Words of Terror</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<specialization type="string">College of Whispers</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level, you learn to infuse innocent-seeming words with an insidious magic that can inspire terror.</p>
					<p>If you speak to a humanoid alone for at least 1 minute, you can attempt to seed paranoia in its mind. At the end of the conversation, the target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw against your spell save DC or be frightened of you or another creature of your choice. The target is frightened in this way for 1 hour, until it is attacked or damaged, or until it witnesses its allies being attacked or damaged.</p>
					<p>If the target succeeds on its saving throw, the target has no hint that you tried to frighten it.</p>
					<p>Once you use this feature, you can't use it again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I'm convinced that no one could ever fool me the way I fool others.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">5'</height>
		<hero type="number">3</hero>
		<herodice type="string">d6</herodice>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">3</temporary>
			<total type="number">24</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Aspiration. I'm determined to make something of myself. (Any)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">1</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">4</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rapier</name>
				<properties type="string">Finesse</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A lamp casts bright light in a 15-foot radius and dim light for an additional 30 feet. Once lit, it burns for 6 hours on a flask (1 pint) of oil.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lamp</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">15 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Fine</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ink (1-ounce Bottle)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.06</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Oil usually comes in a clay flask that holds 1 pint. As an action, you can splash the oil in this flask onto a creature within 5 feet of you or throw it up to 20 feet, shattering it on impact. Make a ranged attack against a target creature or object, treating the oil as an improvised weapon. On a hit, the target is covered in oil. If the target takes any fire damage before the oil dries (after 1 minute), the target takes an additional 5 fire damage from the burning oil. You can also pour a flask of oil on the ground to cover a 5-foot-square area, provided that the surface is level. If lit, the oil burns for 2 rounds and deals 5 fire damage to any creature that enters the area or ends its turn in the area. A creature can take this damage only once per turn.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Oil (Flask)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">5</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Paper (One Sheet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Chest</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">25</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sealing Wax</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.03</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This cylindrical leather case can hold up to ten rolled-up sheets of paper or five rolled-up sheets of parchment.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Case, Map Or Scroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ink Pen</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.02</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Vial</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Soap</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">30 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Several of the most common types of musical instruments are shown on the table as examples. If you have proficiency with a given musical instrument, you can add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make to play music with the instrument. A bard can use a musical instrument as a spellcasting focus, as described in Part 3: The Rules of Magic, Casting a Spell. Each type of musical instrument requires a separate proficiency.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lyre</name>
				<subtype type="string">Musical Instrument</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">600 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>These furred boots are snug and feel quite warm.</p>
					<p>While you wear them, you gain the following benefits:</p>
					<list>
						<li>You have resistance to cold damage.</li>
					</list>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.typeresistancecold@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Type Resistance (Cold)</link>
					</linklist>
					<list>
						<li>You ignore difficult terrain created by ice or snow.</li>
						<li>You can tolerate temperatures as low as -50 degrees Fahrenheit without any additional protection.</li>
					</list>
					<p>If you wear heavy clothes, you can tolerate temperatures as low as -100 degrees Fahrenheit.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Boots of the Winterlands</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Boots</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A pair of thick warm boots.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon (requires attunement)</rarity>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d4 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<ac type="number">11</ac>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Made from supple and thin materials, light armor favors agile adventurers since it offers some protection without sacrificing mobility. If you wear light armor, you add your Dexterity modifier to the base number from your armor type to determine your Armor Class.</p>
					<p>The breastplate and shoulder protectors of this armor are made of leather that has been stiffened by being boiled in oil. The rest of the armor is made of softer and more flexible materials.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">Yes</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Leather (Long Coat)</name>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Light Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This pouch of cosmetics, hair dye, and small props lets you create disguises that change your physical appearance. Proficiency with this kit lets you add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make to create a visual disguise.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Disguise Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Kits / Sets</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">15 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small box contains a variety of papers and parchments, pens and inks, seals and sealing wax, gold and silver leaf, and other supplies necessary to create convincing forgeries of physical documents. Proficiency with this kit lets you add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make to create a physical forgery of a document.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Forgery Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Kits / Sets</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A cloth or leather pouch can hold up to 20 sling bullets or 50 blowgun needles, among other things. A compartmentalized pouch for holding spell components is called a component pouch (described earlier in this section).</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Pouch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00019>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Elvish</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Dwarven</name>
			</id-00003>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">3</level>
		<name type="string">Gentalmen Jack</name>
		<notes type="string">False Identity Jack: Jacket is a traveling merchant with all the correct paper work to open doors in any field he desires\nDivergent Persona: GentalMan Jack; a professional theif with training in theives tools; Jack is a smoth talking professional acquisitions Agent!</notes>
		<pc_label_hero type="string">Hero Point</pc_label_hero>
		<perception type="number">12</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I lie about almost everything, even when there's no good reason to.</personalitytraits>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">Bardic Inspiration</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<savemod type="number">0</savemod>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<uses type="number">3</uses>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">Words of Terror</name>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<uses type="number">1</uses>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">Unsettling Visage</name>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<uses type="number">1</uses>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00004>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">4</max>
				<used type="number">4</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">2</max>
				<used type="number">1</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">preparation</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When a creature you can see makes an attack roll against you, you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on the roll. You must use this feature before knowing whether the attack hits or misses. Using this trait reveals your shapeshifting nature to any creature within 30 feet that can see you. Once you use this trait, you can't use it again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Unsettling Visage</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Unsettling Visage</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Changeling</source>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>As an action, you can transform your appearance or revert to your natural form. You can't duplicate the appearance of a creature you've never seen, and you revert to your natural form if you die.</p>
					<p>You decide what you look like, including your height, weight, facial features, the sound of your voice, coloration, hair length, sex, and any other distinguishing characteristics. You can make yourself appear as a member of another race, though none of your game statistics change. You also can't appear as a creature of a different size than you, and your basic shape stays the same; if you're bipedal, you can't use this trait to become quadrupedal, for instance. Your clothing and other equipment don't change in appearance, size, or shape to match your new form, requiring you to keep a few extra outfits on hand to make the most compelling disguise possible.</p>
					<p>Even to the most astute observers, your ruse is usually indiscernible. If you rouse suspicion, or if a wary creature suspects something is amiss, you have advantage on any Charisma (Deception) check you make to avoid detection.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Change Appearance</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<source type="string">Changeling</source>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<label type="string">Frightened</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<label type="string">Frightened</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level, you learn to infuse innocent-seeming words with an insidious magic that can inspire terror.</p>
					<p>If you speak to a humanoid alone for at least 1 minute, you can attempt to seed paranoia in its mind. At the end of the conversation, the target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw against your spell save DC or be frightened of you or another creature of your choice. The target is frightened in this way for 1 hour, until it is attacked or damaged, or until it witnesses its allies being attacked or damaged.</p>
					<p>If the target succeeds on its saving throw, the target has no hint that you tried to frighten it.</p>
					<p>Once you use this feature, you can't use it again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Words of Terror</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Words of Terror</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<specialization type="string">College of Whispers</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning at 2nd level, you can use soothing music or oration to help revitalize your wounded allies during a short rest. If you or any friendly creature who can hear your performance regains any hit points during the short rest, that creature regains 1d6 extra hit points at the end of the rest. A creature regains the extra hit points only if it spends one or more Hit Dice at the end of the short rest.</p>
					<p>The extra hit points increase when you reach certain levels in this class: 1d8 at 9th level, 1d10 at 13th level, and 1d12 at 17th level.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Song of Rest</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<label type="string">DMG: 2d6 psychic</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">4</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you join the College of Whispers at 3rd level, you gain the ability to make your weapon attacks magically toxic to a creature's mind.</p>
					<p>When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one use of your Bardic Inspiration to deal an extra 2d6 psychic damage to that target. You can do so only once per round on your turn.</p>
					<p>The psychic damage increases when you reach certain levels in this class, increasing to 3d6 at 5th level, 5d6 at 10th level, and 8d6 at 15th level.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Bardic Inspiration</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Psychic Blades</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<specialization type="string">College of Whispers</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can inspire others through stirring words or music. To do so, you use a bonus action on your turn to choose one creature other than yourself within 60 feet of you who can hear you. That creature gains one Bardic Inspiration die, a d6.</p>
					<p>Once within the next 10 minutes, the creature can roll the die and add the number rolled to one ability check, attack roll, or saving throw that it just made. The creature can wait until after it rolls the die for the ability check, attack roll, or saving throw, but before the DM says whether or not it succeeds or fails before deciding to use the Bardic Inspiration die. Once the Bardic Inspiration die is rolled, it is lost. A creature can have only one Bardic Inspiration die at a time.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Charisma modifier (a minimum of once). You regain any expended uses when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>Your Bardic Inspiration die changes when you reach certain levels in this class. The die becomes a d8 at 5th level, a d10 at 10th level, and a d12 at 15th level.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Bardic Inspiration</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bardic Inspiration</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<label type="string">Boots of Winterlands; RESIST: cold</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">Boots of winterlands</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 minute</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (two lodestones)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell repairs a single break or tear in an object you touch, such as a broken chain link, two halves of a broken key, a torn cloak, or a leaking wineskin. As long as the break or tear is no larger than 1 foot in any dimension, you mend it. leaving no trace of the former damage.</p>
					<p>This spell can physically repair a magic item or construct, but the spell can't restore magic to such an object.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mending</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell is a minor magical trick that novice spellcasters use for practice. You create one of the following magical effects within range:</p>
					<list>
						<li>You create an instantaneous, harmless sensory effect, such as a shower of sparks, a puff of wind, faint musical notes, or an odd odor.</li>
						<li>You instantaneously light or snuff out a candle, a torch, or a small campfire.</li>
						<li>You instantaneously clean or soil an object no larger than 1 cubic foot.</li>
						<li>You chill, warm, or flavor up to 1 cubic foot of nonliving material for 1 hour.</li>
						<li>You make a color, a small mark, or a symbol appear on an object or a surface for 1 hour.</li>
						<li>You create a nonmagical trinket or an illusory image that can fit in your hand and that lasts until the end of your next turn.</li>
					</list>
					<p>If you cast this spell multiple times, you can have up to three of its non-instantaneous effects active at a time, and you can dismiss such an effect as an action.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Prestidigitation</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch regains a number of hit points equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cure Wounds</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">psychic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You whisper a discordant melody that only one creature of your choice within range can hear, wracking it with terrible pain. The target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, it takes 3d6 psychic damage and must immediately use its reaction, if available, to move as far as its speed allows away from you. The creature doesn't move into obviously dangerous ground, such as a fire or a pit. On a successful save, the target takes half as much damage and doesn't have to move away. A deafened creature automatically succeeds on the save.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dissonant Whispers</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Warlock (Great Old One)</source>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any.</p>
					<p>The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Magic</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Eldritch Knight, Eldritch Invocations, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Invisible; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (an eyelash encased in gum arabic)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch becomes invisible until the spell ends. Anything the target is wearing or carrying is invisible as long as it is on the target's person. The spell ends for a target that attacks or casts a spell.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Invisibility</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid Grassland Circle, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, no sound can be created within or pass through a 20-foot-radius sphere centered on a point you choose within range. Any creature or object entirely inside the sphere is immune to thunder damage, and creatures are deafened while entirely inside it.</p>
					<p>Casting a spell that includes a verbal component is impossible there.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Silence</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid Desert Circle, Monk, Ranger</source>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<label type="string">Heroism: IMMUNE: frightened; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A willing creature you touch is imbued with bravery.</p>
					<p>Until the spell ends, the creature is immune to being frightened and gains temporary hit points equal to your spellcasting ability modifier at the start of each of its turns. When the spell ends, the target loses any remaining temporary hit points from this spell.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heroism</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Paladin</source>
			</id-00016>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">2</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: Disguise kit, forgery kit, Theive's Tools</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple weapons, hand crossbows, longswords, rapiers, shortswords</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Lute, Lyre, shawm</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Armor: Light armor</name>
			</id-00004>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Changeling (Dexterity Increase)</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.changeling@DD Wayfinder's Guide to Eberron</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">2</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">7</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">2</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">7</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Disguies Kit</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Theives' Tools</name>
				<prof type="number">2</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">7</total>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Forgery Kit</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00021>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00009_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Unsettling Visage</name>
				<source type="string">Changeling</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When a creature you can see makes an attack roll against you, you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on the roll. You must use this feature before knowing whether the attack hits or misses. Using this trait reveals your shapeshifting nature to any creature within 30 feet that can see you. Once you use this trait, you can't use it again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divergent Persona</name>
				<source type="string">Changeling</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain proficiency with one tool of your choice. Define a unique identity associated with that proficiency; establish the name, race, gender, age, and other details. While you are in the form of this persona, the related proficiency bonus is doubled for any ability check you make that uses that proficiency.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Change Appearance</name>
				<source type="string">Changeling</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>As an action, you can transform your appearance or revert to your natural form. You can't duplicate the appearance of a creature you've never seen, and you revert to your natural form if you die.</p>
					<p>You decide what you look like, including your height, weight, facial features, the sound of your voice, coloration, hair length, sex, and any other distinguishing characteristics. You can make yourself appear as a member of another race, though none of your game statistics change. You also can't appear as a creature of a different size than you, and your basic shape stays the same; if you're bipedal, you can't use this trait to become quadrupedal, for instance. Your clothing and other equipment don't change in appearance, size, or shape to match your new form, requiring you to keep a few extra outfits on hand to make the most compelling disguise possible.</p>
					<p>Even to the most astute observers, your ruse is usually indiscernible. If you rouse suspicion, or if a wary creature suspects something is amiss, you have advantage on any Charisma (Deception) check you make to avoid detection.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Changeling Instincts</name>
				<source type="string">Changeling</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain proficiency with two of the following skills of your choice: Deception, Intimidation, Insight, and Persuasion.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00004>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<handling type="number">0</handling>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Rapier (sword cane)</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00001</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<handling type="number">0</handling>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00015</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<handling type="number">0</handling>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">1</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00015</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00003>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">95</weight>
	</character>
</root>
