<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:4">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">6</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">17</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">36</age>
		<alignment type="string">NG</alignment>
		<background type="string">Adventurer</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>background.id-00001@Incarnate-5eExpansion</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">As a child, a guard gave their life to protect me from a monster. If it came to it, I'd be willing to do the same.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d8</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">7</level>
				<name type="string">Druid</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.druid@DD Xanathar's Guide to Everything Players</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">160</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">186</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">EP</name>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">183</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">3</armor>
				<disstealth type="number">0</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">16</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">50</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">100</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">300</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">96.1</load>
			<max type="number">150</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">764</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">800</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Beloved Outcast</name>
				<source type="string">Adventurer</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can always find a job, but somehow you can never find a place to sleep. People know you`re good for the work, but the fact that you are indicates that you`re probably not the sort of person they want to have around. People view adventurers in a mixed light with conflicting values. On the one hand, most adventurers are nothing more than murderous, grave-robbing vagrants. On the other hand, who else will rob that grave and murder those local bullies for you? Most common folk consider adventurers to be dangerous, unpredictable, and probably insane... But in a world filled with slavers, mad cults, dragons, walking dead, pit fiends, and extra-dimensional horrors, just about everyone could find a use for a psychotic sell-sword. Adventurers who survive and reach higher renown may find they have a small following of supporters or fans, but even they may cringe at the idea of that adventurer spending an evening in their home. Most adventurers by profession are members of an adventurers guild through which they can readily attain professional work and contacts in the field.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">6</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mighty Summoner</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of the Shepherd</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 6th level, beasts and fey that you conjure are more resilient than normal. Any beast or fey summoned or created by a spell that you cast gains the following benefits:</p>
					<list>
						<li>The creature appears with more hit points than normal: 2 extra hit points per Hit Die it has.</li>
						<li>The damage from its natural weapons is considered magical for the purpose of overcoming immunity and resistance to nonmagical attacks and damage.</li>
					</list>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Druidic</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You know Druidic, the secret language of druids. You can speak the language and use it to leave hidden messages. You and others who know this language automatically spot such a message. Others spot the message's presence with a successful DC 15 Wisdom (Perception) check but can't decipher it without magic.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Drawing on the divine essence of nature itself, you can cast spells to shape that essence to your will.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="lists.spells.druid@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Druid Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you know two cantrips of your choice from the druid spell list. You learn additional druid cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Druid table.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00038@Incarnate-5eExpansion">The Druid</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Druid table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these druid spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of druid spells that are available for you to cast, choosing from the druid spell list. When you do so, choose a number of druid spells equal to your Wisdom modifier + your druid level (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you are a 3rd-level druid, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With a Wisdom of 16, your list of prepared spells can include six spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination. If you prepare the 1st-level spell <i>cure wounds </i>, you can cast it using a 1st-level or 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can also change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of druid spells requires time spent in prayer and meditation at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Wisdom is your spellcasting ability for your druid spells, since your magic draws upon your devotion and attunement to nature. You use your Wisdom whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Wisdom modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a druid spell you cast and making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<list>
						<li><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</li>
						<li><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</li>
					</list>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast a druid spell as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag and you have the spell prepared.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a druidic focus (see &#34;Equipment&#34;) as a spellcasting focus for your druid spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Circle of the Shepherd</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Druids of the Circle of the Shepherd commune with the spirits of nature, especially the spirits of beasts and the fey, and call to those spirits for aid. These druids recognize that all living things play a role in the natural world, yet they focus on protecting animals and fey creatures that have difficulty defending themselves.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="imagewindow" recordname="reference.imagedata.img_shepherddruid_jpg@*"><b>Image: </b></link>Druid of the Circle of the Shepherd</linklist>
					<p>Shepherds, as they are known, see such creatures as their charges. They ward off monsters that threaten them, rebuke hunters who kill more prey than necessary, and prevent civilization from encroaching on rare animal habitats and on sites sacred to the fey. Many of these druids are happiest far from cities and towns, content to spend their days in the company of animals and the fey creatures of the wilds.</p>
					<p>Members of this circle become adventurers to oppose forces that threaten their charges or to seek knowledge and power that will help them safeguard their charges better. Wherever these druids go, the spirits of the wilderness are with them.</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.druid.features.speechofthewoods2@*">Speech of the Woods</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.druid.features.spirittotem2@*">Spirit Totem</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.druid.features.mightysummoner6@*">Mighty Summoner</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.druid.features.guardianspirit10@*">Guardian Spirit</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.druid.features.faithfulsummons14@*">Faithful Summons</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wild Shape</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Common Transformations</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.p98wildshape_polymorphcheatsheet@Incarnate-5eExpansion">98 Wildshape/Polymorph</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Main Description</h>
					<p>Starting at 2nd Level, you can use your action to magically assume the shape of a beast that you have seen before. You can use this feature twice. You regain expended uses when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>Your druid level determines the beasts you can transform into as shown in the Beast Shapes table. At 2nd level, for example, you can transform into any beast that has a challenge rating of 1/4 or lower that doesn't have a flying or swimming speed.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td colspan="6"><b>Beast Shapes</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td></td>
							<td><b>Max.</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Level</b></td>
							<td><b>CR</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"><b>Limitations</b></td>
							<td><b>Example</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2nd</td>
							<td>1/4</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying or swimming speed</td>
							<td>Wolf</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4th</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying speed</td>
							<td>Crocodile</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8th</td>
							<td><b>1</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td>Giant eagle</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>You can stay in a beast shape for a number of hours equal to half your druid level (rounded down). You then revert to your normal form unless you expend another use of this feature. You can revert to your normal form earlier by using a bonus action on your turn. You automatically revert if you fall unconscious, drop to 9 hit points, or die.</p>
					<p>While you are transformed the following rules apply:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Your game statistics are replaced by the statistics of the beast, but you retain your alignment, personality, and Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma scores. You also retain all of your skill and saving throw proficiencies, in addition to gaining those of the creature. If the creature has the same proficiency as you and the bonus in its stat block is higher than yours, use the creature's bonus instead of yours. If the creature has any legendary or lair actions, you can't use them.</li>
						<li>When you transform, you assume the beast's hit points and Hit Dice. When you revert to your normal form, you return to the number of hit points you had before you transformed. However if you revert as a result of dropping to 0 hit points, any excess damage carries over to your normal form. For example, if you take 10 damage in animal form and only have 1 hit point left, you revert and take 9 damage. As long as the excess damage doesn't reduce your normal form to 0 hit points, you aren't knocked unconscious.</li>
						<li>You can't cast spells, and your ability to speak or take any action that requires hands is limited to the capabilities f your beast form. Transforming doesn't break your concentration on a spell you've already cast, however, or prevent you from taking actions that are part of a spell, such as <i>call lightning </i>, that you've already cast.</li>
						<li>You retain the benefit of any features from your class, race, or other source and can use them if the new form is physically capable of doing so. However, you can't use any of your special senses, such as darkvision, unless your new form also has that sense.</li>
						<li>You choose whether your equipment falls to the ground in your space, merges into your new form or is worn by it. Worn equipment functions as normal, but the GM decides if it is practical for the new form to ear a piece of equipment based on the creature's shape and size. Your equipment doesn't change size or shape to match the new form and any equipment that the new form can't wear must either fall to the ground or merge with it. Equipment that merges with the form has no effect until you leave the form.</li>
					</list>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spirit Totem</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of the Shepherd</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can call forth nature spirits to influence the world around you. As a bonus action, you can magically summon an incorporeal spirit to a point you can see within 60 feet of you. The spirit creates an aura in a 30-foot radius around that point. It counts as neither a creature nor an object, though it has the spectral appearance of the creature it represents.</p>
					<p>As a bonus action, you can move the spirit up to 60 feet to a point you can see.</p>
					<p>The spirit persists for 1 minute or until you're incapacitated. Once you use this feature, you can't use it again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>The effect of the spirit's aura depends on the type of spirit you summon from the options below.</p>
					<p><b><i>Bear Spirit. </i></b>The bear spirit grants you and your allies its might and endurance. Each creature of your choice in the aura when the spirit appears gains temporary hit points equal to 5 + your druid level. In addition, you and your allies gain advantage on Strength checks and Strength saving throws while in the aura.</p>
					<p><b><i>Hawk Spirit. </i></b>The hawk spirit is a consummate hunter, aiding you and your allies with its keen sight. When a creature makes an attack roll against a target in the spirit's aura, you can use your reaction to grant advantage to that attack roll. In addition, you and your allies have advantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks while in the aura.</p>
					<p><b><i>Unicorn Spirit. </i></b>The unicorn spirit lends its protection to those nearby. You and your allies gain advantage on all ability checks made to detect creatures in the spirit's aura. In addition, if you cast a spell using a spell slot that restores hit points to any creature inside or outside the aura, each creature of your choice in the aura also regains hit points equal to your druid level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Speech of the Woods</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of the Shepherd</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you gain the ability to converse with beasts and many fey.</p>
					<p>You learn to speak, read, and write Sylvan. In addition, beasts can understand your speech, and you gain the ability to decipher their noises and motions. Most beasts lack the intelligence to convey or understand sophisticated concepts, but a friendly beast could relay what it has seen or heard in the recent past. This ability doesn't grant you friendship with beasts, though you can combine this ability with gifts to curry favor with them as you would with any nonplayer character.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I cannot maintain meaningful relationships.\nList of people hated:\nTalaal Al-ajid</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Gender Fluid</gender>
		<height type="string">5'2&#34;</height>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">49</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">This is what I was made to do.\nI'm doing what I do so others can benefit.</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">3</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1 bludgeoning</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This wooden training sword is great for the standard farmer who wants to practice with a sword. It lets you practice your swings without cutting off your hand or foot. For those who rarely if ever hit yourself... you will want a better weapon.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wooden Training Sword</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Improvised</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">priceless... but only to you</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="table" recordname="tables.id-01878@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Random Trophy</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Trophy</name>
				<rarity type="string">Rare</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cloak</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shovel</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tiny leather pouch is perfect for keeping your coins close at hand. Just watch out for someone trying to cut it off of your belt.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Coin Pouch - Small</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Using a crowbar grants advantage to Strength checks where the crowbar's leverage can be applied.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Crowbar</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">910 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 slashing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.celestialslayer@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Celestial Slayer</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</p>
					<p>When you hit an Celestial with it, the creature takes an extra 2d6 damage of the weapon's type and must succeed on a DC 15 Strength saving throw or fall prone. For the purpose of this weapon, &#34;Celestial&#34; refers to any creature with the Celestial type.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shortsword of Celestial Slaying</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Shortsword</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">For when you want something longer than a dagger but shorter than a longsword the shortsword is for you.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Finesse light</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 slashing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Scimitar</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Scimitar</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A sharp scimitar.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">7</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">9</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tin box contains a cup and simple cutlery. The box clamps together, and one side can be used as a cooking pan and the other as a plate or shallow bowl.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mess Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Equipment Kits</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<ac type="number">11</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The breastplate and shoulder protectors of this armor are made of leather that has been stiffened by being boiled in oil. The rest of the armor is made of softer and more flexible materials.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">Yes</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Leather Armor</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Leather Armor</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Some well-crafted leather armor.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">common</rarity>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Light Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A druidic focus might be a sprig of mistletoe or holly, a wand or scepter made of yew or another special wood, a staff drawn whole out of a living tree, or a totem object incorporating feathers, fur, bones, and teeth from sacred animals. A druid can use such an object as a spellcasting focus.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Yew Wand</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Wand</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A magical wand.</nonidentified>
				<subtype type="string">Druidic Focus</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">heartstone</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00021>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">900 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tiny object looks like a feather. Different types of feather tokens exist, each with a different single-- use effect. The GM chooses the kind of token or determines it randomly.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>d100</td>
							<td>Feather Token</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>01-20</td>
							<td>Anchor</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>51-65</td>
							<td>Swan boat</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>21-35</td>
							<td>Bird</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>66-90</td>
							<td>Tree</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>36-50</td>
							<td>Fan</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>91-00</td>
							<td>Whip</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p><b>Anchor </b>. You can use an action to touch the token to a boat or ship. For the next 24 hours, the vessel can't be moved by any means. Touching the token to the vessel again ends the effect. When the effect ends, the token disappears.</p>
					<p><b>Bird </b>. You can use an action to toss the token 5 feet into the air. The token disappears and an enormous, multicolored bird takes its place. The bird has the statistics of a roc, but it obeys your simple commands and can't attack. It can carry up to 500 pounds while flying at its maximum speed (16 miles an hour for a maximum of 144 miles per day, with a one--hour rest for every 3 hours of flying), or 1,000 pounds at half that speed. The bird disappears after flying its maximum distance for a day or if it drops to 0 hit points. You can dismiss the bird as an action.</p>
					<p><b>Fan </b>. If you are on a boat or ship, you can use an action to toss the token up to 10 feet in the air. The token disappears, and a giant flapping fan takes its place. The fan floats and creates a wind strong enough to fill the sails of one ship, increasing its speed by 5 miles per hour for 8 hours. You can dismiss the fan as an action.</p>
					<p><b>Swan Boat </b>. You can use an action to touch the token to a body of water at least 60 feet in diameter. The token disappears, and a 50--foot--long, 20--foot-- wide boat shaped like a swan takes its place. The boat is self--propelled and moves across water at a speed of 6 miles per hour. You can use an action while on the boat to command it to move or to turn up to 90 degrees. The boat can carry up to thirty--two Medium or smaller creatures. A Large creature counts as four Medium creatures, while a Huge creature counts as nine. The boat remains for 24 hours and then disappears. You can dismiss the boat as an action.</p>
					<p><b>Tree </b>. You must be outdoors to use this token. You can use an action to touch it to an unoccupied space on the ground. The token disappears, and in its place a nonmagical oak tree springs into existence. The tree is 60 feet tall and has a 5--foot--diameter trunk, and its branches at the top spread out in a 20--foot radius.</p>
					<p><b>Whip </b>. You can use an action to throw the token to a point within 10 feet of you. The token disappears, and a floating whip takes its place. You can then use a bonus action to make a melee spell attack against a creature within 10 feet of the whip, with an attack bonus of +9. On a hit, the target takes 1d6 + 5 force damage. As a bonus action on your turn, you can direct the whip to fly up to 20 feet and repeat the attack against a creature within 10 feet of it. The whip disappears after 1 hour, when you use an action to dismiss it, or when you are incapacitated or die.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Feather Token - Tree</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Feather</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">This tiny object looks like a feather.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">rare</rarity>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">0.2</weight>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">150 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Linked Spell</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.speakwithplants@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Speak with Plants</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>A spell scroll bears the words of a single spell, written in a mystical cipher. If the spell is on your class's spell list, you can read the scroll and cast its spell without providing any material components.</p>
					<p>Otherwise, the scroll is unintelligible. Casting the spell by reading the scroll requires the spell's normal casting time. Once the spell is cast, the words on the scroll fade, and it crumbles to dust. If the casting is interrupted, the scroll is not lost.</p>
					<p>If the spell is on your class's spell list but of a higher level than you can normally cast, you must make an ability check using your spellcasting ability to determine whether you cast it successfully. The DC equals 10 + the spell's level. On a failed check, the spell disappears from the scroll with no other effect.</p>
					<p>The level of the spell on the scroll determines the spell's saving throw DC and attack bonus, as well as the scroll's rarity, as shown in the Spell Scroll table.</p>
					<p>Spell Scroll</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Spell Level</td>
							<td>Rarity</td>
							<td>Save DC</td>
							<td>Attack Bonus</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>3rd</td>
							<td>Uncommon</td>
							<td>15</td>
							<td>+7</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>A wizard spell on a spell scroll can be copied just as spells in spellbooks can be copied. When a spell is copied from a spell scroll, the copier must succeed on an Intelligence (Arcana) check with a DC equal to 10 + the spell's level. If the check succeeds, the spell is successfully copied. Whether the check succeeds or fails, the spell scroll is destroyed.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Scroll of Speak with Plants</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Scroll</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Scroll</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Scroll</type>
				<weight type="number">0.3</weight>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<ac type="number">12</ac>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">501 - 5,000 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>The most basic form of magic armor is a superb product of physical and magical craft. You have a +1 bonus to AC while wearing this armor.</p>
					<p>A suit of +1 armor never rusts or deteriorates, and it magically resizes to fit its wearer.</p>
					<p><b>Studded Leather Notes</b></p>
					<p>Made from supple and thin materials, light armor favors agile adventurers since it offers some protection without sacrificing mobility. If you wear light armor, you add your Dexterity modifier to the base number from your armor type to determine your Armor Class.</p>
					<p>Made from tough but flexible leather, studded leather is reinforced with close-set rivets or spikes.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">Yes</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Studded Leather Armor, +1</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Fine Studded Leather Armor</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">This suit of armor is finely wrought</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Magic</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Rare</rarity>
				<spells>
					<id-00001>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class></class>
							<recordname></recordname>
						</link>
						<name type="string">Armor, +1</name>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class></class>
							<recordname></recordname>
						</link>
						<name type="string">Studded Leather</name>
					</id-00002>
				</spells>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Studded Leather</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">13</weight>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">128 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You regain 4d4 + 4 hit points when you drink this potion. The potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Potion of Greater Healing</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Potion</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A vial of red liquid that shimmers when agitated.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Magic</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<spells>
					<id-00001>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class></class>
							<recordname></recordname>
						</link>
						<name type="string">Potion of Greater Healing</name>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class></class>
							<recordname></recordname>
						</link>
						<name type="string">Potion</name>
					</id-00002>
				</spells>
				<type type="string">Potion</type>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00025>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">902 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d4 piercing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Sound</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00010@Incarnate-Syrinscape"><b>Syrinscape </b></link>: Dagger</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon.</p>
					<p>You can use an action to cause thick, black poison to coat the blade. The poison remains for 1 minute or until an attack using this weapon hits a creature.</p>
					<p>That creature must succeed on a DC 15 Constitution saving throw or take 2d10 poison damage and become poisoned for 1 minute. The dagger can't be used this way again until the next dawn.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dagger of Venom</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Dagger</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A finely crafted dagger</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<rarity type="string">rare</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">(dagger)</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00025>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Elvish</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Goblin</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Draconic</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<name type="string">Sylvan</name>
			</id-00005>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">7</level>
		<name type="string">Herbal</name>
		<notes type="string">Own a Pseudodragon with \n+10 to hp\nSame as wofie</notes>
		<perception type="number">13</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I will live to see the infernal houses fall. Demons have no place in our world.\nTraveling with Vok as lead to a hate for dragons.\nWith the death of desire and the training as a druid gives Herbal a bruning hate for the undead.</personalitytraits>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<atkstat type="string">wisdom</atkstat>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<savestat type="string">wisdom</savestat>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Class</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">Wilds shape</name>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<name type="string">Item</name>
			</id-00005>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">4</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">1</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">standard</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">5</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">druid</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">druid</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can call forth nature spirits to influence the world around you. As a bonus action, you can magically summon an incorporeal spirit to a point you can see within 60 feet of you. The spirit creates an aura in a 30-foot radius around that point. It counts as neither a creature nor an object, though it has the spectral appearance of the creature it represents.</p>
					<p>As a bonus action, you can move the spirit up to 60 feet to a point you can see.</p>
					<p>The spirit persists for 1 minute or until you're incapacitated. Once you use this feature, you can't use it again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>The effect of the spirit's aura depends on the type of spirit you summon from the options below.</p>
					<p><b><i>Bear Spirit. </i></b>The bear spirit grants you and your allies its might and endurance. Each creature of your choice in the aura when the spirit appears gains temporary hit points equal to 5 + your druid level. In addition, you and your allies gain advantage on Strength checks and Strength saving throws while in the aura.</p>
					<p><b><i>Hawk Spirit. </i></b>The hawk spirit is a consummate hunter, aiding you and your allies with its keen sight. When a creature makes an attack roll against a target in the spirit's aura, you can use your reaction to grant advantage to that attack roll. In addition, you and your allies have advantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks while in the aura.</p>
					<p><b><i>Unicorn Spirit. </i></b>The unicorn spirit lends its protection to those nearby. You and your allies gain advantage on all ability checks made to detect creatures in the spirit's aura. In addition, if you cast a spell using a spell slot that restores hit points to any creature inside or outside the aura, each creature of your choice in the aura also regains hit points equal to your druid level.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spirit Totem</name>
				<prepared type="number">2</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of the Shepherd</specialization>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">ability</savedcbase>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savedcstat type="string">wisdom</savedcstat>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">necrotic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d12,d12</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">necrotic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You point at one creature you can see within range, and the sound of a dolorous bell fills the air around it for a moment. The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or take 1d8 necrotic damage. If the target is missing any of its hit points, it instead takes 1d12 necrotic damage.</p>
					<p>The spell's damage increases by one die when you reach 5th level (2d8 or 2d12), 11th level (3d8 or 3d12), and 17th level (4d8 or 4d12).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Toll the Dead</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Necromancy</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You choose a portion of dirt or stone that you can see within range and that fits within a 5-foot cube. You manipulate it in one of the following ways:</p>
					<list>
						<li>If you target an area of loose earth, you can instantaneously excavate it, move it along the ground, and deposit it up to 5 feet away. This movement doesn't involve enough force to cause damage.</li>
						<li>You cause shapes, colors, or both to appear on the dirt or stone, spelling out words, creating images, or shaping patterns. The changes last for 1 hour.</li>
						<li>If the dirt or stone you target is on the ground, you cause it to become difficult terrain. Alternatively, you can cause the ground to become normal terrain if it is already difficult terrain. This change lasts for 1 hour.</li>
					</list>
					<p>If you cast this spell multiple times, you can have no more than two of its non-instantaneous effects active at a time, and you can dismiss such an effect as an action.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous or 1 hour (see below)</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mold Earth</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">ability</atkbase>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atkstat type="string">wisdom</atkstat>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A flickering flame appears in your hand. The flame remains there for the duration and harms neither you nor your equipment. The flame sheds bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet. The spell ends if you dismiss it as an action or if you cast it again. You can also attack with the flame, although doing so ends the spell. When you cast this spell, or as an action on a later turn, you can hurl the flame at a creature within 30 feet of you. Make a ranged spell attack. On a hit, the target takes 1d8 fire damage. This spell's damage increases by 1d8 when you reach 5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Produce Flame</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4,d4</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature of your choice that you can see within range regains hit points equal to 1d4 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d4 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Healing Word</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain the ability to comprehend and verbally communicate with beasts for the duration. The knowledge and awareness of many beasts is limited by their intelligence, but at minimum, beasts can give you information about nearby locations and monsters, including whatever they can perceive or have perceived within the past day. You might be able to persuade a beast to perform a small favor for you, at the GM's discretion.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Speak with Animals</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">ability</atkbase>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atkstat type="string">dexterity</atkstat>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">ability</savedcbase>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savedcstat type="string">wisdom</savedcstat>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d10</dice>
								<type type="string">piercing,magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">cold,magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">S, M (a drop of water or a piece of ice)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create a shard of ice and fling it at one creature within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes 1d10 piercing damage. Hit or miss, the shard then explodes. The target and each creature within 5 feet of it must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw or take 2d6 cold damage.</p>
					<p><b><i>At Higher Levels. </i></b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the cold damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ice Knife</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Faerie Fire; GRANTADVATK; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Each object in a 20-foot cube within range is outlined in blue, green, or violet light (your choice). Any creature in the area when the spell is cast is also outlined in light if it fails a Dexterity saving throw. For the duration, objects and affected creatures shed dim light in a 10-foot radius. Any attack roll against an affected creature or object has advantage if the attacker can see it, and the affected creature or object can't benefit from being invisible.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Faerie Fire</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
					<id-00003>
						<apply type="string">action</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Celestial Slayer; IFT:TYPE(celestial);DMG:2d6</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">fixed</savedcbase>
						<savedcmod type="number">15</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00004>
					<id-00005>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">day</durunit>
						<label type="string">prone</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00005>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="itemtemplate" recordname="itemtemplate.id-00008@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Celestial Slayer</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Item</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Celestial Slayer</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Item - Action Code</source>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">ability</savedcbase>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savedcstat type="string">wisdom</savedcstat>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Heat Metal; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<label type="string">DMGO: 2d8 fire</label>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a piece of iron and a flame)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose a manufactured metal object, such as a metal weapon or a suit of heavy or medium metal armor, that you can see within range. You cause the object to glow red-hot. Any creature in physical contact with the object takes 2d8 fire damage when you cast the spell. Until the spell ends, you can use a bonus action on each of your subsequent turns to cause this damage again. If a creature is holding or wearing the object and takes the damage from it, the creature must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or drop the object if it can. If it doesn't drop the object, it has disadvantage on attack rolls and ability checks until the start of your next turn. At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heat Metal</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Whispering to the spirits of nature, you create one of the following effects within range:</p>
					<list>
						<li>You create a tiny, harmless sensory effect that predicts what the weather will be at your location for the next 24 hours. The effect might manifest as a golden orb for clear skies, a cloud for rain, falling snowflakes for snow, and so on. This effect persists for 1 round.</li>
						<li>You instantly make a flower blossom, a seed pod open, or a leaf bud bloom.</li>
						<li>You create an instantaneous, harmless sensory effect, such as falling leaves, a puff of wind, the sound of a small animal, or the faint odor of skunk. The effect must fit in a 5-foot cube.</li>
						<li>You instantly light or snuff out a candle, a torch, or a small campfire.</li>
					</list>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Druidcraft</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Healing Spirit (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<label type="string">REGEN: 2d6</label>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You call forth a nature spirit to soothe the wounded. The intangible spirit appears in a space that is a 5-foot cube you can see within range. The spirit looks like a transparent beast or fey (your choice).</p>
					<p>Until the spell ends, whenever you or a creature you can see moves into the spirit's space for the first time on a turn or starts its turn there, you can cause the spirit to restore 1d6 hit points to that creature (no action required). The spirit can't heal constructs or undead.</p>
					<p>As a bonus action on your turn, you can move the spirit up to 30 feet to a space you can see.</p>
					<p><b><i>At Higher Levels. </i></b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Healing Spirit</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10,d10</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">STR: [-2STR]; STR: 4; DEX: [-2DEX]; DEX: 2; CON: [-2CON]; CON: 3; AC: -2</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">5</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">fixed</savedcbase>
						<savedcmod type="number">12</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00005>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">4</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00005>
					<id-00006>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">slashing</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00006>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.axebeak@Incarnate-5eBattles">Axe Beak</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wilds shape</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Transformation - Crocodile</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">DMG: 1d6 force; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">10</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A nature spirit answers your call and transforms you into a powerful guardian. The transformation lasts until the spell ends. You choose one of the following forms to assume: Primal Beast or Great Tree.</p>
					<p><b><i>Primal Beast. </i></b>Bestial fur covers your body, your facial features become feral, and you gain the following benefits:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Your walking speed increases by 10 feet.</li>
						<li>You gain darkvision with a range of 120 feet.</li>
						<li>You make Strength-based attack rolls with advantage.</li>
						<li>Your melee weapon attacks deal an extra 1d6 force damage on a hit.</li>
					</list>
					<p><b><i>Great Tree. </i></b>Your skin appears barky, leaves sprout from your hair, and you gain the following benefits:</p>
					<list>
						<li>You gain 10 temporary hit points.</li>
						<li>You make Constitution saving throws with advantage.</li>
						<li>You make Dexterity-and Wisdom-based attack rolls with advantage.</li>
						<li>While you are on the ground, the ground within 15 feet of you is difficult terrain for your enemies.</li>
					</list>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Guardian of Nature</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">6</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8,d8</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">STR: [-2STR]; STR: 4; DEX: [-2DEX]; DEX: 0; CON: [-2CON]; CON: 4;</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">slashing</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">5</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00005>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">3</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00005>
					<id-00006>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">piercing</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00006>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.wolf@Incarnate-5eBattles">Wolf</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wilds shape</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Transformation - Green Bear</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose one creature, object, or magical effect within range. Any spell of 3rd level or lower on the target ends. For each spell of 4th level or higher on the target, make an ability check using your spellcasting ability. The DC equals 10 + the spell's level. On a successful check, the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher, you automatically end the effects of a spell on the target if the spell's level is equal to or less than the level of the spell slot you used.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dispel Magic</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<group type="string">Wilds shape</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">Uses of Wild Shape</name>
				<prepared type="number">2</prepared>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10,d10</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<label type="string">STR: [-2STR]; STR: 6; DEX: [-2DEX]; DEX: 3; CON: [-2CON]; CON: 3; AC: -2</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">fixed</savedcbase>
						<savedcmod type="number">14</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
					<id-00005>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">6</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">5</order>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00005>
					<id-00006>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">6</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00006>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<group type="string">Wilds shape</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">Transformation - Warhorse</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4,d4,d4</dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Item Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00392@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Greater Potion of Healing</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Greater Potion of Healing</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Item - Action Code</source>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Conjure Animals; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You summon fey spirits that take the form of beasts and appear in unoccupied spaces that you can see within range. Choose one of the following options for what appears:</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="table" recordname="tables.id-02413@Incarnate-5eExpansion">One beast of challenge rating 2 or lower</link>
						<link class="table" recordname="tables.id-02414@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Two beasts of challenge rating 1 or lower</link>
						<link class="table" recordname="tables.id-02415@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Four beasts of challenge rating 1/2 or lower</link>
						<link class="table" recordname="tables.id-02416@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Eight beasts of challenge rating 1/4 or lower</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>Each beast is also considered fey, and it disappears when it drops to 0 hit points or when the spell ends. The summoned creatures are friendly to you and your companions. Roll initiative for the summoned creatures as a group, which has its own turns. They obey any verbal commands that you issue to them (no action required by you). If you don't issue any commands to them, they defend themselves from hostile creatures, but otherwise take no actions. The GM has the creatures' statistics.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using certain higher-level spell slots, you choose one of the summoning options above, and more creatures appear: twice as many with a 5th-level slot, three times as many with a 7th-level slot, and four times as many with a 9th-level slot.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Conjure Animals</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">ability</savedcbase>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savedcstat type="string">wisdom</savedcstat>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10</dice>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Moonbeam; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10,d10</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00004>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (several seeds of any moonseed plant and a piece of opalescent feldspar)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A silvery beam of pale light shines down in a 5-foot- radius, 40-foot-high cylinder centered on a point within range. Until the spell ends, dim light fills the cylinder. When a creature enters the spell's area for the first time on a turn or starts its turn there, it is engulfed in ghostly flames that cause searing pain, and it must make a Constitution saving throw. It takes 2d10 radiant damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. A shapechanger makes its saving throw with disadvantage. If it fails, it also instantly reverts to its original form and can't assume a different form until it leaves the spell's light. On each of your turns after you cast this spell, you can use an action to move the beam 60 feet in any direction.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d10 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Moonbeam</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00023>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<label type="string">DMGTYPE: magic</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 6th level, beasts and fey that you conjure are more resilient than normal. Any beast or fey summoned or created by a spell that you cast gains the following benefits:</p>
					<list>
						<li>The creature appears with more hit points than normal: 2 extra hit points per Hit Die it has.</li>
						<li>The damage from its natural weapons is considered magical for the purpose of overcoming immunity and resistance to nonmagical attacks and damage.</li>
					</list>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mighty Summoner</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of the Shepherd</specialization>
			</id-00023>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">3</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: Thieves' Tools</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Clubs, daggers, darts, javelins, maces, quarterstaffs, scimitars, sickles, slings, spears</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Tool: Herbalism kit</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Armor: light armor, medium armor, shields (druids will not wear armor or use shields made of metal)</name>
			</id-00004>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Half-Elf-Variant (Studied)</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.half_elf_variant@D&#38;D Sword Coast Adventurer's Guide - Player's Guide</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<senses type="string">Darkvision 60</senses>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00009_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fey Ancestry</name>
				<source type="string">Half-Elf-Variant</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against being charmed, and magic can't put you to sleep.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cantrip</name>
				<source type="string">Studied</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You know one cantrip of your choice from the wizard spell list. Intelligence is your spellcasting ability for it.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00002>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
						<dice type="dice"></dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
						<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Wooden Training Sword</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00001</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">slashing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Scimitar</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00008</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attackbonus type="number">1</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
						<type type="string">slashing,magic</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Shortsword of Celestial Slaying</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse light</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00007</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<attackbonus type="number">1</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger of Venom</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00025</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<attackbonus type="number">1</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">1</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger of Venom</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00025</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00005>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">105 Lbs</weight>
	</character>
</root>
