<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:4">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">5</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">15</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">4</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">-1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">8</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">11</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<age type="string">24</age>
		<alignment type="string">CN</alignment>
		<background type="string">Guild Artisan</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>reference.backgrounddata.guildartisan@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">Something important was taken from me, and I aim to steal it back.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d8</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<name type="string">Bard</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.bard@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">1</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d8</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<name type="string">Warlock</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.warlock@DD Xanathar's Guide to Everything Players</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00002>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">15</amount>
				<name type="string">gp</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">1</armor>
				<disstealth type="number">0</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">13</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<deity type="string">A voice offered power, so why not.</deity>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">40</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">80</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">240</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">62.05</load>
			<max type="number">120</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">0</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">0</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have learned to untangle and reshape the fabric of reality in harmony with your wishes and music. Your spells are part of your vast repertoire, magic that you can tune to different situations. See chapter 10 for the general rules of spellcasting and chapter 11 for the bard spell list.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="reference.spelllists.bard@DD PHB Deluxe">Bard Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>You know two cantrips of your choice from the bard spell list. You learn additional bard cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Bard table.</p>
					<p><b>Spell Slots</b></p>
					<p>The Bard table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You must finish a long rest to regain any expended spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you know the 1st-level spell cure wounds and have a 1st-level and a 2nd-level spell slot available, you can cast cure wounds using either slot.</p>
					<p><b>Spells Known of 1st Level and Higher</b></p>
					<p>You know four 1st-level spells of your choice from the bard spell list.</p>
					<p>The Spells Known column of the Bard table shows when you learn more bard spells of your choice. Each of these spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots, as shown on the table. For instance, when you reach 3rd level in this class, you can learn one new spell of 1st or 2nd level.</p>
					<p>Additionally, when you gain a level in this class, you can choose one of the spells you know and replace it with another spell from the bard spell list, which must be of a level for which you have spell slots, as shown on the table.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Charisma is your spellcasting ability for your bard spells, since the power of your magic comes from the heart and soul you pour into the performance of your music or oration. You use your Charisma whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Charisma modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a bard spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p><b>Spell Save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spell Attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast any bard spell you know as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag. To cast a spell as a ritual, you must add 10 minutes to the spell's casting time, as normal.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a musical instrument as the material component for a bard spell, as described in chapter 10.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bardic Inspiration</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can inspire others through stirring words or music. To do so, you use a bonus action on your turn to choose one creature other than yourself within 60 feet of you who can hear you. That creature gains one Bardic Inspiration die, a d6.</p>
					<p>Once within the next 10 minutes, the creature can roll the die and add the number rolled to one ability check, attack roll, or saving throw that it just made. The creature can wait until after it rolls the die for the ability check, attack roll, or saving throw, but before the DM says whether or not it succeeds or fails before deciding to use the Bardic Inspiration die. Once the Bardic Inspiration die is rolled, it is lost. A creature can have only one Bardic Inspiration die at a time.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Charisma modifier (a minimum of once). You regain any expended uses when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>Your Bardic Inspiration die changes when you reach certain levels in this class. The die becomes a d8 at 5th level, a d10 at 10th level, and a d12 at 15th level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">The Celestial</name>
				<source type="string">Warlock</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your patron is a powerful being of the Upper Planes. You have bound yourself to an ancient empyrean, solar, ki-rin, unicorn, or other entity that resides in the planes of everlasting bliss. Your pact with that being allows you to experience the barest touch of the holy light that illuminates the multiverse.</p>
					<p>Being connected to such power can cause changes in your behavior and beliefs. You might find yourself driven to annihilate the undead, to defeat fiends, and to protect the innocent. At times, your heart might also be filled with a longing for the celestial realm of your patron, and a desire to wander that paradise for the rest of your days. But you know that your mission is among mortals for now, and that your pact binds you to bring light to the dark places of the world.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="imagewindow" recordname="reference.imagedata.img_celestialwarlock_jpg@*"><b>Image: </b></link>Warlock of the Celestial</linklist>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.warlock.features.expandedspelllist_celestial_1@*">Expanded Spell List (Celestial)</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.warlock.features.bonuscantrips1@*">Bonus Cantrips</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.warlock.features.healinglight1@*">Healing Light</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.warlock.features.radiantsoul6@*">Radiant Soul</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.warlock.features.celestialresilience10@*">Celestial Resilience</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.warlock.features.searingvengeance14@*">Searing Vengeance</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Pact Magic</name>
				<source type="string">Warlock</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your arcane research and the magic bestowed on you by your patron have given you facility with spells. See chapter 10 for the general rules of spellcasting and chapter 11 for the warlock spell list.</p>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>You know two cantrips of your choice from the warlock spell list. You learn additional warlock cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Warlock table.</p>
					<p><b>Spell Slots</b></p>
					<p>The Warlock table shows how many spell slots you have. The table also shows what the level of those slots is; all of your spell slots are the same level. To cast one of your warlock spells of 1st level or higher, you must expend a spell slot. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>For example, when you are 5th level, you have two 3rd-level spell slots. To cast the 1st-level spell <i>thunderwave </i>, you must spend one of those slots, and you cast it as a 3rd-level spell.</p>
					<p><b>Spells Known of 1st Level and Higher</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you know two 1st-level spells of your choice from the warlock spell list.</p>
					<p>The Spells Known column of the Warlock table shows when you learn more warlock spells of your choice of 1st level and higher. A spell you choose must be of a level no higher than what's shown in the table's Slot Level column for your level. When you reach 6th level, for example, you learn a new warlock spell, which can be 1st, 2nd, or 3rd level.</p>
					<p>Additionally, when you gain a level in this class, you can choose one of the warlock spells you know and replace it with another spell from the warlock spell list, which also must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Charisma is your spellcasting ability for your warlock spells, so you use your Charisma whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Charisma modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a warlock spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use an arcane focus (found in chapter 5) as a spellcasting focus for your warlock spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Healing Light</name>
				<source type="string">Warlock</source>
				<specialization type="string">The Celestial</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 1st level, you gain the ability to channel celestial energy to heal wounds. You have a pool of d6s that you spend to fuel this healing. The number of dice in the pool equals 1 + your warlock level.</p>
					<p>As a bonus action, you can heal one creature you can see within 60 feet of you, spending dice from the pool. The maximum number of dice you can spend at once equals your Charisma modifier (minimum of one die).</p>
					<p>Roll the dice you spend, add them together, and restore a number of hit points equal to the total.</p>
					<p>Your pool regains all expended dice when you finish a long rest.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bonus Cantrips</name>
				<source type="string">Warlock</source>
				<specialization type="string">The Celestial</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 1st level, you learn the <i>light </i>and <i>sacred flame </i>cantrips. They count as warlock cantrips for you, but they don't count against your number of cantrips known.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.light@*"><b>Cantrip: </b></link>Light</linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.sacredflame@*"><b>Cantrip: </b></link>Sacred Flame
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Expanded Spell List (Celestial)</name>
				<source type="string">Warlock</source>
				<specialization type="string">The Celestial</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>The Celestial lets you choose from an expanded list of spells when you learn a warlock spell. The following spells are added to the warlock spell list for you.</p>
					<h>Celestial Expanded Spells</h>
					<p><b>Spell Level - Spells</b></p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.curewounds@*"><b>1st Level: </b></link>Cure Wounds</linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.guidingbolt@*"><b>1st Level: </b></link>Guiding Bolt
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.flamingsphere@*"><b>2nd Level: </b></link>Flaming Sphere
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.lesserrestoration@*"><b>2nd Level: </b></link>Lesser Restoration
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.daylight@*"><b>3rd Level: </b></link>Daylight
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.revivify@*"><b>3rd Level: </b></link>Revivify
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.guardianoffaith@*"><b>4th Level: </b></link>Guardian of Faith
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.walloffire@*"><b>4th Level: </b></link>Wall of Fire
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.flamestrike@*"><b>5th Level: </b></link>Flame Strike
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.greaterrestoration@*"><b>5th Level: </b></link>Greater Restoration
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Song of Rest</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning at 2nd level, you can use soothing music or oration to help revitalize your wounded allies during a short rest. If you or any friendly creature who can hear your performance regains any hit points during the short rest, that creature regains 1d6 extra hit points at the end of the rest. A creature regains the extra hit points only if it spends one or more Hit Dice at the end of the short rest.</p>
					<p>The extra hit points increase when you reach certain levels in this class: 1d8 at 9th level, 1d10 at 13th level, and 1d12 at 17th level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Jack of All Trades</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can add half your proficiency bonus, rounded down, to any ability check you make that doesn't already include that bonus.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Guild Membership</name>
				<source type="string">Guild Artisan</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>As an established and respected member of a guild, you can rely on certain benefits that membership provides. Your fellow guild members will provide you with lodging and food if necessary, and pay for your funeral if needed. In some cities and towns, a guildhall offers a central place to meet other members of your profession, which can be a good place to meet potential patrons, allies, or hirelings.</p>
					<p>Guilds often wield tremendous political power. If you are accused of a crime, your guild w ill support you if a good case can be made for your innocence or the crime is justifiable. You can also gain access to powerful political figures through the guild, if you are a member in good standing. Such connections might require the donation of money or magic items to the guild's coffers. You must pay dues of 5 gp per month to the guild. If you miss payments, you must make up back dues to remain in the guild's good graces.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00010>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I'm too greedy for my own good. I can't resist taking a risk if there's money involved.\nYou spend excessively on creature comforts\n.I'm never satisfied with what I have- I always want more.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">5' 6</height>
		<hp>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">24</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Excitement. Can you steal the sleeping giant's pouch? Of course you can!\nFreedom. Everyone should be free to pursue his or her own livelihood.\nPeople. I'm committed to the people I care about, not to ideals.</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">2</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Belt</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rapier</name>
				<properties type="string">Finesse</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">7</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Costume</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">5</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This pouch of cosmetics, hair dye, and small props lets you create disguises that change your physical appearance. Proficiency with this kit lets you add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make to create a visual disguise.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Disguise Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Kits / Sets</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">5</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For 1 hour, a candle sheds bright light in a 5-foot radius and dim light for an additional 5 feet.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Candle</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<ac type="number">11</ac>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Made from supple and thin materials, light armor favors agile adventurers since it offers some protection without sacrificing mobility. If you wear light armor, you add your Dexterity modifier to the base number from your armor type to determine your Armor Class.</p>
					<p>The breastplate and shoulder protectors of this armor are made of leather that has been stiffened by being boiled in oil. The rest of the armor is made of softer and more flexible materials.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">Yes</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Leather</name>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Light Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d4 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Belt</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>These special tools include the items needed to pursue a craft or trade. The table shows examples of the most common types of tools, each providing items related to a single craft. Proficiency with a set of artisan's tools lets you add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make using the tools in your craft. Each type of artisan's tools requires a separate proficiency.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Leatherworker's Tools</name>
				<subtype type="string">Artisan's Tools</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Traveler's</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A cloth or leather pouch can hold up to 20 sling bullets or 50 blowgun needles, among other things. A compartmentalized pouch for holding spell components is called a component pouch (described earlier in this section).</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Belt</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Pouch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<location type="string">CLothes, Traveler's</location>
				<name type="string">Belt</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00017>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">30 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Viol</name>
				<subtype type="string">Musical Instrument</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00017>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Elvish</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Abyssal</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Draconic</name>
			</id-00004>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">3</level>
		<name type="string">Akris</name>
		<perception type="number">12</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I'm a born gambler who can't resist taking a risk for a potential payoff.\nI pocket anything I see that might have some value.\nYou always see the bright side of a situation.\nI am driven by wanderlust and want to explore lands far from our cities.</personalitytraits>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells (Warlock)</name>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">Race</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<savemod type="number">0</savemod>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<uses type="number">0</uses>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">Class</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<savemod type="number">0</savemod>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<uses type="number">0</uses>
			</id-00004>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">1</max>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">3</max>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">standard</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">IMMUNE: poison</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You are immune to poison damage and the poisoned condition.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Race</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Poison Immunity</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Yuan-ti Pureblood</source>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Magic Resistance</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against spells and other magical effects.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Race</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Magic Resistance</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Yuan-ti Pureblood</source>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d12</dice>
								<type type="string">poison</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You extend your hand toward a creature you can see within range and project a puff of noxious gas from your palm. The creature must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or take 1d12 poison damage.</p>
					<p>This spell's damage increases by 1d12 when you reach 5th level (2d12), 11th level (3d12), and 17th level (4d12).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Race</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Poison Spray</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">24</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Charmed</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a morsel of food)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell lets you convince a beast that you mean it no harm. Choose a beast that you can see within range. It must see and hear you. If the beast's Intelligence is 4 or higher, the spell fails. Otherwise, the beast must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be charmed by you for the spell's duration. If you or one of your companions harms the target, the spells ends.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can affect one additional beast for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">24 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Race</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Animal Friendship</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Nature Domain, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, M (a snake's tongue and either a bit of honeycomb or a drop of sweet oil)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You suggest a course of activity (limited to a sentence or two) and magically influence a creature you can see within range that can hear and understand you.</p>
					<p>Creatures that can't be charmed are immune to this effect. The suggestion must be worded in such a manner as to make the course of action sound reasonable.</p>
					<p>Asking the creature to stab itself, throw itself onto a spear, immolate itself, or do some other obviously harmful act ends the spell.</p>
					<p>The target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, it pursues the course of action you described to the best of its ability. The suggested course of action can continue for the entire duration. If the suggested activity can be completed in a shorter time, the spell ends when the subject finishes what it was asked to do. You can also specify conditions that will trigger a special activity during the duration. For example, you might suggest that a knight give her warhorse to the first beggar she meets. If the condition isn't met before the spell expires, the activity isn't performed.</p>
					<p>If you or any of your companions damage the target, the spell ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Race</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Suggestion</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Knowledge Domain, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 1st level, you gain the ability to channel celestial energy to heal wounds. You have a pool of d6s that you spend to fuel this healing. The number of dice in the pool equals 1 + your warlock level.</p>
					<p>As a bonus action, you can heal one creature you can see within 60 feet of you, spending dice from the pool. The maximum number of dice you can spend at once equals your Charisma modifier (minimum of one die).</p>
					<p>Roll the dice you spend, add them together, and restore a number of hit points equal to the total.</p>
					<p>Your pool regains all expended dice when you finish a long rest.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Healing Light</name>
				<prepared type="number">2</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Warlock</source>
				<specialization type="string">The Celestial</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, M (a firefly or phosphorescent moss)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch one object that is no larger than 10 feet in any dimension. Until the spell ends, the object sheds bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. The light can be colored as you like. Completely covering the object with something opaque blocks the light. The spell ends if you cast it again or dismiss it as an action.</p>
					<p>If you target an object held or worn by a hostile creature, that creature must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw to avoid the spell.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Class</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Light</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Flame-like radiance descends on a creature that you can see within range. The target must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw or take 1d8 radiant damage. The target gains no benefit from cover for this saving throw. The spell's damage increases by 1d8 when you reach 5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Class</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sacred Flame</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<type type="string">psychic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You unleash a string of insults laced with subtle enchantments at a creature you can see within range. If the target can hear you (though it need not understand you), it must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or take 1d4 psychic damage and have disadvantage on the next attack roll it makes before the end of its next turn. This spell's damage increases by 1d4 when you reach 5th level (2d4), 11th level (3d4), and 17th level (4d4).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Vicious Mockery</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 minute</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (two lodestones)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell repairs a single break or tear in an object you touch, such as a broken chain link, two halves of a broken key, a torn cloak, or a leaking wineskin. As long as the break or tear is no larger than 1 foot in any dimension, you mend it. leaving no trace of the former damage.</p>
					<p>This spell can physically repair a magic item or construct, but the spell can't restore magic to such an object.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mending</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">GRANTADVATK; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Each object in a 20-foot cube within range is outlined in blue, green, or violet light (your choice). Any creature in the area when the spell is cast is also outlined in light if it fails a Dexterity saving throw. For the duration, objects and affected creatures shed dim light in a 10-foot radius. Any attack roll against an affected creature or object has advantage if the attacker can see it, and the affected creature or object can't benefit from being invisible.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Faerie Fire</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Light Domain, Druid, Warlock (Archfey)</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">charisma</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">ATK: -1d4; SAVE: -1d4; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a drop of blood)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Up to three creatures of your choice that you can see within range must make Charisma saving throws. Whenever a target that fails this saving throw makes an attack roll or a saving throw before the spell ends, the target must roll a d4 and subtract the number rolled from the attack roll or saving throw.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bane</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Eldritch Invocations</source>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any.</p>
					<p>The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Magic</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Eldritch Knight, Eldritch Invocations, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Prone; Incapacitated; NOTE: Unable to stand up; NOTE: Save on end of round and damage; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (tiny tarts and a feather that is waved in the air)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature of your choice that you can see within range perceives everything as hilariously funny and falls into fits of laughter if this spell affects it. The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or fall prone, becoming incapacitated and unable to stand up for the duration. A creature with an Intelligence score of 4 or less isn't affected.</p>
					<p>At the end of each of its turns, and each time it takes damage, the target can make another Wisdom saving throw. The target has advantage on the saving throw if it's triggered by damage. On a success, the spell ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tasha's Hideous Laughter</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Warlock (Great Old One), Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A willing creature you touch is imbued with bravery.</p>
					<p>Until the spell ends, the creature is immune to being frightened and gains temporary hit points equal to your spellcasting ability modifier at the start of each of its turns. When the spell ends, the target loses any remaining temporary hit points from this spell.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heroism</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Paladin</source>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<type type="string">necrotic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d12</dice>
								<type type="string">necrotic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You point at one creature you can see within range, and the sound of a dolorous bell fills the air around it for a moment. The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or take 1d8 necrotic damage. If the target is missing any of its hit points, it instead takes 1d12 necrotic damage.</p>
					<p>The spell's damage increases by one die when you reach 5th level (2d8 or 2d12), 11th level (3d8 or 3d12), and 17th level (4d8 or 4d12).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Warlock)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Toll the Dead</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Necromancy</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10</dice>
								<type type="string">force</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A beam of crackling energy streaks toward a creature within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes 1d10 force damage.</p>
					<p>The spell creates more than one beam when you reach higher levels: two beams at 5th level, three beams at 11th level, and four beams at 17th level. You can direct the beams at the same target or at different ones. Make a separate attack roll for each beam.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Warlock)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Eldritch Blast</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Warlock</source>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">GRANTADVATK</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A flash of light streaks toward a creature of your choice within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes 4d6 radiant damage, and the next attack roll made against this target before the end of your next turn has advantage, thanks to the mystical dim light glittering on the target until then.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by</p>
					<p>1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Warlock)</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Guiding Bolt</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch regains a number of hit points equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Warlock)</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cure Wounds</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00025>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Bardic Inspiration; ATK: 1d6; SAVE: 1d6; CHECK: 1d6</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Quick Links</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_class" recordname="class.probard@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Bard</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.probard.features.id-00013@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Bardic Inspiration</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bardic Inspiration</name>
				<prepared type="number">3</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Bard - Class Ability</source>
			</id-00025>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">2</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple weapons, hand crossbows, longswords, rapiers, shortswords</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Tool: Viol, Flute, Lute</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Armor: Light armor</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00006>
				<name type="string">Tool: Leatherworker's Tools</name>
			</id-00006>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Yuan-ti Pureblood</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.yuan_tipureblood@Volos Guide to Monsters Players</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<senses type="string">Darkvision 60</senses>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">3</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token"></token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Innate Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Yuan-ti Pureblood</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You know the poison spray cantrip. You can cast animal friendship an unlimited number of times with this trait, but you can target only snakes with it. Starting at 3rd level, you can also cast suggestion with this trait. Once you cast it, you can't do so again until you finish a long rest. Charisma is your spellcasting ability for these spells.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.poisonspray@*"><b>Cantrip: </b></link>Poison Spray</linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.animalfriendship@*"><b>Spell: </b></link>Animal Friendship
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.suggestion@*"><b>Spell: </b></link>Suggestion
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Poison Immunity</name>
				<source type="string">Yuan-ti Pureblood</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You are immune to poison damage and the poisoned condition.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Magic Resistance</name>
				<source type="string">Yuan-ti Pureblood</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against spells and other magical effects.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00003>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Rapier</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00001</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00010</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00010</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00003>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">132</weight>
	</character>
</root>
