<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:4">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">15</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">4</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">11</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">5</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<alignment type="string">Lawful Good</alignment>
		<background type="string">City Watch</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>reference.backgrounddata.citywatch@D&#38;D Sword Coast Adventurer's Guide - Player's Guide</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">My honor is my life.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">2</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d10</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<name type="string">Ranger</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.ranger@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">638</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">EP</name>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">6</armor>
				<dexbonus type="string">no</dexbonus>
				<disstealth type="number">1</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">2</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">18</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">80</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">160</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">480</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">129.16</load>
			<max type="number">240</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">495</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">500</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Watcher's Eye</name>
				<source type="string">City Watch</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your experience in enforcing the law, and dealing with lawbreakers, gives you a feel for local laws and criminals. You can easily find the local outpost of the watch or a similar organization, and just as easily pick out the dens of criminal activity in a community, although you're more likely to be welcome in the former locations rather than the latter.</p>
					<h>Variant: Investigator</h>
					<p>Rarer than watch or patrol members are a community's investigators, who are responsible for solving crimes after the fact. Though such folk are seldom found in rural areas, nearly every settlement of decent size has at least one or two watch members who have the skill to investigate crime scenes and track down criminals. If your prior experience is as an investigator, you have proficiency in Investigation rather than Athletics.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Natural Explorer (forest)</name>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You are particularly familiar with one type of natural environment and are adept at traveling and surviving in such regions. Choose one type of favored terrain: arctic, coast, desert, forest, grassland, mountain, swamp, or the Underdark. When you make an Intelligence or Wisdom check related to your favored terrain, your proficiency bonus is doubled if you are using a skill that you're proficient in.</p>
					<p>While traveling for an hour or m ore in your favored terrain, you gain the following benefits:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Difficult terrain doesn't slow your group's travel.</li>
						<li>Your group can't become lost except by magical means.</li>
						<li>Even when you are engaged in another activity while traveling (such as foraging, navigating, or tracking), you remain alert to danger.</li>
						<li>If you are traveling alone, you can move stealthily at a normal pace.</li>
						<li>When you forage, you find twice as much food as you normally would.</li>
						<li>While tracking other creatures, you also learn their exact number, their sizes, and how long ago they passed through the area.</li>
					</list>
					<p>You choose additional favored terrain types at 6th and 10th level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Favored Enemy (undead)</name>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning at 1st level, you have significant experience studying, tracking, hunting, and even talking to a certain type of enemy.</p>
					<p>Choose a type of favored enemy: aberrations, beasts, celestials, constructs, dragons, elementals, fey, fiends, giants, monstrosities, oozes, plants, or undead. Alternatively, you can select two races of humanoid (such as gnolls and orcs) as favored enemies.</p>
					<p>You have advantage on Wisdom(Survival) checks to track your favored enemies, as well as on Intelligence checks to recall information about them.</p>
					<p>When you gain this feature, you also learn one language of your choice that is spoken by your favored enemies, if they speak one at all.</p>
					<p>You choose one additional favored enemy, as well as an associated language, at 6th and 14th level. As you gain levels, your choices should reflect the types of monsters you have encountered on your adventures.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style (dueling)</name>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you adopt a particular style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the following options. You can't take a Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.</p>
					<p><b>Archery</b></p>
					<p>You gain a +2 bonus to attack rolls you make with ranged weapons.</p>
					<p><b>Defense</b></p>
					<p>While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC.</p>
					<p><b>Dueling</b></p>
					<p>When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.</p>
					<p><b>Two-Weapon Fighting</b></p>
					<p>When you engage in two-weapon fighting, you can add your ability modifier to the damage of the second attack.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>By the time you reach 2nd level, you have learned to use the magical essence of nature to cast spells, much as a druid does. See chapter 10 for the general rules of spellcasting and chapter 11 for the ranger spell list.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="reference.spelllists.ranger@DD PHB Deluxe">Ranger Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Spell Slots</b></p>
					<p>The Ranger table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your ranger spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>For example, if you know the 1st-level spell animal friendship and have a 1st-level and a 2nd-level spell slot available, you can cast animal friendship using either slot.</p>
					<p><b>Spells Known of 1st Level and Higher</b></p>
					<p>You know two 1st-level spells of your choice from the ranger spell list.</p>
					<p>The Spells Known column of the Ranger table shows when you learn more ranger spells of your choice. Each of these spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots. For instance, when you reach 5th level in this class, you can learn one new spell of 1st or 2nd level. Additionally, when you gain a level in this class, you can choose one of the ranger spells you know and replace it with another spell from the ranger spell list, which also must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Wisdom is your spellcasting ability for your ranger spells, since your magic draws on your attunement to nature. You use your Wisdom whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Wisdom modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a ranger spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Monster Slayer</name>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have dedicated yourself to hunting down creatures of the night and wielders of grim magic. A Monster Slayer seeks out vampires, dragons, evil fey, fiends, and other magical threats. Trained in supernatural techniques to overcome such monsters, slayers are experts at unearthing and defeating mighty, mystical foes.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="imagewindow" recordname="reference.imagedata.img_monsterslayer_jpg@*"><b>Image: </b></link>Monster Slayer</linklist>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.ranger.features.monsterslayermagic3@*">Monster Slayer Magic</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.ranger.features.hunter_ssense3@*">Hunter's Sense</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.ranger.features.slayer_sprey3@*">Slayer's Prey</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.ranger.features.supernaturaldefense7@*">Supernatural Defense</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.ranger.features.magic_user_snemesis11@*">Magic-User's Nemesis</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.ranger.features.slayer_scounter15@*">Slayer's Counter</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Primeval Awareness</name>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning at 3rd level, you can use your action and expend one ranger spell slot to focus your awareness on the region around you. For 1 minute per level of the spell slot you expend, you can sense whether the following types of creatures are present within 1 mile of you (or within up to 6 miles if you are in your favored terrain): aberrations, celestials, dragons, elementals, fey, fiends, and undead. This feature doesn't reveal the creatures' location or number.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Monster Slayer Magic</name>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
				<specialization type="string">Monster Slayer</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 3rd level, you learn an additional spell when you reach certain levels in this class, as shown in the Monster Slayer Spells table. The spell counts as a ranger spell for you, but it doesn't count against the number of ranger spells you know.</p>
					<h>Monster Slayer Spells</h>
					<p><b>Level Spell</b></p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.protectionfromevilandgood@*"><b>3rd Level: </b></link>Protection from Evil and Good</linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.zoneoftruth@*"><b>5th Level: </b></link>Zone of Truth
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.magiccircle@*"><b>9th Level: </b></link>Magic Circle
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.banishment@*"><b>13th Level: </b></link>Banishment
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.holdmonster@*"><b>17th Level: </b></link>Hold Monster
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Slayer's Prey</name>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
				<specialization type="string">Monster Slayer</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 3rd level, you can focus your ire on one foe, increasing the harm you inflict on it. As a bonus action, you designate one creature you can see within 60 feet of you as the target of this feature. The first time each turn that you hit that target with a weapon attack, it takes an extra 1d6 damage from the weapon.</p>
					<p>This benefit lasts until you finish a short or long rest. It ends early if you designate a different creature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hunter's Sense</name>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
				<specialization type="string">Monster Slayer</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level, you gain the ability to peer at a creature and magically discern how best to hurt it. As an action, choose one creature you can see within 60 feet of you. You immediately learn whether the creature has any damage immunities, resistances, or vulnerabilities and what they are. If the creature is hidden from divination magic, you sense that it has no damage immunities, resistances, or vulnerabilities.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (minimum of once). You regain all expended uses of it when you finish a long rest.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00011>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I made a terrible mistake in battle that cost many lives-and I would do anything to keep that mistake secret.</flaws>
		<hero type="number">1</hero>
		<herodice type="string">d6</herodice>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">36</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Nation. My city, nation, or people are all that matter. (Any)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">2</total>
		</initiative>
		<inspiration type="number">0</inspiration>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A cloth or leather pouch can hold up to 20 sling bullets or 50 blowgun needles, among other things. A compartmentalized pouch for holding spell components is called a component pouch (described earlier in this section).</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Pouch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">3 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Several of the most common types of musical instruments are shown on the table as examples. If you have proficiency with a given musical instrument, you can add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make to play music with the instrument. A bard can use a musical instrument as a spellcasting focus, as described in Part 3: The Rules of Magic, Casting a Spell. Each type of musical instrument requires a separate proficiency.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Horn</name>
				<subtype type="string">Musical Instrument</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>These metal restraints can bind a Small or Medium creature. Escaping the manacles requires a successful DC 20 Dexterity check. Breaking them requires a successful DC 20 Strength check. Each set of manacles comes with one key. Without the key, a creature proficient with thieves' tools can pick the manacles' lock with a successful DC 15 Dexterity check. Manacles have 15 hit points.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Manacles</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>City Watch uniform indicative of your rank.</p>
				</description>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Uniform, City Watch</name>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">15 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Vestments</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<ac type="number">16</ac>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">75 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Of all the armor categories, heavy armor offers the best protection. These suits of armor cover the entire body and are designed to stop a wide range of attacks. Only proficient warriors can manage their weight and bulk.</p>
					<p>Made of interlocking metal rings, chain mail includes a layer of quilted fabric worn underneath the mail to prevent chafing and to cushion the impact of blows. The suit includes gauntlets.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Chain Mail</name>
				<stealth type="string">Disadvantage</stealth>
				<strength type="string">Str 13</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Heavy Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">55</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">5</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Javelin</name>
				<properties type="string">Thrown (range 30/120)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A holy symbol is a representation of a god or pantheon. It might be an amulet depicting a symbol representing a deity, the same symbol carefully engraved or inlaid as an emblem on a shield, or a tiny box holding a fragment of a sacred relic. The Player's Handbook lists many gods in the multiverse and their typical symbols. A cleric or paladin can use a holy symbol as a spellcasting focus, as described in chapter To use the symbol in this way, the caster must hold it in hand, wear it visibly, or bear it on a shield.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Amulet</name>
				<subtype type="string">Holy Symbol</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For 1 hour, a candle sheds bright light in a 5-foot radius and dim light for an additional 5 feet.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Candle</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<ac type="number">2</ac>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A shield is made from wood or metal and is carried in one hand. Wielding a shield increases your Armor Class by 2. You can benefit from only one shield at a time.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield</name>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Shield</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 slashing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Battleaxe</name>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Blanket</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Incense (One Block)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.03</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Alms Box</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Censer</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">50 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A character who drinks the magical red fluid in this vial regains 2d4 + 2 hit points. Drinking or administering a potion takes an action.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Pouch</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Potion of Healing</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">50 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Longbow</name>
				<properties type="string">Ammunition (range 150/600), heavy, two-handed</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Ranged Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00023>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Arrows (20)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Ammunition</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00025>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack</name>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00025>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Elvish</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Draconic</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Celestial</name>
			</id-00004>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">4</level>
		<name type="string">Malik</name>
		<pc_label_hero type="string">Hero Point</pc_label_hero>
		<perception type="number">10</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I'm always polite and respectful.</personalitytraits>
		<powerdisplaymode type="string">action</powerdisplaymode>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<savemod type="number">0</savemod>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<uses type="number">0</uses>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">consumables</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">standard actions</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">class features</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<savemod type="number">0</savemod>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<uses type="number">0</uses>
			</id-00004>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">combat</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<group type="string">consumables</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">healing potion</name>
				<prepared type="number">2</prepared>
				<usesperiod type="string">once</usesperiod>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<group type="string">consumables</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">rations</name>
				<prepared type="number">2</prepared>
				<usesperiod type="string">once</usesperiod>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<group type="string">consumables</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">water</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<usesperiod type="string">once</usesperiod>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<group type="string">consumables</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">light source</name>
				<prepared type="number">10</prepared>
				<usesperiod type="string">once</usesperiod>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Dodge</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">Action</castingtime>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you take the Dodge action, you focus entirely on avoiding attacks. Until the start of your next turn, any attack roll made against you has disadvantage if you can see the attacker, and you make Dexterity saving throws with advantage. You lose this benefit if you are incapacitated (as explained in the appendix) or if your speed drops to 0.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">standard actions</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Action: Dodge</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Actions</school>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">DMG: 2 melee</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you adopt a particular style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the following options. You can't take a Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.</p>
					<p><b>Archery</b></p>
					<p>You gain a +2 bonus to attack rolls you make with ranged weapons.</p>
					<p><b>Defense</b></p>
					<p>While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC.</p>
					<p><b>Dueling</b></p>
					<p>When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.</p>
					<p><b>Two-Weapon Fighting</b></p>
					<p>When you engage in two-weapon fighting, you can add your ability modifier to the damage of the second attack.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">class features</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style (dueling)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">action</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Help; ADVCHK: all; ADVATK</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">Action</castingtime>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can lend your aid to another creature in the completion of a task. When you take the Help action, the creature you aid gains advantage on the next ability check it makes to perform the task you are helping with, pjrovided that it makes the check before the start of your next turn.</p>
					<p>Alternatively, you can aid a friendly creature in attacking a creature within 5 feet of you. You feint, distract the target, or in some other way team up to make your ally's attack more effective. If your ally attacks the target before your next turn, the first attack roll is made with advantage.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">standard actions</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Action: Help</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Actions</school>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Hide</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">Action</castingtime>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you take the Hide action, you make a Dexterity (Stealth) check in an attempt to hide, following the rules in chapter 7 for hiding. If you succeed, you gain certain benefits, as described in the &#34;Unseen Attackers and Targets&#34; section later in this chapter.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">standard actions</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Action: Hide</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Action</school>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Ready</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">Action</castingtime>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Sometimes you want to get the jump on a foe or wait for a particular circumstance before you act. To do so, you can take the Ready action on your turn so that you can act later in the round using your reaction. For more information see &#34;Actions in Combat, Ch 9&#34;</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">standard actions</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Action: Ready</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Actions</school>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">action</apply>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Favored Enemy; ADVSKILL: survival</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<apply type="string">action</apply>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Favored Enemy; ADVCHK: intelligence</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning at 1st level, you have significant experience studying, tracking, hunting, and even talking to a certain type of enemy.</p>
					<p>Choose a type of favored enemy: aberrations, beasts, celestials, constructs, dragons, elementals, fey, fiends, giants, monstrosities, oozes, plants, or undead.</p>
					<p>Alternatively, you can select two races of humanoid (such as gnolls and orcs) as favored enemies.</p>
					<p>You have advantage on Wisdom(Survival) checks to track your favored enemies, as well as on Intelligence checks to recall information about them.</p>
					<p>When you gain this feature, you also learn one language of your choice that is spoken by your favored enemies, if they speak one at all.</p>
					<p>You choose one additional favored enemy, as well as an associated language, at 6th and 14th level. As you gain levels, your choices should reflect the types of monsters you have encountered on your adventures.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">class features</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ranger: Favored Enemy</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Class</school>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Natural Explorer; Group not slowed or lost, can move stealthily while traveling alone, tracking special</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You are particularly familiar with one type of natural environment and are adept at traveling and surviving in such regions. Choose one type of favored terrain: arctic, coast, desert, forest, grassland, mountain, swamp, or the Underdark. When you make an Intelligence or Wisdom check related to your favored terrain, your proficiency bonus is doubled if you are using a skill that you're proficient in.</p>
					<p>While traveling for an hour or m ore in your favored terrain, you gain the following benefits:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Difficult terrain doesn't slow your group's travel.</li>
						<li>Your group can't become lost except by magical means.</li>
						<li>Even when you are engaged in another activity while traveling (such as foraging, navigating, or tracking), you remain alert to danger.</li>
						<li>If you are traveling alone, you can move stealthily at a normal pace.</li>
						<li>When you forage, you find twice as much food as you normally would.</li>
						<li>While tracking other creatures, you also learn their exact number, their sizes, and how long ago they passed through the area.</li>
					</list>
					<p>You choose additional favored terrain types at 6th and 10th level.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">class features</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ranger: Natural Explorer</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Class</school>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level, you gain the ability to peer at a creature and magically discern how best to hurt it. As an action, choose one creature you can see within 60 feet of you. You immediately learn whether the creature has any damage immunities, resistances, or vulnerabilities and what they are. If the creature is hidden from divination magic, you sense that it has no damage immunities, resistances, or vulnerabilities.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (minimum of once). You regain all expended uses of it when you finish a long rest.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">class features</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ranger: Hunter's Sense (60)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<specialization type="string">Monster Slayer</specialization>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Primeval Awareness</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning at 3rd level, you can use your action and expend one ranger spell slot to focus your awareness on the region around you. For 1 minute per level of the spell slot you expend, you can sense whether the following types of creatures are present within 1 mile of you (or within up to 6 miles if you are in your favored terrain): aberrations, celestials, dragons, elementals, fey, fiends, and undead. This feature doesn't reveal the creatures' location or number.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">class features</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ranger: Primeval Awareness</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Class</school>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Slayer's Prey; DMG: 1d6</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 3rd level, you can focus your ire on one foe, increasing the harm you inflict on it. As a bonus action, you designate one creature you can see within 60 feet of you as the target of this feature. The first time each turn that you hit that target with a weapon attack, it takes an extra 1d6 damage from the weapon.</p>
					<p>This benefit lasts until you finish a short or long rest. It ends early if you designate a different creature.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">class features</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ranger: Slayer's Prey (B) (60)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<specialization type="string">Monster Slayer</specialization>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch regains a number of hit points equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p>At Higher Levels.</p>
					<p>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cure Wounds (T)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain the ability to comprehend and verbally communicate with beasts for the duration. The knowledge and awareness of many beasts is limited by their intelligence, but at minimum, beasts can give you information about nearby locations and monsters, including whatever they can perceive or have perceived within the past day. You might be able to persuade a beast to perform a small favor for you, at the DM's discretion.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Speak with Animals (RIT) (S)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Nature Domain, Druid, Eldritch Invocations, Ranger</source>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Hunter's Mark: IFT:Marked; DMG 1d6</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Marked</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You choose a creature you can see within range and mystically mark it as your quarry. Until the spell ends, you deal an extra 1d6 damage to the target whenever you hit it with a weapon attack, and you have advantage on any Wisdom (Perception) or Wisdom (Survival) check you make to find it. If the target drops to 0 hit points before this spell ends, you can use a bonus action on a subsequent turn of yours to mark a new creature.</p>
					<p>At Higher Levels.</p>
					<p>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd or 4th level, you can maintain your concentration on the spell for up to 8 hours. When you use a spell slot of 5th level or higher, you can maintain your concentration on the spell for up to 24 hours.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hunter's Mark (B) (90) (C) (SD)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">90 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Ranger</source>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 minute</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a tiny bell and a piece of fine silver wire)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You set an alarm against unwanted intrusion. Choose a door, a window, or an area within range that is no larger than a 20-foot cube. Until the spell ends, an alarm alerts you whenever a Tiny or larger creature touches or enters the warded area. When you cast the spell, you can designate creatures that won't set off the alarm. You also choose whether the alarm is mental or audible.</p>
					<p>A mental alarm alerts you with a ping in your mind if you are within 1 mile of the warded area. This ping awakens you if you are sleeping.</p>
					<p>An audible alarm produces the sound of a hand bell for 10 seconds within 60 feet.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Alarm (RIT) (30)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Ranger, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Detect Magic (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any.</p>
					<p>The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Magic (S) (C) (RIT)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Eldritch Knight, Eldritch Invocations, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00022>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">2</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple weapons, martial weapons</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Armor: Light armor, medium armor, shields</name>
			</id-00002>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Human</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.human@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">fletcher</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00019>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00003_token</token>
		<traitlist>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Javelin</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Thrown (range 30/120)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00010</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ammo type="number">0</ammo>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">5</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Javelin</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Thrown (range 30/120)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00010</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
						<type type="string">slashing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Battle axe</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00014</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00005>
				<ammo type="number">6</ammo>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">20</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Longbow</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Ammunition (range 150/600), heavy, two-handed</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00021</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">1</type>
			</id-00005>
		</weaponlist>
	</character>
</root>
