<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:3">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">6</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
				<save type="number">7</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">18</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">-1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">8</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<date type="string">12/09/2017</date>
				<earnmagic type="string">2</earnmagic>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">2017_12_09 game - Colin's GM</name>
				<startmagic type="string">0</startmagic>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>I Got 2 Dagger's +1 as reward from Queen Grevilea. when we restored heir throne</p>
				</text>
				<totalmagic type="string">2</totalmagic>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<date type="string">12/06/2017</date>
				<earnmagic type="string">1</earnmagic>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">2017_12_06 game - ProNobis GM</name>
				<startmagic type="string">0</startmagic>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Got a magical rope of climbing.</p>
				</text>
				<totalmagic type="string">1</totalmagic>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<date type="string">YYYY_MM_DD in title</date>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">2017_12_17 game - ProNobis GM</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Potion of Healing.</p>
					<p>Potion of Greater Healing.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">2018_01_14 game - ProNobis GM</name>
			</id-00004>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">22</age>
		<alignment type="string">Chaotic Neutral</alignment>
		<appearance type="string">Use a mask to hide a scar on the forehead.\nDresses most like a Jester. If needed to disguise, can take off the mask and put some other costume.</appearance>
		<background type="string">Entertainer</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>reference.backgrounddata.entertainer@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">I idolize a hero of the old tales and measure my deeds against that person's.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d8</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">6</level>
				<name type="string">Bard</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.bard@DD Xanathar's Guide to Everything Players</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">533</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">363</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">387</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">25</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">1</armor>
				<disstealth type="number">0</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">15</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<deity type="string">Tymora</deity>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">50</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">100</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">300</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">54.03</load>
			<max type="number">150</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">660</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">700</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">By Popular Demand</name>
				<source type="string">Entertainer</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can always find a place to perform, usually in an inn or tavern but possibly with a circus, at a theater, or even in a noble's court. At such a place, you receive free lodging and food of a modest or comfortable standard (depending on the quality of the establishment), as long as you perform each night. In addition, your performance makes you something of a local figure. When strangers recognize you in a town where you have performed, they typically take a liking to you.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have learned to untangle and reshape the fabric of reality in harmony with your wishes and music. Your spells are part of your vast repertoire, magic that you can tune to different situations. See chapter 10 for the general rules of spellcasting and chapter 11 for the bard spell list.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="reference.spelllists.bard@DD PHB Deluxe">Bard Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>You know two cantrips of your choice from the bard spell list. You learn additional bard cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Bard table.</p>
					<p><b>Spell Slots</b></p>
					<p>The Bard table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You must finish a long rest to regain any expended spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you know the 1st-level spell cure wounds and have a 1st-level and a 2nd-level spell slot available, you can cast cure wounds using either slot.</p>
					<p><b>Spells Known of 1st Level and Higher</b></p>
					<p>You know four 1st-level spells of your choice from the bard spell list.</p>
					<p>The Spells Known column of the Bard table shows when you learn more bard spells of your choice. Each of these spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots, as shown on the table. For instance, when you reach 3rd level in this class, you can learn one new spell of 1st or 2nd level.</p>
					<p>Additionally, when you gain a level in this class, you can choose one of the spells you know and replace it with another spell from the bard spell list, which must be of a level for which you have spell slots, as shown on the table.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Charisma is your spellcasting ability for your bard spells, since the power of your magic comes from the heart and soul you pour into the performance of your music or oration. You use your Charisma whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Charisma modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a bard spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p><b>Spell Save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spell Attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast any bard spell you know as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag. To cast a spell as a ritual, you must add 10 minutes to the spell's casting time, as normal.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a musical instrument as the material component for a bard spell, as described in chapter 10.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bardic Inspiration (1d8)</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can inspire others through stirring words or music. To do so, you use a bonus action on your turn to choose one creature other than yourself within 60 feet of you who can hear you. That creature gains one Bardic Inspiration die, a d6.</p>
					<p>Once within the next 10 minutes, the creature can roll the die and add the number rolled to one ability check, attack roll, or saving throw that it just made. The creature can wait until after it rolls the die for the ability check, attack roll, or saving throw, but before the DM says whether or not it succeeds or fails before deciding to use the Bardic Inspiration die. Once the Bardic Inspiration die is rolled, it is lost. A creature can have only one Bardic Inspiration die at a time.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Charisma modifier (a minimum of once). You regain any expended uses when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>Your Bardic Inspiration die changes when you reach certain levels in this class. The die becomes a d8 at 5th level, a d10 at 10th level, and a d12 at 15th level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Song of Rest</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning at 2nd level, you can use soothing music or oration to help revitalize your wounded allies during a short rest. If you or any friendly creature who can hear your performance regains any hit points during the short rest, that creature regains 1d6 extra hit points at the end of the rest. A creature regains the extra hit points only if it spends one or more Hit Dice at the end of the short rest.</p>
					<p>The extra hit points increase when you reach certain levels in this class: 1d8 at 9th level, 1d10 at 13th level, and 1d12 at 17th level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Jack of All Trades</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can add half your proficiency bonus, rounded down, to any ability check you make that doesn't already include that bonus.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">College of Lore</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Bards of the College of Lore know something about everything, collecting bits of knowledge from sources as diverse as ancient tomes and peasant tales. Whether singing folk ballads in taverns or elaborate compositions in royal courts, these bards use their gifts to hold audiences spellbound. When the applause dies down, the audience members might find themselves questioning everything they held to be true, from their faith in the priesthood of the local temple to their loyalty to the king.</p>
					<p>The loyalty of these bards lies in the pursuit of beauty and truth, not in fealty to a monarch or following the tenets of a deity. A noble who keeps such a bard as a herald or adviser knows that the bard would rather be honest than politic.</p>
					<p>The college's members gather in libraries and sometimes in actual colleges, complete with classrooms and dormitories, to share their lore with one another. They also meet at festivals or affairs of state, where they can expose corruption, unravel lies, and poke fun at self important figures of authority.</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.bard.features.bonusproficiencies_lore_3@DD PHB Deluxe">Bonus Proficiencies (Lore)</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.bard.features.cuttingwords3@DD PHB Deluxe">Cutting Words</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.bard.features.additionalmagicalsecrets6@DD PHB Deluxe">Additional Magical Secrets</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.bard.features.peerlessskill14@DD PHB Deluxe">Peerless Skill</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cutting Words</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<specialization type="string">College of Lore</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you join the College of Lore at 3rd level, you learn how to use your wit to distract, confuse, and otherwise sap the confidence and competence of others.</p>
					<p>When a creature that you can see within 60 feet of you makes an attack roll, an ability check, or a damage roll, you can use your reaction to expend one of your uses of Bardic Inspiration, rolling a Bardic Inspiration die and subtracting the number rolled from the creature's roll. You can choose to use this feature after the creature makes its roll, but before the DM determines whether the attack roll or ability check succeeds or fails, or before the creature deals its damage. The creature is immune if it can't hear you or if it's immune to being charmed.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bonus Proficiencies (Lore) - Athletics, Insight, Investigation</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<specialization type="string">College of Lore</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you join the College of Lore at 3rd level, you gain proficiency with three skills of your choice.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Expertise - Performance, Acrobatics</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level, choose two of your skill proficiencies. Your proficiency bonus is doubled for any ability check you make that involves one of the chosen proficiencies.</p>
					<p>At 10th level, you can choose another two skill proficiencies to gain this benefit.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement (+2 Dex)</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<level type="number">5</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Font of Inspiration</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning when you reach 5th level, you regain all of your expended uses of Bardic Inspiration when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<level type="number">6</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Countercharm</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 6th level, you gain the ability to use musical notes or words of power to disrupt mind influencing effects. As an action, you can start a performance that lasts until the end of your next turn. During that time, you and any friendly creature within 30 feet of you have advantage on saving throws against being frightened or charmed. A creature must be able to hear you to gain this benefit. The performance ends early if you are incapacitated or silenced or you voluntarily end it (no action required).</p>
				</text>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<level type="number">6</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Additional Magical Secrets (Counterspell, Haste)</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<specialization type="string">College of Lore</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 6th level, you learn two spells of your choice from any class. A spell you choose must be of a level you can cast, as shown on the Bard table, or a cantrip. The chosen spells count as bard spells for you and don't count against the number of bard spells you know.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00013>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I'll do anything to win fame and renown.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">3'1''</height>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">45</total>
			<wounds type="number">2</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Creativity. The world is in need of new ideas and bold action. (Chaotic)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">4</total>
		</initiative>
		<inspiration type="number">1</inspiration>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">7</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Costume</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This pouch of cosmetics, hair dye, and small props lets you create disguises that change your physical appearance. Proficiency with this kit lets you add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make to create a visual disguise.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Disguise Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Kits / Sets</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For 1 hour, a candle sheds bright light in a 5-foot radius and dim light for an additional 5 feet.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Candle</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">12 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Several of the most common types of musical instruments are shown on the table as examples. If you have proficiency with a given musical instrument, you can add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make to play music with the instrument. A bard can use a musical instrument as a spellcasting focus, as described in Part 3: The Rules of Magic, Casting a Spell. Each type of musical instrument requires a separate proficiency.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Pan Flute</name>
				<subtype type="string">Musical Instrument</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">101 - 500 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You regain 4d4 + 4 hit points when you drink this potion. The potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Potion of Greater Healing</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Potion</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A vial of red liquid that shimmers when agitated.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Potion</type>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<ac type="number">11</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Made from supple and thin materials, light armor favors agile adventurers since it offers some protection without sacrificing mobility. If you wear light armor, you add your Dexterity modifier to the base number from your armor type to determine your Armor Class.</p>
					<p>The breastplate and shoulder protectors of this armor are made of leather that has been stiffened by being boiled in oil. The rest of the armor is made of softer and more flexible materials.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">Yes</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Leather</name>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Light Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">300 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.bracersofarchery@Incarnate-Engine">Bracers of Archery</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>While wearing these bracers, you have proficiency with the longbow and shortbow, and you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls on ranged attacks made with such weapons.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bracers of Archery</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Bracers</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Thin leather bracers.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">uncommon (requires attunement)</rarity>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">35 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Several of the most common types of musical instruments are shown on the table as examples. If you have proficiency with a given musical instrument, you can add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make to play music with the instrument. A bard can use a musical instrument as a spellcasting focus, as described in Part 3: The Rules of Magic, Casting a Spell. Each type of musical instrument requires a separate proficiency.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lute</name>
				<subtype type="string">Musical Instrument</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">50 - 100 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You regain 2d4 + 2 hit points when you drink this potion. The potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Potion of Healing</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Potion</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A vial of red liquid that shimmers when agitated.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<type type="string">Potion</type>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This is a necklace said to belong to a hero of old tales I Idolize</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Necklace</name>
				<subtype type="string">Adventuring Gear</subtype>
				<type type="string">Necklace</type>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A cloth or leather pouch can hold up to 20 sling bullets or 50 blowgun needles, among other things. A compartmentalized pouch for holding spell components is called a component pouch (described earlier in this section).</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Pouch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">101 - 500 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>This 60-foot length of silk rope weighs 3 pounds and can hold up to 3,000 pounds. If you hold one end of the rope and use an action to speak the command word, the rope animates. As a bonus action, you can command the other end to move toward a destination you choose. That end moves 10 feet on your turn when you first command it and 10 feet on each of your turns until reaching its destination, up to its maximum length away, or until you tell it to stop. You can also tell the rope to fasten itself securely to an object or to unfasten itself, to knot or unknot itself, or to coil itself for carrying.</p>
					<p>If you tell the rope to knot, large knots appear at 1-foot intervals along the rope. While knotted, the rope shortens to a 50-foot length and grants advantage on checks made to climb it.</p>
					<p>The rope has AC 20 and 20 hit points. It regains 1 hit point every 5 minutes as long as it has at least 1 hit point. If the rope drops to 0 hit points, it is destroyed.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope of Climbing</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Silken Rope</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A 60 foot length of fine quality silken rope.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Quenn Grevillea give to us a necklace so her people will recognize us in her service</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Grevillea Flower necklace</name>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">101 - 500 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<damage type="string">1d4 piercing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>Magic weapons are unmistakably finer in quality than their ordinary counterparts. You have a +1 bonus to the attack rolls and damage rolls you make with this weapon.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dagger, +1</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Refined Dagger</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">The attention to detail and the materials used mark this weapon out as special.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60), magic</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<spells>
					<id-00001>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class></class>
							<recordname></recordname>
						</link>
						<name type="string">Weapon, +1</name>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class></class>
							<recordname></recordname>
						</link>
						<name type="string">Dagger</name>
					</id-00002>
				</spells>
				<subtype type="string">Dagger</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">6</count>
				<damage type="string">1d4 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00019>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Halfling</name>
			</id-00002>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">6</level>
		<name type="string">Milo High-hill</name>
		<notes type="string">Entertainer Routines: juggler, Instrumentalist, Storyteller\nSome history: Not the wisest one bard, trying to have a bold performance juggling daggers, in kind of ways to win fame in some city of the North (Faerun) did not percept a fight starting in the tavern, tables are turn, chairs flying, and got myself a pretty bad injury on the forehead, leaving a scar. Try to hide the scar with a mask to not intimidate people, so i can continue performance and earn a renown wherever i go, and follow a path toward greatness like my hero Regis.\n\nAdventuring everytime that a group would accept so can win famous too, creating or living some heroic stories to tell after.\n\nIn battle: prefers to dual weapon fighting style, dual daggers, can throw one of them to leave a hand free for somatic spells, or to play a pan flute. Try to focus in spells to control the battle, rather to just explore damage. As an extent of a juggler, intends to be an Dual-Throwing-dagger fight-style.</notes>
		<perception type="number">9</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">Nobody stays angry at me or around me for long, since I can defuse any amount of tension. I love a good insult, even one directed at me.</personalitytraits>
		<powerdisplaymode type="string">action</powerdisplaymode>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<savemod type="number">0</savemod>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<uses type="number">0</uses>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Bardic Inspiration</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">Features</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<savemod type="number">0</savemod>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<uses type="number">0</uses>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Potions</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<name type="string">Racial Trait</name>
			</id-00005>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">4</max>
				<used type="number">3</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">3</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">2</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">standard</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">charisma</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">ATK: -1d4; SAVE: -1d4; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a drop of blood)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Up to three creatures of your choice that you can see within range must make Charisma saving throws. Whenever a target that fails this saving throw makes an attack roll or a saving throw before the spell ends, the target must roll a d4 and subtract the number rolled from the attack roll or saving throw.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bane</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Eldritch Invocations</source>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">thunder</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a chip of mica)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A sudden loud ringing noise, painfully intense, erupts from a point of your choice within range. Each creature in a 10-foot-radius sphere centered on that point must make a Constitution saving throw. A creature takes 3d8 thunder damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. A creature made of inorganic material such as stone, crystal, or metal has disadvantage on this saving throw.</p>
					<p>A nonmagical object that isn't being worn or carried also takes the damage if it's in the spell's area.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shatter</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Tempest Domain, Eldritch Knight, Monk, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, M (a firefly or phosphorescent moss)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch one object that is no larger than 10 feet in any dimension. Until the spell ends, the object sheds bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. The light can be colored as you like. Completely covering the object with something opaque blocks the light. The spell ends if you cast it again or dismiss it as an action.</p>
					<p>If you target an object held or worn by a hostile creature, that creature must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw to avoid the spell.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Light</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<type type="string">psychic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">DISATK</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You unleash a string of insults laced with subtle enchantments at a creature you can see within range. If the target can hear you (though it need not understand you), it must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or take 1d4 psychic damage and have disadvantage on the next attack roll it makes before the end of its next turn. This spell's damage increases by 1d4 when you reach 5th level (2d4), 11th level (3d4), and 17th level (4d4).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Vicious Mockery</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Jack of All Trades; CHECK: [HPRF]; SKILL: [-HPRF], acrobatics, athletics, deception, insight, investigation, performance, persuasion, stealth</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can add half your proficiency bonus, rounded down, to any ability check you make that doesn't already include that bonus.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Features</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Jack of All Trades</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4,d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature of your choice that you can see within range regains hit points equal to 1d4 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d4 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Healing Word</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Unconscious</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of fine sand, rose petals, or a cricket)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell sends creatures into a magical slumber.</p>
					<p>Roll 5d8; the total is how many hit points of creatures this spell can affect. Creatures within 20 feet of a point you choose within range are affected in ascending order of their current hit points (ignoring unconscious creatures).</p>
					<p>Starting with the creature that has the lowest current hit points, each creature affected by this spell falls unconscious until the spell ends, the sleeper takes damage, or someone uses an action to shake or slap the sleeper awake. Subtract each creature's hit points from the total before moving on to the creature with the next lowest hit points. A creature's hit points must be equal to or less than the remaining total for that creature to be affected.</p>
					<p>Undead and creatures immune to being charmed aren't affected by this spell.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, roll an additional 2d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sleep</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">90 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Warlock (Archfey), Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">thunder</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A wave of thunderous force sweeps out from you. Each creature in a 15-foot cube originating from you must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, a creature takes 2d8 thunder damage and is pushed 10 feet away from you. On a successful save, the creature takes half as much damage and isn't pushed.</p>
					<p>In addition, unsecured objects that are completely within the area of effect are automatically pushed 10 feet away from you by the spell's effect, and the spell emits a thunderous boom audible out to 300 feet.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Thunderwave</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self (15-foot cube)</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Tempest Domain, Druid, Eldritch Knight, Monk, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Lucky; IF: (SKL, ATK, CHK); Reroll 1</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you roll a 1 on an attack roll, ability check, or saving throw, you can reroll the die and must use the new roll.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Racial Trait</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lucky</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Brave; ADVSAV: wisdom</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against being frightened.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Racial Trait</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Brave</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<label type="string">ATK: -1d6; CHECK: -1d6; DMG: -1d6</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you join the College of Lore at 3rd level, you learn how to use your wit to distract, confuse, and otherwise sap the confidence and competence of others.</p>
					<p>When a creature that you can see within 60 feet of you makes an attack roll, an ability check, or a damage roll, you can use your reaction to expend one of your uses of Bardic Inspiration, rolling a Bardic Inspiration die and subtracting the number rolled from the creature's roll. You can choose to use this feature after the creature makes its roll, but before the DM determines whether the attack roll or ability check succeeds or fails, or before the creature deals its damage. The creature is immune if it can't hear you or if it's immune to being charmed.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Bardic Inspiration</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cutting Words</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<specialization type="string">College of Lore</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Bardic Inspiration (d8) used for ability check, attack roll, or saving throw</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">ATK: 1d8; CHECK: 1d8: SAVE: 1d8</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">3</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can inspire others through stirring words or music. To do so, you use a bonus action on your turn to choose one creature other than yourself within 60 feet of you who can hear you. That creature gains one Bardic Inspiration die, a d6.</p>
					<p>Once within the next 10 minutes, the creature can roll the die and add the number rolled to one ability check, attack roll, or saving throw that it just made. The creature can wait until after it rolls the die for the ability check, attack roll, or saving throw, but before the DM says whether or not it succeeds or fails before deciding to use the Bardic Inspiration die. Once the Bardic Inspiration die is rolled, it is lost. A creature can have only one Bardic Inspiration die at a time.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Charisma modifier (a minimum of once). You regain any expended uses when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>Your Bardic Inspiration die changes when you reach certain levels in this class. The die becomes a d8 at 5th level, a d10 at 10th level, and a d12 at 15th level.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Bardic Inspiration</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bardic Inspiration</name>
				<prepared type="number">3</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">RESIST: bludgeoning,piercing,slashing</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You extend your hand and trace a sigil of warding in the air. Until the end of your next turn, you have resistance against bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing damage dealt by weapon attacks.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Blade Ward</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">psychic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You whisper a discordant melody that only one creature of your choice within range can hear, wracking it with terrible pain. The target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, it takes 3d6 psychic damage and must immediately use its reaction, if available, to move as far as its speed allows away from you. The creature doesn't move into obviously dangerous ground, such as a fire or a pit. On a successful save, the target takes half as much damage and doesn't have to move away. A deafened creature automatically succeeds on the save.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dissonant Whispers</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Warlock (Great Old One)</source>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Naturally Stealthy; Hide attempt obsucured by creature at least one size larger</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can attempt to hide even when you are obscured only by a creature that is at least one size larger than you.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Racial Trait</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Halfling: Naturally Stealthy</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Racial</school>
				<source type="string">Lightfoot</source>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Paralyzed; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a small, straight piece of iron)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose a humanoid that you can see within range.</p>
					<p>The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be paralyzed for the duration. At the end of each of its turns, the target can make another Wisdom saving throw. On a success, the spell ends on the target.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you can target one additional humanoid for each slot level above 2nd. The humanoids must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hold Person</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Druid Arctic Circle, Eldritch Knight, Monk, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<group type="string">Features</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">Song of Rest</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Incapacitated; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">S, M (a glowing stick of incense or a crystal vial filled with phosphorescent material)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create a twisting pattern of colors that weaves through the air inside a 30-foot cube within range. The pattern appears for a moment and vanishes. Each creature in the area who sees the pattern must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, the creature becomes charmed for the duration. While charmed by this spell, the creature is incapacitated and has a speed of 0.</p>
					<p>The spell ends for an affected creature if it takes any damage or if someone else uses an action to shake the creature out of its stupor.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hypnotic Pattern</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<group type="string">Potions</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">Healing Potion</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4,d4,d4</dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4,d4,d4</dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<group type="string">Potions</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">Potion of Greater Healing</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a rotten egg or several skunk cabbage leaves)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create a 20-foot-radius sphere of yellow, nauseating gas centered on a point within range. The cloud spreads around corners, and its area is heavily obscured. The cloud lingers in the air for the duration.</p>
					<p>Each creature that is completely within the cloud at the start of its turn must make a Constitution saving throw against poison. On a failed save, the creature spends its action that turn retching and reeling.</p>
					<p>Creatures that don't need to breathe or are immune to poison automatically succeed on this saving throw.</p>
					<p>A moderate wind (at least 10 miles per hour) disperses the cloud after 4 rounds. A strong wind (at least 20 miles per hour) disperses it after 1 round.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Stinking Cloud</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">90 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid Swamp Circle, Druid Underdark Circle, Eldritch Knight, Warlock (Fiend), Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 reaction, which you take when you see a creature within 60 feet of you casting a spell</castingtime>
				<components type="string">S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You attempt to interrupt a creature in the process of casting a spell. If the creature is casting a spell of 3rd level or lower, its spell fails and has no effect. If it is casting a spell of 4th level or higher, make an ability check using your spellcasting ability. The DC equals 10 + the spell's level. On a success, the creature's spell fails and has no effect.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher, the interrupted spell has no effect if its level is less than or equal to the level of the spell slot you used.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Counterspell</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">NOTE: Hasted; AC: 2; ADVSAV: dexterity; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a shaving of licorice root)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose a willing creature that you can see within range.</p>
					<p>Until the spell ends, the target's speed is doubled, it gains a +2 bonus to AC, it has advantage on Dexterity saving throws, and it gains an additional action on each of its turns. That action can be used only to take the Attack (one weapon attack only), Dash, Disengage, Hide, or Use an Object action.</p>
					<p>When the spell ends, the target can't move or take actions until after its next turn, as a wave of lethargy sweeps over it.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Haste</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid Grassland Circle, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00023>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">3</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: Disguise kit, one type of musical instrument (Pan flute)</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple weapons, hand crossbows, longswords, rapiers, shortswords</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Tool: Three musical instruments of your choice (Lute, Drums, Lyre)</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Armor: Light armor</name>
			</id-00004>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Halfling (Lightfoot)</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.halfling@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<size type="string">Small</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">2</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">9</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">2</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">10</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">7</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">25</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">25</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00008_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lucky</name>
				<source type="string">Halfling</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you roll a 1 on an attack roll, ability check, or saving throw, you can reroll the die and must use the new roll.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Halfling Nimbleness</name>
				<source type="string">Halfling</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can move through the space of any creature that is of a size larger than yours.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Brave</name>
				<source type="string">Halfling</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against being frightened.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Naturally Stealthy</name>
				<source type="string">Lightfoot</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can attempt to hide even when you are obscured only by a creature that is at least one size larger than you.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00004>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">1</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<type type="string">piercing, magic</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger, +1 (2nd Hand ATK)</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class></class>
					<recordname></recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ammo type="number">0</ammo>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<maxammo type="number">6</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger (2nd hand throw)</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class></class>
					<recordname></recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attackbonus type="number">1</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing, magic</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger, +1</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00018</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00005>
				<ammo type="number">0</ammo>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">6</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00019</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00005>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">41 lb</weight>
	</character>
</root>
