<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:4">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">-1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">9</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">13</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">5</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">-1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">9</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">5</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">35</age>
		<alignment type="string">Chaotic Good</alignment>
		<appearance type="string">Mirfal has a very pale complexion; long black dreads as well as a long beard.\nHis spellbook is a faded leather binder, inside is a collection of tattered notes. The spells are written in a special ink that can only been seen if veiwed via a special eye glass that Mirfal wears around his neck.\n\nHis clothing has faded from years of use but are otherwise clean and in good condition. Mirfal keeps mint in his pockets to mask the smell of tobacco.</appearance>
		<background type="string">Hermit</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>reference.backgrounddata.hermit@DD PHB PC Customization Pack</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">I entered seclusion because I loved someone I could not have.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d6</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<name type="string">Wizard</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.wizard@DD PHB Class Pack - Wizard</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">109</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">39</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">48</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">0</armor>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">11</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">45</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">90</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">270</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">77.8</load>
			<max type="number">135</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">477</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">400</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Discovery</name>
				<source type="string">Hermit</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>The quiet seclusion of your extended hermitage gave you access to a unique and powerful discovery. The exact nature of this revelation depends on the nature of your seclusion. It might be a great truth about the cosmos, the deities, the powerful beings of the outer planes, or the forces of nature. It could be a site that no one else has ever seen. You might have uncovered a fact that has long been forgotten, or unearthed some relic of the past that could rewrite history. It might be information that would be damaging to the people w ho or consigned you to exile, and hence the reason for your return to society. Work with your DM to determine the details of your discovery and its impact on the campaign.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>As a student of arcane magic, you have a spellbook containing spells that show the first glimmerings of your true power. See chapter 10 for the general rules of spellcasting and chapter 11 for the wizard spell list.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="reference.spelllists.wizard@DD PHB Class Pack - Wizard">Wizards Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you know three cantrips of your choice from the wizard spell list. You learn additional wizard cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Wizard table.</p>
					<p><b>Spellbook</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you have a spellbook containing six 1st-level wizard spells of your choice.</p>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Wizard table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your wizard spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of wizard spells that are available for you to cast. To do so, choose a number of wizard spells from your spellbook equal to your Intelligence modifier + your wizard level (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you're a 3rd-level wizard, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With an Intelligence of 16, your list of prepared spells can include six spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination, chosen from your spellbook. If you prepare the 1st-level spell magic missile, you can cast it using a 1st-level or a 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of wizard spells requires time spent studying your spellbook and memorizing the incantations and gestures you must make to cast the spell: at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Intelligence is your spellcasting ability for your wizard spells, since you learn your spells through dedicated study and memorization. You use your Intelligence whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability.</p>
					<p>In addition, you use your Intelligence modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a wizard spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Intelligence modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Intelligence modifier</p>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast a wizard spell as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag and you have the spell in your spellbook. You don't need to have the spell prepared.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use an arcane focus (found in chapter 5) as a spellcasting focus for your wizard spells.</p>
					<p><b>Learning Spells of 1st Level and Higher</b></p>
					<p>Each time you gain a wizard level, you can add two wizard spells of your choice to your spellbook. Each of these spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots, as shown on the Wizard table. On your adventures, you might find other spells that you can add to your spellbook (see the &#34;Your Spellbook&#34; sidebar).</p>
					<h>Your Spellbook</h>
					<p>The spells that you add to your spellbook as you gain levels reflect the arcane research you conduct on your own, as well as intellectual breakthroughs you have had about the nature of the multiverse. You might find other spells during your adventures. You could discover a spell recorded on a scroll in an evil wizard's chest, for example, or in a dusty tome in an ancient library.</p>
					<p><b><i>Copying a Spell into the book. </i></b>When you find a wizard spell of 1st level or higher, you can add it to your spellbook if it is of a level for which you have spell slots and if you can spare the time to decipher and copy it. The spells copied into a spellbook must be of a spell level the wizard can prepare.</p>
					<p>Copying a spell into your spellbook involves reproducing the basic form of the spell, then deciphering the unique system of notation used by the wizard who wrote it. You must practice the spell until you understand the sounds or gestures required, then transcribe it into your spellbook using your own notation.</p>
					<p>For each level of the spell, the process takes 2 hours and costs 50gp. The cost represents material components you expend as you experiment with the spell to master it, as well as the fine inks you need to record it. Once you have spent this time and money, you can prepare the spell just like your other spells.</p>
					<p><b><i>Replacing the Book. </i></b>You can copy a spell from your own spellbook into another book-for example, if you want to make a backup copy of your spellbook. This is just like copying a new spell into your spellbook, but faster and easier, since you understand your own notation and already know how to cast the spell. You need spend only 1 hour and 10 gp for each level of the copied spell. If you lose your spellbook, you can use the same procedure to transcribe the spells that you have prepared into a new spellbook. Filling out the remainder of your spellbook requires you to find new spells to do so, as normal. For this reason, many wizards keep backup spellbooks in a safe place.</p>
					<p><b><i>The Book's Appearance </i></b>Your spellbook is a unique compilation of spells, with its own decorative flourishes and margin notes. It might be a plain, functional leather volume that you received as a gift from your master, a finely bound gilt-edged tome you found in an ancient library, or even a loose collection of notes scrounged together after you lost your previous spellbook in a mishap.</p>
					<p>A spellbook doesn't contain cantrips.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Arcane Recovery</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have learned to regain some of your magical energy by studying your spellbook. Once per day when you finish a short rest, you can choose expended spell slots to recover. The spell slots can have a combined level that is equal to or less than half your wizard level (rounded up), and none of the slots can be 6th level or higher.</p>
					<p>For example, if you're a 4th-level wizard, you can recover up to two levels worth of spell slots. You can recover either a 2nd-level spell slot or two 1st-level spell slots.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">School of Illusion</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You focus your studies on magic that dazzles the senses, befuddles the mind, and tricks even the wisest folk. Your magic is subtle, but the illusions crafted by your keen mind make the impossible seem real. Some illusionists-including many gnome wizards-are benign tricksters who use their spells to entertain. Others are more sinister masters of deception, using their illusions to frighten and fool others for their personal gain.</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.illusionsavant2@DD PHB Deluxe">Illusion Savant</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.improvedminorillusion2@DD PHB Deluxe">Improved Minor Illusion</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.malleableillusions6@DD PHB Deluxe">Malleable Illusions</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.illusoryself10@DD PHB Deluxe">Illusory Self</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.illusoryreality14@DD PHB Deluxe">Illusory Reality</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Improved Minor Illusion</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<specialization type="string">School of Illusion</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you choose this school at 2nd level, you learn the minor illusion cantrip. If you already know this cantrip, you learn a different wizard cantrip of your choice. The cantrip doesn't count against your number of cantrips known.</p>
					<p>When you cast minor illusion, you can create both a sound and an image with a single casting of the spell.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Illusion Savant</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<specialization type="string">School of Illusion</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning when you select this school at 2nd level, the gold and time you must spend to copy an illusion spell into your spellbook is halved.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">Now that I have returned to the world, I enjoy its delights a little to much.\nI am a tobacco fiend.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">5.7&#34;</height>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">25</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Inquiry and curiosity are the pillars of progress.</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">1</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 bludgeoning</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Quarterstaff</name>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d8)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">7</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">8</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tin box contains a cup and simple cutlery. The box clamps together, and one side can be used as a cooking pan and the other as a plate or shallow bowl.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mess Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Equipment Kits</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">50 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Essential for wizards, a spellbook is a leather-bound tome with 100 blank vellum pages suitable for recording spells.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellbook</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Common</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This kit contains a variety of instruments such as clippers, mortar and pestle, and pouches and vials used by herbalists to create remedies and potions. Proficiency with this kit lets you add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make to identify or apply herbs. Also, proficiency with this kit is required to create antitoxin and potions of healing.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Herbalism Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Kits / Sets</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Winter Blanket</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Skill Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_skill" recordname="skill.id-00275@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Shawm</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>A hollow wooden instrument where the player blows through the mouthpiece to make sound. There are usually holes along the length of the pipe that change the sound when covered by the player's fingers.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00002@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Rules for Using a Musical Instrument</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shawm</name>
				<subtype type="string">Musical Instrument</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tool</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">7</count>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<name type="string">Small Feather</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">400 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This hollow metal tube measures about 1 foot long and weighs 1 pound. You can strike it as an action, pointing it at an object within 120 feet of you that can be opened, such as a door, lid, or lock. The chime issues a clear tone, and one lock or latch on the object opens unless the sound can't reach the object.</p>
					<p>If no locks or latches remain, the object itself opens.</p>
					<p>The chime can be used ten times. After the tenth time, it cracks and becomes useless.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Chime of Opening</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Metal Tube</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A hollow metal tube about 1 foot long</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Rare</rarity>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">4</count>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<name type="string">Cured Leather</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">50 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Linked Spell</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.illusoryscript@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Illusory Script</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>A spell scroll bears the words of a single spell, written in a mystical cipher. If the spell is on your class's spell list, you can read the scroll and cast its spell without providing any material components.</p>
					<p>Otherwise, the scroll is unintelligible. Casting the spell by reading the scroll requires the spell's normal casting time. Once the spell is cast, the words on the scroll fade, and it crumbles to dust. If the casting is interrupted, the scroll is not lost.</p>
					<p>If the spell is on your class's spell list but of a higher level than you can normally cast, you must make an ability check using your spellcasting ability to determine whether you cast it successfully. The DC equals 10 + the spell's level. On a failed check, the spell disappears from the scroll with no other effect.</p>
					<p>The level of the spell on the scroll determines the spell's saving throw DC and attack bonus, as well as the scroll's rarity, as shown in the Spell Scroll table.</p>
					<p>Spell Scroll</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Spell Level</td>
							<td>Rarity</td>
							<td>Save DC</td>
							<td>Attack Bonus</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>1st</td>
							<td>Common</td>
							<td>13</td>
							<td>+5</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>A wizard spell on a spell scroll can be copied just as spells in spellbooks can be copied. When a spell is copied from a spell scroll, the copier must succeed on an Intelligence (Arcana) check with a DC equal to 10 + the spell's level. If the check succeeds, the spell is successfully copied. Whether the check succeeds or fails, the spell scroll is destroyed.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Scroll of Illusory Script</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Scroll</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Mundane Scroll</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<type type="string">Scroll</type>
				<weight type="number">0.3</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">4</count>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<name type="string">Fleece</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<name type="string">Lodestones</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">100 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Action Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.potionofgreaterhealing@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Potion of Greater Healing</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You regain hit points when you drink this potion.</p>
					<p>The number of hit points depends on the potion's rarity, as shown in the Potions of Healing table. Whatever its potency, the potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</p>
					<h>Potions of Healing</h>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Potion of .</td>
							<td>Rarity</td>
							<td>HP Regained</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Greater healing</td>
							<td>Uncommon</td>
							<td>4d4 + 4</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Greater Potion of Healing</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Dim Potion</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">The potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Potion</type>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00021>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Elvish</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Gnomish</name>
			</id-00004>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">4</level>
		<name type="string">Mirfal Benosel</name>
		<notes type="string">Backstory:\nMirfal Benosel grew up in Baldur's Gate in a middle class merchant's family with his father(Ovir) and older sister(Birala), his mother died of a illness when Mirfel was just a baby. \n\nGrowing up Mirfal was interested in history, music and magic. His father encouraged this and hired Rehner Remmo, one of the best tutors in Baldurs Gate for an education. From Rehner he learned about the world, pratical skills and some instruments. Rehner did not know alot about magic but did teach Mirfal how to go about learning magic and it turned out Mirfal had a natural knack for it.\n\nRehner liked to form study groups for his most learned students and so when Mirfal was 12 Rehner formed a small group for Mirfal to study in. The group consisted of 6 students. One of which was Ava Anila from a Noble family. Mirfal fell in love with Ava. Mirfal did not get along with his study group but Ava was always very nice to Mirfal, she was nice to everybody. He tried to keep his feeling to himself, waiting to make something of himself before trying to court her. Mirfal waited too long, Ava married a guard named Baf Dheko. Heartbroken, Mirfal left Baldurs Gate at age 20 to live by himself.\n\nDuring Mirfals time in isolation, he studied. Sometimes his sister would visit him and bring supplies. Mirfal only returned to Baldurs Gate once to check up on Ava Dheko while using a disguise from a spell, she was very happy and had 2 children.\n\nAt age 35 Mirfal had enough of his life of seclution and decided to find an adventure. What adventures await him?</notes>
		<perception type="number">13</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I feel tremendous empathy for all who suffer.\nI am utterly serene, even in the face of disaster.</personalitytraits>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">3</prepared>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">Item</name>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">POTIONS</name>
			</id-00003>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">4</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">S, M (a bit of fleece)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create a sound or an image of an object within range that lasts for the duration. The illusion also ends if you dismiss it as an action or cast this spell again.</p>
					<p>If you create a sound, its volume can range from a whisper to a scream. It can be your voice, someone else's voice, a lion's roar, a beating of drums, or any other sound you choose. The sound continues unabated throughout the duration, or you can make discrete sounds at different times before the spell ends.</p>
					<p>If you create an image of an object-such as a chair, muddy footprints, or a small chest-it must be no larger than a 5-foot cube. The image can't create sound, light, smell, or any other sensory effect. Physical interaction with the image reveals it to be an illusion, because things can pass through it.</p>
					<p>If a creature uses its action to examine the sound or image, the creature can determine that it is an illusion with a successful Intelligence (Investigation) check against your spell save DC. If a creature discerns the illusion for what it is, the illusion becomes faint to the creature.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Minor Illusion</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 minute</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (two lodestones)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell repairs a single break or tear in an object you touch, such as a broken chain link, two halves of a broken key, a torn cloak, or a leaking wineskin. As long as the break or tear is no larger than 1 foot in any dimension, you mend it. leaving no trace of the former damage.</p>
					<p>This spell can physically repair a magic item or construct, but the spell can't restore magic to such an object.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mending</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You hurl a mote of fire at a creature or object within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes 1d10 fire damage. A flammable object hit by this spell ignites if it isn't being worn or carried.</p>
					<p>This spell's damage increases by 1d10 when you reach 5th level (2d10), 11th level (3d10), and 17th level (4d10).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fire Bolt</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">8</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">AC: 3</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a piece of cured leather)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a willing creature who isn't wearing armor, and a protective magical force surrounds it until the spell ends. The target's base AC becomes 13 + its Dexterity modifier. The spell ends if the target dons armor or if you dismiss the spell as an action.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mage Armor</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">AC: 5</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 reaction, which you take when you are hit by an attack or targeted by the magic missile spell</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>An invisible barrier of magical force appears and protects you. Until the start of your next turn, you have a +5 bonus to AC, including against the triggering attack, and you take no damage from magic missile.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You make yourself-including your clothing, armor, weapons, and other belongings on your person-look different until the spell ends or until you use your action to dismiss it. You can seem 1 foot shorter or taller and can appear thin, fat, or in between. You can't change your body type, so you must adopt a form that has the same basic arrangement of limbs. Otherwise, the extent of the illusion is up to you.</p>
					<p>The changes wrought by this spell fail to hold up to physical inspection. For example, if you use this spell to add a hat to your outfit, objects pass through the hat, and anyone who touches it would feel nothing or would feel your head and hair. If you use this spell to appear thinner than you are, the hand of someone who reaches out to touch you would bump into you while it was seemingly still in midair.</p>
					<p>To discern that you are disguised, a creature can use its action to inspect your appearance and must succeed on an Intelligence (Investigation) check against your spell save DC.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Disguise Self</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">force</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create three glowing darts of magical force. Each dart hits a creature of your choice that you can see within range. A dart deals 1d4 + 1 force damage to its target. The darts all strike simultaneously, and you can direct them to hit one creature or several.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the spell creates one more dart for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Magic Missile</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 reaction, which you take when you or a creature within 60 feet of you falls</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, M (a small feather or piece of down)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose up to five falling creatures within range. A falling creature's rate of descent slows to 60 feet per round until the spell ends. If the creature lands before the spell ends, it takes no falling damage and can land on its feet, and the spell ends for that creature.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Feather Fall</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>As you hold your hands with thumbs touching and fingers spread, a thin sheet of flames shoots forth from your outstretched fingertips. Each creature in a 15-foot cone must make a Dexterity saving throw. A creature takes 3d6 fire damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.</p>
					<p>The fire ignites any flammable objects in the area that aren't being worn or carried.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Burning Hands</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self (15-foot cone)</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
								<type type="string">acid</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You hurl a bubble of acid. Choose one creature you can see within range, or choose two creatures you can see within range that are within 5 feet of each other. A target must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw or take 1d6 acid damage. This spell's damage increases by 1d6 when you reach 5th level (2d6), 11th level (3d6), and 17th level (4d6).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Acid Splash</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4,d4,d4</dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Item Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00392@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Greater Potion of Healing</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">POTIONS</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Greater Potion of Healing</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Item - Action Code</source>
			</id-00011>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">2</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: Herbalism kit</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Daggers, darts, slings, quarterstaffs, light crossbows</name>
			</id-00002>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Human</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.human@DD PHB PC Customization Pack</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00005_token</token>
		<traitlist>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Quarterstaff</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d8)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00001</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">134 pounds</weight>
	</character>
</root>
