<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:4">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">12</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">4</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">13</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">6</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">17</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">16</age>
		<alignment type="string">Lawful Neutral</alignment>
		<background type="string">Doctor</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>background.id-00009@Incarnate-5eExpansion</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">My professor is the most important person in the world to me.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d8</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">1</hdused>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<name type="string">Druid</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>class.prodruid@Incarnate-5eExpansion</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">0</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d8</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">1</hdused>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<name type="string">Monk</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.monk@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00002>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">2234</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">598</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">348</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">7</armor>
				<dexbonus type="string">no</dexbonus>
				<disstealth type="number">0</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<stat2 type="string">wisdom</stat2>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">20</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<deity type="string">Teenage mutant ninja turtles</deity>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">50</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">100</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">300</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">111.9</load>
			<max type="number">150</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">500</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">500</expneeded>
		<featlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ritual Caster (wizard)</name>
				<prerequisite type="string">Intelligence or Wisdom 13 or higher</prerequisite>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p><i>Prerequisite: Intelligence or Wisdom 13 or higher</i></p>
					<p>You have learned a number of spells that you can cast as rituals. These spells are written in a ritual book, which you must have in hand while casting one of them. When you choose this feat, you acquire a ritual book holding two 1st-level spells of your choice. Choose one of the following classes: bard, cleric, druid, sorcerer, warlock, or wizard. You must choose your spells from that class's spell list, and the spells you choose must have the ritual tag. The class you choose also determines your spellcasting ability for these spells: Charisma for bard, sorcerer, or warlock; Wisdom for cleric or druid; or Intelligence for wizard.</p>
					<p>If you come across a spell in written form, such as a magical spell scroll or a wizard's spellbook, you might be able to add it to your ritual book. The spell must be on the spell list for the class you chose, the spell's level can be no higher than half your level (rounded up), and it must have the ritual tag. The process of copying the spell into your ritual book takes 2 hours per level of the spell, and costs 50 gp per level. The cost represents material components you expend as you experiment with the spell to master it, as well as the fine inks you need to record it.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Doctor - Starting Items</name>
				<source type="string">Doctor</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Parcel</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="treasureparcel" recordname="treasureparcels.id-00037@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Starting Items - Doctor</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Burden of Life</name>
				<source type="string">Doctor</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Due to your vow, you are expected to cure the ill, regardless of morals or prejudice, even if they are your enemy. It is considered a horrid evil to intentionally kill a doctor for no reason. As such, intelligent enemies are less likely to target you, (Provided they are not frighteningly evil in a manner that would be inappropriate for younger audiences) and even your enemy patients will at least not attack immediately while under your care. What happens after they leave your care...? Well you can't decide their fate. Restored individuals may be grateful, or feel some form of life-debt to you. Enemies may repay you by specifically choosing not to kill you, or they may give free information, or a scout you once saved may turn a blind eye to your presence.</p>
					<p>Provided you stay true to your vow, (as best as you can) you can make use of any hospital or medical facility, (typically located in churches, noble estates, universities, and other places of higher learning) as temporary residence for yourself, your patient(s), and your companions if there is room for them. Doctors will put you up at a lifestyle one step below their own if you can maintain a good relationship with them.</p>
					<p>However, if ever you are proven to have broken your vow, you will be fully and publicly discredited as a doctor, and other doctors who pay attention to medical society will recognize you as such. You and all who are with you will be turned away from mundane medicine and the places it is provided. Because you swore on your life, breaking your vow is technically a personal death sentence, though no doctor true to his vows is free to enact it upon you. Even so, more enlightened nations are likely to have laws regarding the treatment of doctors and their vows, and enlightened does not necessarily mean &#34;kind&#34; or &#34;gentle&#34;.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Druid Starting Items</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p><b>Click the shield below to open you choices for druid starting items.</b></p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_weapontable" recordname="lists.startingequipment.druid@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Druid Starting Equipment Options</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Druidic</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You know Druidic, the secret language of druids. You can speak the language and use it to leave hidden messages. You and others who know this language automatically spot such a message. Others spot the message's presence with a successful DC 15 Wisdom (Perception) check but can't decipher it without magic.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Drawing on the divine essence of nature itself, you can cast spells to shape that essence to your will.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="lists.spells.druid@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Druid Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you know two cantrips of your choice from the druid spell list. You learn additional druid cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Druid table.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00038@Incarnate-5eExpansion">The Druid</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Druid table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these druid spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of druid spells that are available for you to cast, choosing from the druid spell list. When you do so, choose a number of druid spells equal to your Wisdom modifier + your druid level (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you are a 3rd-level druid, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With a Wisdom of 16, your list of prepared spells can include six spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination. If you prepare the 1st-level spell <i>cure wounds </i>, you can cast it using a 1st-level or 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can also change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of druid spells requires time spent in prayer and meditation at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Wisdom is your spellcasting ability for your druid spells, since your magic draws upon your devotion and attunement to nature. You use your Wisdom whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Wisdom modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a druid spell you cast and making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<list>
						<li><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</li>
						<li><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</li>
					</list>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast a druid spell as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag and you have the spell prepared.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a druidic focus (see &#34;Equipment&#34;) as a spellcasting focus for your druid spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Circle of the Shepherd</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Druids of the Circle of the Shepherd commune with the spirits of nature, especially the spirits of beasts and the fey, and call to those spirits for aid. These druids recognize that all living things play a role in the natural world, yet they focus on protecting animals and fey creatures that have difficulty defending themselves.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="imagewindow" recordname="reference.imagedata.img_shepherddruid_jpg@*"><b>Image: </b></link>Druid of the Circle of the Shepherd</linklist>
					<p>Shepherds, as they are known, see such creatures as their charges. They ward off monsters that threaten them, rebuke hunters who kill more prey than necessary, and prevent civilization from encroaching on rare animal habitats and on sites sacred to the fey. Many of these druids are happiest far from cities and towns, content to spend their days in the company of animals and the fey creatures of the wilds.</p>
					<p>Members of this circle become adventurers to oppose forces that threaten their charges or to seek knowledge and power that will help them safeguard their charges better. Wherever these druids go, the spirits of the wilderness are with them.</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.druid.features.speechofthewoods2@*">Speech of the Woods</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.druid.features.spirittotem2@*">Spirit Totem</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.druid.features.mightysummoner6@*">Mighty Summoner</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.druid.features.guardianspirit10@*">Guardian Spirit</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.druid.features.faithfulsummons14@*">Faithful Summons</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wild Shape</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Common Transformations</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.p98wildshape_polymorphcheatsheet@Incarnate-5eExpansion">98 Wildshape/Polymorph</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Main Description</h>
					<p>Starting at 2nd Level, you can use your action to magically assume the shape of a beast that you have seen before. You can use this feature twice. You regain expended uses when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>Your druid level determines the beasts you can transform into as shown in the Beast Shapes table. At 2nd level, for example, you can transform into any beast that has a challenge rating of 1/4 or lower that doesn't have a flying or swimming speed.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td colspan="6"><b>Beast Shapes</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td></td>
							<td><b>Max.</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Level</b></td>
							<td><b>CR</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"><b>Limitations</b></td>
							<td><b>Example</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2nd</td>
							<td>1/4</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying or swimming speed</td>
							<td>Wolf</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4th</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying speed</td>
							<td>Crocodile</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8th</td>
							<td><b>1</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td>Giant eagle</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>You can stay in a beast shape for a number of hours equal to half your druid level (rounded down). You then revert to your normal form unless you expend another use of this feature. You can revert to your normal form earlier by using a bonus action on your turn. You automatically revert if you fall unconscious, drop to 9 hit points, or die.</p>
					<p>While you are transformed the following rules apply:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Your game statistics are replaced by the statistics of the beast, but you retain your alignment, personality, and Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma scores. You also retain all of your skill and saving throw proficiencies, in addition to gaining those of the creature. If the creature has the same proficiency as you and the bonus in its stat block is higher than yours, use the creature's bonus instead of yours. If the creature has any legendary or lair actions, you can't use them.</li>
						<li>When you transform, you assume the beast's hit points and Hit Dice. When you revert to your normal form, you return to the number of hit points you had before you transformed. However if you revert as a result of dropping to 0 hit points, any excess damage carries over to your normal form. For example, if you take 10 damage in animal form and only have 1 hit point left, you revert and take 9 damage. As long as the excess damage doesn't reduce your normal form to 0 hit points, you aren't knocked unconscious.</li>
						<li>You can't cast spells, and your ability to speak or take any action that requires hands is limited to the capabilities f your beast form. Transforming doesn't break your concentration on a spell you've already cast, however, or prevent you from taking actions that are part of a spell, such as <i>call lightning </i>, that you've already cast.</li>
						<li>You retain the benefit of any features from your class, race, or other source and can use them if the new form is physically capable of doing so. However, you can't use any of your special senses, such as darkvision, unless your new form also has that sense.</li>
						<li>You choose whether your equipment falls to the ground in your space, merges into your new form or is worn by it. Worn equipment functions as normal, but the GM decides if it is practical for the new form to ear a piece of equipment based on the creature's shape and size. Your equipment doesn't change size or shape to match the new form and any equipment that the new form can't wear must either fall to the ground or merge with it. Equipment that merges with the form has no effect until you leave the form.</li>
					</list>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spirit Totem</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of the Shepherd</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can call forth nature spirits to influence the world around you. As a bonus action, you can magically summon an incorporeal spirit to a point you can see within 60 feet of you. The spirit creates an aura in a 30-foot radius around that point. It counts as neither a creature nor an object, though it has the spectral appearance of the creature it represents.</p>
					<p>As a bonus action, you can move the spirit up to 60 feet to a point you can see.</p>
					<p>The spirit persists for 1 minute or until you're incapacitated. Once you use this feature, you can't use it again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>The effect of the spirit's aura depends on the type of spirit you summon from the options below.</p>
					<p><b><i>Bear Spirit. </i></b>The bear spirit grants you and your allies its might and endurance. Each creature of your choice in the aura when the spirit appears gains temporary hit points equal to 5 + your druid level. In addition, you and your allies gain advantage on Strength checks and Strength saving throws while in the aura.</p>
					<p><b><i>Hawk Spirit. </i></b>The hawk spirit is a consummate hunter, aiding you and your allies with its keen sight. When a creature makes an attack roll against a target in the spirit's aura, you can use your reaction to grant advantage to that attack roll. In addition, you and your allies have advantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks while in the aura.</p>
					<p><b><i>Unicorn Spirit. </i></b>The unicorn spirit lends its protection to those nearby. You and your allies gain advantage on all ability checks made to detect creatures in the spirit's aura. In addition, if you cast a spell using a spell slot that restores hit points to any creature inside or outside the aura, each creature of your choice in the aura also regains hit points equal to your druid level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Speech of the Woods</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of the Shepherd</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you gain the ability to converse with beasts and many fey.</p>
					<p>You learn to speak, read, and write Sylvan. In addition, beasts can understand your speech, and you gain the ability to decipher their noises and motions. Most beasts lack the intelligence to convey or understand sophisticated concepts, but a friendly beast could relay what it has seen or heard in the recent past. This ability doesn't grant you friendship with beasts, though you can combine this ability with gifts to curry favor with them as you would with any nonplayer character.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Martial Arts</name>
				<source type="string">Monk</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 1st level, your practice of martial arts gives you mastery of combat styles that use unarmed strikes and monk weapons, which are shortswords and any simple melee weapons that don't have the two handed or heavy property.</p>
					<p>You gain the following benefits while you are unarmed or wielding only monk weapons and you aren't wearing armor or wielding a shield:</p>
					<list>
						<li>You can use Dexterity instead of Strength for the attack and damage rolls of your unarmed strikes and monk weapons.</li>
						<li>You can roll a d4 in place of the normal damage of your unarmed strike or monk weapon. This die changes as you gain monk levels, as shown in the Martial Arts column of the Monk table.</li>
					</list>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00040@Incarnate-5eExpansion">The Monk</link>
					</linklist>
					<list>
						<li>When you use the Attack action with an unarmed strike or a monk weapon on your turn, you can make one unarmed strike as a bonus action. For example, if you take the Attack action and attack with a quarterstaff, you can also make an unarmed strike as a bonus action, assuming you haven't already taken a bonus action this turn.</li>
					</list>
					<h>Item Code</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00030@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Unarmed Strike (Monk)</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>Certain monasteries use specialized forms of the monk weapons. For example, you might use a club that is two lengths of wood connected by a short chain (called a nunchaku) or a sickle with a shorter straighter blade (called a kama). Whatever name you use for a monk weapon, you can use the game statistics provided for the weapon.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Monk Starting Items</name>
				<source type="string">Monk</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p><b>Click the shield below to open you choices for monk starting items.</b></p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_weapontable" recordname="lists.startingequipment.monk@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Monk Starting Equipment Options</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Unarmored Defense</name>
				<source type="string">Monk</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning at 1st level, while you are wearing no armor and not wielding a shield, your AC equals 10 + your Dexterity modifier + your Wisdom modifier.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00013>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I took the vow not realizing its full implications.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">6 feet</height>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">33</total>
			<wounds type="number">2</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Honor - I swore my oath, and now I must live by its tenets. We are all in this together, for better or for worse. Everyone deserves to live. (Neutral)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">0</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tin box contains a cup and simple cutlery. The box clamps together, and one side can be used as a cooking pan and the other as a plate or shallow bowl.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mess Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Equipment Kits</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">7</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">20 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Skill Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_skill" recordname="skill.id-00006@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Doctor's Tools</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>A stethoscope, some splints, a bone saw, and a magnifying glass.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Doctor's Tools</name>
				<rarity type="string">Very Rare</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Artisan's Tool</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 slashing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Scimitar</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Scimitar</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A sharp scimitar.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield (Wooden)</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Shield</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A well crafted shield.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">common</rarity>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Shield</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A druidic focus might be a sprig of mistletoe or holly, a wand or scepter made of yew or another special wood, a staff drawn whole out of a living tree, or a totem object incorporating feathers, fur, bones, and teeth from sacred animals. A druid can use such an object as a spellcasting focus.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Yew Wand</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Wand</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A magical wand.</nonidentified>
				<subtype type="string">Druidic Focus</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">7</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 piercing,radiant</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shortsword</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Shortsword</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">For when you want something longer than a dagger but shorter than a longsword, the shortsword is for you.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">3 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">5</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Even in a culture with many people who smell most strongly, there is some use for soap. Some people even believe that it can help prevent disease!</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bar of Soap</name>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Blanket</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This is a medical book that has specialized in one field:</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="table" recordname="tables.id-01881@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Medical Book - Field</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Book, Medical</name>
				<rarity type="string">Very Rare</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tiny leather pouch is perfect for keeping your coins close at hand. Just watch out for someone trying to cut it off of your belt.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Coin Pouch - Small</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">3 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A small cloth tent that when pitched can fit 2 men.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tent, 2-man</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">900 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A figurine of wondrous power is a statuette of a beast small enough to fit in a pocket. If you use an action to speak the command word and throw the figurine to a point on the ground within 60 feet of you, the figurine becomes a living creature. If the space where the creature would appear is occupied by other creatures or objects, or if there isn't enough space for the creature, the figurine doesn't become a creature.</p>
					<p>The creature is friendly to you and your companions. It understands your languages and obeys your spoken commands. If you issue no commands, the creature defends itself but takes no other actions.</p>
					<p>The creature exists for a duration specific to each figurine. At the end of the duration, the creature reverts to its figurine form. It reverts to a figurine early if it drops to 0 hit points or if you use an action to speak the command word again while touching it.</p>
					<p>When the creature becomes a figurine again, its property can't be used again until a certain amount of time has passed, as specified in the figurine's description.</p>
					<p><b>Golden Lions (Rare) </b>. These gold statuettes of lions are always created in pairs. You can use one figurine or both simultaneously. Each can become a lion for up to 1 hour. Once a lion has been used, it can't be used again until 7 days have passed.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">0</locked>
				<name type="string">Figurine of Wondrous Power (Golden Lions)</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Golden Lions</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Two lions forged from gold. They may not be large, but they are beautiful.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Rare</rarity>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">1,800 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>While wearing this ring, you have resistance to cold damage. In addition, you and everything you wear and carry are unharmed by temperatures as low as -50 degrees Fahrenheit.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.typeresistancecold@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Type Resistance (Cold)</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ring of Warmth</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Ring</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A ruby ring.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">rare (requires attunement)</rarity>
				<type type="string">Ring</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">38 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">3</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You regain 2d4 + 2 hit points when you drink this potion. The potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Potion of Healing</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Potion</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A vial of red liquid that shimmers when agitated.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Magic</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<spells>
					<id-00001>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class></class>
							<recordname></recordname>
						</link>
						<name type="string">Potion of Healing</name>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class></class>
							<recordname></recordname>
						</link>
						<name type="string">Potion</name>
					</id-00002>
				</spells>
				<type type="string">Potion</type>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">300 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The wand has 3 charges. While holding it, you can use an action to expend 1 of its charges, and if a secret door or trap is within 30 feet of you, the wand pulses and points at the one nearest to you. The wand regains 1d3 expended charges daily at dawn.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wand of Secrets</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Wand</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A magical wand.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Wand</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">100 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This concoction looks, smells, and tastes like a potion of healing or other beneficial potion. However, it is actually poison masked by illusion magic. An identify spell reveals its true nature.</p>
					<p>If you drink it, you take 3d6 poison damage, and you must succeed on a DC 13 Constitution saving throw or be poisoned. At the start of each of your turns while you are poisoned in this way, you take 3d6 poison damage. At the end of each of your turns, you can repeat the saving throw. On a successful save, the poison damage you take on your subsequent turns decreases by 1d6. The poison ends when the damage decreases to 0.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Potion of Poison</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Dim Potion</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">The potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Potion</type>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Consuming this removes the poisoned condition.</p>
				</description>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bottle of Antivenom</name>
				<subtype type="string">Alchemy</subtype>
				<type type="string">Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00025>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">50 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Essential for wizards, a spellbook is a leather-bound tome with 100 blank vellum pages suitable for recording spells.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellbook</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00025>
			<id-00026>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">5</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This glass bottle contains a large spider suspended in amber liquid.</p>
					<p>Upon drinking the Spider Wine, roll a DC 15 Constitution saving throw. On a success you are granted resistance to poison for 1 hour. On an 7 or lower, you are poisoned for 1 hour.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spider Wine</name>
				<rarity type="string">Rare (Contraband)</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Alcohol</subtype>
				<type type="string">Sustance</type>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00026>
			<id-00027>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">50 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">20</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This poison must be harvested from a dead or incapacitated poisonous spider. A creature subjected to this poison must succeed on a DC 18 Constitution saving throw, taking 12 (2d8) poison damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spider Venom (Injury)</name>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Poisons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00027>
			<id-00028>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">6</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="combattracker.list.id-00016">Bone Spider Queen</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bone Spider Queen Fang</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00028>
			<id-00029>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.id-00004@HoHF (5e) - Creaking In The Dark">Bone Spider</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bone spider Egg</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Bone Spider Egg</nonid_name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00029>
			<id-00030>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2000 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 slashing, silver, magic</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
					<p><b>Silver Weapon Notes</b></p>
					<p>There are creatures that lurk in the night. These strange creatures are said to be able to change shape. It is also said that they are resistant to most damage. The best way to cut through their pelts is with silver, but the silver must be carefully applied by a master smith so that the weapon stays sharp.</p>
					<p><b>Electrified Notes</b></p>
					<h>Action Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.electrified@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Electrified</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>You can use a bonus action to speak this magic weapon's command word, causing its runes to sparkle with yellow light. The sparkling casts dim light for 15 feet.</p>
					<p>While the runes are sparkling, it deals an extra 1d6 lightning damage to any target it hits. The target cannot take any reactions until the beginning of your next turn. The sparkling last until you use a bonus action to speak the command word again or until you drop or sheathe the weapon.</p>
					<p><b>Flame Tongue Notes</b></p>
					<h>Action Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.flametongue@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Flame Tongue</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>You can use a bonus action to speak this magic weapon's command word, causing flames to erupt from the blade. These flames shed bright light in a 40--foot radius and dim light for an additional 40 feet.</p>
					<p>While the weapon is ablaze, it deals an extra 2d6 fire damage to any target it hits. The flames last until you use a bonus action to speak the command word again or until you drop or sheathe the weapon.</p>
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Silver Scimitar [Electrified] [Flame Tongue]</name>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light</properties>
				<rarity type="string">rare (requires attunement)</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00030>
			<id-00031>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">150 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Linked Spell</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.magiccircle@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Magic Circle</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>A spell scroll bears the words of a single spell, written in a mystical cipher. If the spell is on your class's spell list, you can read the scroll and cast its spell without providing any material components.</p>
					<p>Otherwise, the scroll is unintelligible. Casting the spell by reading the scroll requires the spell's normal casting time. Once the spell is cast, the words on the scroll fade, and it crumbles to dust. If the casting is interrupted, the scroll is not lost.</p>
					<p>If the spell is on your class's spell list but of a higher level than you can normally cast, you must make an ability check using your spellcasting ability to determine whether you cast it successfully. The DC equals 10 + the spell's level. On a failed check, the spell disappears from the scroll with no other effect.</p>
					<p>The level of the spell on the scroll determines the spell's saving throw DC and attack bonus, as well as the scroll's rarity, as shown in the Spell Scroll table.</p>
					<p>Spell Scroll</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Spell Level</td>
							<td>Rarity</td>
							<td>Save DC</td>
							<td>Attack Bonus</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>3rd</td>
							<td>Uncommon</td>
							<td>15</td>
							<td>+7</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>A wizard spell on a spell scroll can be copied just as spells in spellbooks can be copied. When a spell is copied from a spell scroll, the copier must succeed on an Intelligence (Arcana) check with a DC equal to 10 + the spell's level. If the check succeeds, the spell is successfully copied. Whether the check succeeds or fails, the spell scroll is destroyed.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Scroll of Magic Circle</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Scroll</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Scroll</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Scroll</type>
				<weight type="number">0.3</weight>
			</id-00031>
			<id-00032>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">300 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Found in a small packet, this powder resembles very fine sand. There is enough of it for one use. When you use an action to throw the dust into the air, you and each creature and object within 10 feet of you become invisible for 2d4 minutes. The duration is the same for all subjects, and the dust is consumed when its magic takes effect. If a creature affected by the dust attacks or casts a spell, the invisibility ends for that creature.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dust of Disappearance</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Bag of Dust</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">-</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00032>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Elvish</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Aquan</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Druidic</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<name type="string">Sylvan</name>
			</id-00005>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">5</level>
		<name type="string">Shi-f&#250;</name>
		<perception type="number">16</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">All I think about is saving lives, or lives that have been lost.I am cold and calculating in my every word and action, even when furious or frightened.</personalitytraits>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">4</prepared>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Effect</name>
			</id-00002>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">4</max>
				<used type="number">3</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">2</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">standard</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Flaming Sphere; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a bit of tallow, a pinch of brimstone, and a dusting of powdered iron)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A 5-foot-diameter sphere of fire appears in an unoccupied space of your choice within range and lasts for the duration. Any creature that ends its turn within 5 feet of the sphere must make a Dexterity saving throw. The creature takes 2d6 fire damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. As a bonus action, you can move the sphere up to 30 feet. If you ram the sphere into a creature, that creature must make the saving throw against the sphere's damage, and the sphere stops moving this turn. When you move the sphere, you can direct it over barriers up to 5 feet tall and jump it across pits up to 10 feet wide. The sphere ignites flammable objects not being worn or carried, and it sheds bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Flaming Sphere</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Wizard</source>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">day</durunit>
						<label type="string">RESIST: cold</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Type Resistance (Cold)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">5e Rule Coding</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A flickering flame appears in your hand. The flame remains there for the duration and harms neither you nor your equipment. The flame sheds bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet. The spell ends if you dismiss it as an action or if you cast it again. You can also attack with the flame, although doing so ends the spell. When you cast this spell, or as an action on a later turn, you can hurl the flame at a creature within 30 feet of you. Make a ranged spell attack. On a hit, the target takes 1d8 fire damage. This spell's damage increases by 1d8 when you reach 5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Produce Flame</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Shillelagh; ATK: [-STR], melee; ATK: [WIS], melee; DMG: [-STR], melee; DMG: [WIS], melee; DMGTYPE: magic</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (mistletoe, a shamrock leaf, and a club or quarterstaff)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The wood of a club or quarterstaff you are holding is imbued with nature's power. For the duration, you can use your spellcasting ability instead of Strength for the attack and damage rolls of melee attacks using that weapon, and the weapon's damage die becomes a d8. The weapon also becomes magical, if it isn't already. The spell ends if you cast it again or if you let go of the weapon.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shillelagh</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch regains a number of hit points equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cure Wounds</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Faerie Fire; GRANTADVATK; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Each object in a 20-foot cube within range is outlined in blue, green, or violet light (your choice). Any creature in the area when the spell is cast is also outlined in light if it fails a Dexterity saving throw. For the duration, objects and affected creatures shed dim light in a 10-foot radius. Any attack roll against an affected creature or object has advantage if the attacker can see it, and the affected creature or object can't benefit from being invisible.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Faerie Fire</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature of your choice that you can see within range regains hit points equal to 1d4 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d4 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Healing Word</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">thunder</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A wave of thunderous force sweeps out from you. Each creature in a 15-foot cube originating from you must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, a creature takes 2d8 thunder damage and is pushed 10 feet away from you. On a successful save, the creature takes half as much damage and isn't pushed. In addition, unsecured objects that are completely within the area of effect are automatically pushed 10 feet away from you by the spell's effect, and the spell emits a thunderous boom audible out to 300 feet.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Thunderwave</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self (15-foot cube)</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Detect Magic; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Sound</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="url" recordname="syrinscape-fantasy:elements/ZXpyZW4tbWFsZS13aXphcmQ6OmRldGVjdC1tYWdpYy1h/play/"><b>Syrinscape </b></link>: Detect Magic - Wizard Spells E</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any. The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Magic</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">STR: [-2STR]; STR: 3; DEX: [-2DEX]; DEX: 0; CON: [-2CON]; CON: 5; AC: -1</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.giantbadger@Incarnate-5eBattles">Giant Badger</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Transformation - Giant Badger</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Polymorph Code</source>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can withdraw into your shell as an action. Until you emerge, you gain a +4 bonus to AC, and you have advantage on Strength and Constitution saving throws. While in your shell, you are prone, your speed is 0 and can't increase, you have disadvantage on Dexterity saving throws, you can't take reactions, and the only action you can take is a bonus action to emerge from your shell.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shell Defense</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Tortle</source>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">5</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">druid</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">druid</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Spirit Totem</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can call forth nature spirits to influence the world around you. As a bonus action, you can magically summon an incorporeal spirit to a point you can see within 60 feet of you. The spirit creates an aura in a 30-foot radius around that point. It counts as neither a creature nor an object, though it has the spectral appearance of the creature it represents.</p>
					<p>As a bonus action, you can move the spirit up to 60 feet to a point you can see.</p>
					<p>The spirit persists for 1 minute or until you're incapacitated. Once you use this feature, you can't use it again until you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>The effect of the spirit's aura depends on the type of spirit you summon from the options below.</p>
					<p><b><i>Bear Spirit. </i></b>The bear spirit grants you and your allies its might and endurance. Each creature of your choice in the aura when the spirit appears gains temporary hit points equal to 5 + your druid level. In addition, you and your allies gain advantage on Strength checks and Strength saving throws while in the aura.</p>
					<p><b><i>Hawk Spirit. </i></b>The hawk spirit is a consummate hunter, aiding you and your allies with its keen sight. When a creature makes an attack roll against a target in the spirit's aura, you can use your reaction to grant advantage to that attack roll. In addition, you and your allies have advantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks while in the aura.</p>
					<p><b><i>Unicorn Spirit. </i></b>The unicorn spirit lends its protection to those nearby. You and your allies gain advantage on all ability checks made to detect creatures in the spirit's aura. In addition, if you cast a spell using a spell slot that restores hit points to any creature inside or outside the aura, each creature of your choice in the aura also regains hit points equal to your druid level.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spirit Totem</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of the Shepherd</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00017>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">3</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: Doctor's Tools</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Clubs, daggers, darts, javelins, maces, quarterstaffs, scimitars, sickles, slings, spears</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Tool: Herbalism kit</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Armor: light armor, medium armor, shields (druids will not wear armor or use shields made of metal)</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple weapons, shortswords</name>
			</id-00005>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Tortle</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.tortle@The Tortle Package - Player</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Doctor's Tools</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Item Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00336@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Doctor's Tools</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Herbalism Kit</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Item Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00259@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Herbalism Kit</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>This kit contains a variety of instruments such as clippers, mortar and pestle, and pouches and vials used by herbalists to create remedies and potions. Proficiency with this kit lets you add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make to identify or apply herbs. Also, proficiency with this kit is required to create antitoxin and potions of healing .</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00061@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Rules for Using Herbalism Kit</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00020>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00001_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hold Breath</name>
				<source type="string">Tortle</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can hold your breath for up to 1 hour at a time. Tortles aren't natural swimmers, but they can remain underwater for some time before needing to come up for air.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Survival Instinct</name>
				<source type="string">Tortle</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain proficiency in the Survival skill. Tortles have finely honed survival instincts.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Natural Armor</name>
				<source type="string">Tortle</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Due to your shell and the shape of your body, you are ill-suited to wearing armor. Your shell provides ample protection, however; it gives you a base AC of 17 (your Dexterity modifier doesn't affect this number). You gain no benefit from wearing armor, but if you are using a shield, you can apply the shield's bonus as normal.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Claws</name>
				<source type="string">Tortle</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your claws are natural weapons, which you can use to make unarmed strikes. If you hit with them, you deal slashing damage equal to 1d4 + your Strength modifier, instead of the bludgeoning damage normal for an unarmed strike.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shell Defense</name>
				<source type="string">Tortle</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can withdraw into your shell as an action. Until you emerge, you gain a +4 bonus to AC, and you have advantage on Strength and Constitution saving throws. While in your shell, you are prone, your speed is 0 and can't increase, you have disadvantage on Dexterity saving throws, you can't take reactions, and the only action you can take is a bonus action to emerge from your shell.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00005>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">slashing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Scimitar</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00009</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00004>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
						<type type="string">slashing,silver,magic</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
						<type type="string">lightning</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
						<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
						<type type="string">fire</type>
					</id-00003>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Silver Scimitar [Electrified] [Flame Tongue]</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00030</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00004>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">460</weight>
	</character>
</root>
