<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:4">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">13</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">4</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">12</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">-1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">8</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
				<save type="number">7</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">18</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">1</age>
		<alignment type="string">Chaotic Good</alignment>
		<appearance type="string">You look where you heard the voice... seeing nothing you start to look around. &#34;Down here you giant.&#34; As you turn back to the voice and look down you see an unassuming 6&#34; brown mouse that seems to be wearing a belt with some spikes and a little backpack.</appearance>
		<background type="string">Chef</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>background.id-00006@Incarnate-5eExpansion</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">I am putting together a book of recipes from around the world!</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d8</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">6</level>
				<name type="string">Druid</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>class.prodruid@Incarnate-5eExpansion</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">143</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">28</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">EP</name>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">23</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">0</armor>
				<misc type="number">2</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">15</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<deity type="string">Eternal</deity>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">20</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">40</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">120</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">5.58</load>
			<max type="number">60</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">628</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">700</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Chef - Starting Items</name>
				<source type="string">Chef</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Parcel</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="treasureparcel" recordname="treasureparcels.id-00030@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Starting Items - Chef</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">A Tasteful Sentiment</name>
				<source type="string">Chef</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can use food to communicate more than just good flavor; you can produce intellectually meaningful dishes which can send a message, however simple and abstract. At the GM's discretion, (Preferably based on how the player describes what they do to send a message) you may make persuasion, deception, and even intimidation attempts by simply feeding a person a meal, or by preparing it in front of them. You may also treat public preparation of food as a performance.</p>
					<p>(For example, in an attempt to persuade a peace between two nations, you may prepare a dish which incorporates both cultures' cuisines in a creative and enjoyable way and then serve it to the negotiation delegates.)</p>
					<p>(An example of an intimidating meal would be one designed to appear poisonous; made from the target's fallen allies; or decorated with unpleasant symbolism, like a union jack cake served to a colonial American minuteman.)</p>
					<p>(Examples of food preparation as a performance would include juggling/tossing of ingredients, fancy knife work, preparation of flambe, and other visually entertaining techniques)</p>
					<p>(To the GM: Generally, this means that they should be allowed to add their tool proficiency to the check, even if they lack the typical skill proficiency, but it's really up to you whether it counts and when. The whole intent of this feature is for you and the player to work together to incorporate their background into play by rewarding its creative application, not to give the player four skill proficiencies for all situations, or to give you a method of wiping out the value of their roleplaying feature. Don't be a pushover OR a jerk about it.)</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Druidic</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You know Druidic, the secret language of druids. You can speak the language and use it to leave hidden messages. You and others who know this language automatically spot such a message. Others spot the message's presence with a successful DC 15 Wisdom (Perception) check but can't decipher it without magic.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Drawing on the divine essence of nature itself, you can cast spells to shape that essence to your will.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="lists.spells.druid@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Druid Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you know two cantrips of your choice from the druid spell list. You learn additional druid cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Druid table.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00038@Incarnate-5eExpansion">The Druid</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Druid table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these druid spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of druid spells that are available for you to cast, choosing from the druid spell list. When you do so, choose a number of druid spells equal to your Wisdom modifier + your druid level (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you are a 3rd-level druid, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With a Wisdom of 16, your list of prepared spells can include six spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination. If you prepare the 1st-level spell <i>cure wounds </i>, you can cast it using a 1st-level or 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can also change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of druid spells requires time spent in prayer and meditation at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Wisdom is your spellcasting ability for your druid spells, since your magic draws upon your devotion and attunement to nature. You use your Wisdom whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Wisdom modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a druid spell you cast and making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<list>
						<li><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</li>
						<li><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</li>
					</list>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast a druid spell as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag and you have the spell prepared.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a druidic focus (see &#34;Equipment&#34;) as a spellcasting focus for your druid spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Circle of Transformation</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>This circle has specialized and perfected their wild shapes. They have mastered these transformations in ways that others cannot even begin to dream of.</p>
					<h>Abilities</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00019@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Level 2: Larger Transformation</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00020@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Level 6: Partial Transformation</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00016@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Level 6: Larger Transformation (CR 1)</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00021@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Level 10: Extra Limbs</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00018@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Level 10: Larger Transformation (CR 2)</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00022@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Level 14: Monstrous Transformation</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00017@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Level 14: Larger Transformation (CR 3)</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">6</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Partial Transformation</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of Transformation</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Through intense training you have become able to transform part of your body independently of the rest. Of the six zones of your body (head, two arms, two legs, and torso) you may transform up to 1 + Wisdom Modifier zones. This counts as a wild shape transformation. You may only transform zones into animals that you are allowed to transform into for wild shape.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.prodruid.features.id-00040@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Wild Shape</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>Benefits of transformation:</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Creature</td>
							<td>CR</td>
							<td>Head</td>
							<td>Arm</td>
							<td>Leg</td>
							<td>Torso</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Ape</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
							<td>WIS: 12</td>
							<td>Climb Speed of 30ft. (requires both arms)</td>
							<td>Walking speed of 30 ft. (requires both legs)</td>
							<td>5 temporary hit points</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Black Bear</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
							<td>Bite; Melee Weapon Attack: reach 5 ft., one target. Hit: 1d6 + STR piercing damage.</td>
							<td>Claws; Melee Weapon Attack: reach 5 ft. Hit: 2d4 + STR.</td>
							<td>Walking speed of 40 ft. (requires both legs and both arms and torso)</td>
							<td>5 temporary hit points</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Crocodile</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
							<td>Hold Breath: You can hold your breath for 15 minutes.</td>
							<td></td>
							<td></td>
							<td>swim speed of 30 ft. (requires torso and head)</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Giant Goat</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
							<td>Ram; reach 5 ft. 2d4 + STR bludgeoning damage</td>
							<td>Nimble: GRANTDISATK (requires both legs and both arms)</td>
							<td>Sure-Footed: You have advantage on Strength and Dexterity saving throws made against effects that would knock it prone. (requires both legs)</td>
							<td></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Giant Mosquito</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
							<td>Mosquito Bite; range 5 ft. 1d10 piercing damage</td>
							<td>20 ft. flying (requires both arms)</td>
							<td></td>
							<td></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Warhorse</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
							<td></td>
							<td></td>
							<td>Walking speed 60 ft. (requires both legs and both arms and torso)</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Brown Bear</td>
							<td>1</td>
							<td>Keen Smell: You have advantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks that rely on smell.</td>
							<td>Claws; Melee Weapon Attack: reach 5 ft. Hit: 2d6 + STR.</td>
							<td>Walking speed of 40 ft. (requires both legs and both arms and torso)</td>
							<td>10 temporary hit points</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Dire Wolf</td>
							<td>1</td>
							<td>Pack tactics: You have advantage on attack rolls against a creature if at least one of your allies is within 5 feet of the creature and the ally isn't incapacitated.</td>
							<td>Walking speed of 50 ft. (requires both legs and both arms and torso)</td>
							<td>Walking speed of 35 ft. (requires both legs)</td>
							<td>8 temporary hit points.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Giant Eagle</td>
							<td>1</td>
							<td>Keen Sight: The eagle has advantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks that rely on sight.</td>
							<td>Fly speed 80 ft. Requires both arms.</td>
							<td>Claws; Melee Weapon Attack: reach 5ft., 2d6 + STR</td>
							<td></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Giant Octopus</td>
							<td>1</td>
							<td>Water Breathing: You may breath underwater</td>
							<td>Tentacles: Melee Weapon Attack: reach 15ft., one target. 2d6 + STR. If target is a creature then it is grappled (escape DC 16).</td>
							<td>Swim speed 60. (requires both arms, both legs, and torso).</td>
							<td>Inc Cloud: a 20 foot radius cloud of ink extends all around the octopus if it is underwater. The area is heavily obscured for 1 minute, although a significant current can disperse the ink. After releasing the ink the octopus can use the Dash action as a bonus action. (recharges after a short or long rest)</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Giant Toad</td>
							<td>1</td>
							<td>Amphibious: You may breath both air and water.</td>
							<td></td>
							<td>Standing Leap: Your long jump is up to 20 feet and your high jump is up to 10 feet. (requires both legs)</td>
							<td>Wet skin; RESIST: Fire</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Tiger</td>
							<td>1</td>
							<td>Darkvision 60 ft.</td>
							<td></td>
							<td>Walking speed of 40 ft. (requires both legs and both arms and torso)</td>
							<td>8 temporary hit points</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Cave Bear</td>
							<td>2</td>
							<td>Keen Smell: You have advantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks that rely on smell.</td>
							<td>Claws; Melee Weapon Attack: reach 5 ft. Hit: 2d6 + STR.</td>
							<td>Walking speed of 40 ft. (requires both legs and both arms and torso)</td>
							<td>Sets your temporary hit points to 10 at each initiative roll.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Giant Constrictor Snake</td>
							<td>2</td>
							<td>blindsight 10 ft.</td>
							<td></td>
							<td></td>
							<td>Constrict: Melee Weapon attack: reach 5 ft., one creature (2d8 + STR) bludgeoning damage, and the target is grappled (escape DC 13 + STR). Until the grapple ends, the creature is restrained, and the snake can't constrict another target.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Rhinoceros</td>
							<td>2</td>
							<td></td>
							<td></td>
							<td></td>
							<td>Leathery skin: RESIST: slashing; RESIST: bludgeoning; VULN: piercing</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">0</locked>
				<name type="string">Wild Shape</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Common Transformations</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.p98wildshape_polymorphcheatsheet@Incarnate-5eExpansion">98 Wildshape/Polymorph</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Main Description</h>
					<p>Starting at 2nd Level, you can use your action to magically assume the shape of a beast that you have seen before. You can use this feature twice. You regain expended uses when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>Your druid level determines the beasts you can transform into as shown in the Beast Shapes table. At 2nd level, for example, you can transform into any beast that has a challenge rating of 1/4 or lower that doesn't have a flying or swimming speed.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td colspan="6"><b>Beast Shapes</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td></td>
							<td><b>Max.</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Level</b></td>
							<td><b>CR</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"><b>Limitations</b></td>
							<td><b>Example</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2nd</td>
							<td>1/4</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying or swimming speed</td>
							<td>Wolf</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4th</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying speed</td>
							<td>Crocodile</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8th</td>
							<td><b>1</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td>Giant eagle</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>You can stay in a beast shape for a number of hours equal to half your druid level (rounded down). You then revert to your normal form unless you expend another use of this feature. You can revert to your normal form earlier by using a bonus action on your turn. You automatically revert if you fall unconscious, drop to 9 hit points, or die.</p>
					<p>While you are transformed the following rules apply:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Your game statistics are replaced by the statistics of the beast, but you retain your alignment, personality, and Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma scores. You also retain all of your skill and saving throw proficiencies, in addition to gaining those of the creature. If the creature has the same proficiency as you and the bonus in its stat block is higher than yours, use the creature's bonus instead of yours. If the creature has any legendary or lair actions, you can't use them.</li>
						<li>When you transform, you assume the beast's hit points and Hit Dice. When you revert to your normal form, you return to the number of hit points you had before you transformed. However if you revert as a result of dropping to 0 hit points, any excess damage carries over to your normal form. For example, if you take 10 damage in animal form and only have 1 hit point left, you revert and take 9 damage. As long as the excess damage doesn't reduce your normal form to 0 hit points, you aren't knocked unconscious.</li>
						<li>You can't cast spells, and your ability to speak or take any action that requires hands is limited to the capabilities f your beast form. Transforming doesn't break your concentration on a spell you've already cast, however, or prevent you from taking actions that are part of a spell, such as <i>call lightning </i>, that you've already cast.</li>
						<li>You retain the benefit of any features from your class, race, or other source and can use them if the new form is physically capable of doing so. However, you can't use any of your special senses, such as darkvision, unless your new form also has that sense.</li>
						<li>You choose whether your equipment falls to the ground in your space, merges into your new form or is worn by it. Worn equipment functions as normal, but the GM decides if it is practical for the new form to ear a piece of equipment based on the creature's shape and size. Your equipment doesn't change size or shape to match the new form and any equipment that the new form can't wear must either fall to the ground or merge with it. Equipment that merges with the form has no effect until you leave the form.</li>
					</list>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement - 2 to wisdom</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">6</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Larger Transformation (CR 1)</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of Transformation</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Those in the circle of transformation can transform into large and more powerful beasts according to the following table:</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Level</td>
							<td>Max CR</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>6th</td>
							<td>1</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Larger Transformation</name>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specialization type="string">Circle of Transformation</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Those in the circle of transformation can transform into large and more powerful beasts according to the following table:</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Level</td>
							<td>Max CR</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2nd</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4th</td>
							<td>1</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8th</td>
							<td>2</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>12th</td>
							<td>3</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</text>
			</id-00010>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">My people believe that Lawful Good is the only way to exist honorably. If they ever discover that I am chaotic, they will hunt me down and drag me back to my warren to &#34;re-educate&#34; me.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">6&#34;</height>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">2</temporary>
			<total type="number">39</total>
			<wounds type="number">36</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Creativity - I don't even follow my own recipes, I just follow my gut instinct! (Chaotic)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">3</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">15 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 piercing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tiny needle can be used to jab at veins and nerves underneath the skin of a targeted foe.</p>
					<p>This weapon is tiny. Small and medium creatures can use it with a -5 modifier on their attack rolls. Large, huge, and gargantuan creatures cannot attempt to use it.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Accupuncture Needle</name>
				<properties type="string">Finesse</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Very Rare</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Tiny Melee</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This backpack holds much less than a normal backpack.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack (tiny)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This bedroll is only big enough for a tiny creature.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack (tiny)</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll (tiny)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Leaf of Grass (Druidric Focus)</name>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tiny tin box's lid serves as a plate or shallow bowl and the other side may be used as a pan to heat things over the fire.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack (tiny)</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mess Kit (tiny)</name>
				<rarity type="string">Rare</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Equipment Kits</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.25</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
					<p>Tiny Rations contain enough rations for a tiny creature for one day.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack (tiny)</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (tiny)</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.25</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A tiny waterskin holds 1/4 gallon of liquid. This is enough for a tiny creature for one day.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack (tiny)</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin (tiny)</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">101 - 500 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.disguiseself@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Spell: Disguise Self</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>While wearing this hat, you can use an action to cast the <i>disguise self </i>spell from it at will. The spell ends if the hat is removed.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hat of Disguise</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">A Cloth Hat</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A seemingly ordinary hat but of finer quality than would normally be the case for something like this.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon (Requires Attunement)</rarity>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 piercing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tiny crossbow can be used to fire regular accupuncture needles at the enemies weakpoints.</p>
					<p>This weapon is tiny. Small and medium creatures can use it with a -5 modifier on their attack rolls. Large, huge, and gargantuan creatures cannot attempt to use it.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mikon Crossbow</name>
				<properties type="string">Amunition (range 40/120), loading</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Very Rare</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Tiny Ranged</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">0.2</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">priceless</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.heartstone@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Heartstone</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>By concentrating on this stone for 1 minute you are teleported into the Nexus, a place of safety for most adventurers. (It is your ticket back, so guard it with your life.)</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack (tiny)</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heartstone</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Heartstone</nonid_name>
				<rarity type="string">legendary</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00010>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Elvish</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Mikon</name>
			</id-00003>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">6</level>
		<name type="string">Swino son of Apia</name>
		<perception type="number">17</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I like to take my time and savor each moment.</personalitytraits>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">4</prepared>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Effect</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Passive</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Wildshape</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<name type="string">Wildshape Ape</name>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00007>
				<name type="string">Wildshape Giant Goat</name>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<name type="string">Wildshape Crocodile</name>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<name type="string">Wildshape Giant Sea Horse</name>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<name type="string">Wildshape Giant Wasp</name>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<name type="string">Wildshape Reef Shark</name>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<name type="string">Wildshape Warhorse</name>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<name type="string">Wildshape Lion</name>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<name type="string">Wildshape Brown Bear</name>
			</id-00014>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">4</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">1</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">2</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">standard</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">day</durunit>
						<label type="string">Exhaustion Level 1; DISCHK</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00004@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Exhaustion</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Exhaustion Level 1</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">5e Rule Coding</source>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A flickering flame appears in your hand. The flame remains there for the duration and harms neither you nor your equipment. The flame sheds bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet. The spell ends if you dismiss it as an action or if you cast it again. You can also attack with the flame, although doing so ends the spell. When you cast this spell, or as an action on a later turn, you can hurl the flame at a creature within 30 feet of you. Make a ranged spell attack. On a hit, the target takes 1d8 fire damage. This spell's damage increases by 1d8 when you reach 5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Produce Flame</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d12,d12</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">poison</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You extend your hand toward a creature you can see within range and project a puff of noxious gas from your palm. The creature must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or take 1d12 poison damage. This spell's damage increases by 1d12 when you reach 5th level (2d12), 11th level (3d12), and 17th level (4d12).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Poison Spray</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">NOTE: Guidance (you may add 1d4 to a check); (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Guidance; CHECK: 1d4; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch one willing creature. Once before the spell ends, the target can roll a d4 and add the number rolled to one ability check of its choice. It can roll the die before or after making the ability check. The spell then ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Guidance</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Resistance; NOTE: you may add 1d4 to a save); (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a miniature cloak)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch one willing creature. Once before the spell ends, the target can roll a d4 and add the number rolled to one saving throw of its choice. It can roll the die before or after making the saving throw. The spell then ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Resistance</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">24</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Charmed</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a morsel of food)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell lets you convince a beast that you mean it no harm. Choose a beast that you can see within range. It must see and hear you. If the beast's Intelligence is 4 or higher, the spell fails. Otherwise, the beast must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be charmed by you for the spell's duration. If you or one of your companions harms the target, the spells ends.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can affect one additional beast t level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">24 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Animal Friendship</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Charmed</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Sound</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="url" recordname="syrinscape-fantasy:elements/ZXpyZW4tbWFsZS13aXphcmQ6OmNoYXJtLXBlcnNvbi1h/play/"><b>Syrinscape </b></link>: Charm - Wizard Spells E</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You attempt to charm a humanoid you can see within range. It must make a Wisdom saving throw, and does so with advantage if you or your companions are fighting it. If it fails the saving throw, it is charmed by you until the spell ends or until you or your companions do anything harmful to it. The charmed creature regards you as a friendly acquaintance. When the spell ends, the creature knows it was charmed by you.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st. The creatures must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Charm Person</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a drop of water if creating water or a few grains of sand if destroying it)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You either create or destroy water.</p>
					<p><b>Create Water </b>. You create up to 10 gallons of clean water within range in an open container. Alternatively, the water falls as rain in a 30-foot cube within range, extinguishing exposed flames in the area.</p>
					<p><b>Destroy Water </b>. You destroy up to 10 gallons of water in an open container within range. Alternatively, you destroy fog in a 30-foot cube within range.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you create or destroy 10 additional gallons of water, or the size of the cube increases by 5 feet, for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Create or Destroy Water</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch regains a number of hit points equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cure Wounds</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Detect Magic; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Sound</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="url" recordname="syrinscape-fantasy:elements/ZXpyZW4tbWFsZS13aXphcmQ6OmRldGVjdC1tYWdpYy1h/play/"><b>Syrinscape </b></link>: Detect Magic - Wizard Spells E</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any. The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Magic</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Detect Poison and Disease; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a yew leaf)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Sound</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="url" recordname="syrinscape-fantasy:elements/ZXpyZW4tbWFsZS13aXphcmQ6OmRldGVjdC1wb2lzb24/play/"><b>Syrinscape </b></link>: Detect Poisons - Wizard Spells E</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>For the duration, you can sense the presence and location of poisons, poisonous creatures, and diseases within 30 feet of you. You also identify the kind of poison, poisonous creature, or disease in each case. The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Poison and Disease</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Restrained; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Entangle; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Grasping weeds and vines sprout from the ground in a 20-foot square starting from a point within range. For the duration, these plants turn the ground in the area into difficult terrain. A creature in the area when you cast the spell must succeed on a Strength saving throw or be restrained by the entangling plants until the spell ends. A creature restrained by the plants can use its action to make a Strength check against your spell save DC. On a success, it frees itself. When the spell ends, the conjured plants wilt away.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Entangle</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">90 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Faerie Fire; GRANTADVATK; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Each object in a 20-foot cube within range is outlined in blue, green, or violet light (your choice). Any creature in the area when the spell is cast is also outlined in light if it fails a Dexterity saving throw. For the duration, objects and affected creatures shed dim light in a 10-foot radius. Any attack roll against an affected creature or object has advantage if the attacker can see it, and the affected creature or object can't benefit from being invisible.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Faerie Fire</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid</source>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Fog Cloud; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Sound</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="url" recordname="syrinscape-fantasy:elements/ZXpyZW4tbWFsZS13aXphcmQ6Om9ic2N1cmluZy1taXN0/play/">Obscuring fog - Wizard Spells E</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You create a 20-foot-radius sphere of fog centered on a point within range. The sphere spreads around corners, and its area is heavily obscured. It lasts for the duration or until a wind of moderate or greater speed (at least 10 miles per hour) disperses it.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the radius of the fog increases by 20 feet for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fog Cloud</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a sprig of mistletoe)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Up to ten berries appear in your hand and are infused with magic for the duration. A creature can use its action to eat one berry. Eating a berry restores 1 hit point, and the berry provides enough nourishment to sustain a creature for one day. The berries lose their potency if they have not been consumed within 24 hours of the casting of this spell.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Goodberry</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature of your choice that you can see within range regains hit points equal to 1d4 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d4 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Healing Word</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a grasshopper's hind leg)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Sound</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="url" recordname="syrinscape-fantasy:elements/ZXpyZW4tbWFsZS13aXphcmQ6Omp1bXAtMQ/play/">Jumping - Wizard Spells E</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You touch a creature. The creature's jump distance is tripled until the spell ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Jump</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of dirt)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature. The target's speed increases by 10 feet until the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Longstrider</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger, Wizard</source>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>All nonmagical food and drink within a 5-foot-radius sphere centered on a point of your choice within range is purified and rendered free of poison and disease.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Purify Food and Drink</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin</source>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You make yourself-including your clothing, armor, weapons, and other belongings on your person- look different until the spell ends or until you use your action to dismiss it. You can seem 1 foot shorter or taller and can appear thin, fat, or in between. You can't change your body type, so you must adopt a form that has the same basic arrangement of limbs. Otherwise, the extent of the illusion is up to you. The changes wrought by this spell fail to hold up to physical inspection. For example, if you use this spell to add a hat to your outfit, objects pass through the hat, and anyone who touches it would feel nothing or would feel your head and hair. If you use this spell to appear thinner than you are, the hand of someone who reaches out to touch you would bump into you while it was seemingly still in midair. To discern that you are disguised, a creature can use its action to inspect your appearance and must succeed on an Intelligence (Investigation) check against your spell save DC.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Disguise Self - Hat of Disguise</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain the ability to comprehend and verbally communicate with beasts for the duration. The knowledge and awareness of many beasts is limited by their intelligence, but at minimum, beasts can give you information about nearby locations and monsters, including whatever they can perceive or have perceived within the past day. You might be able to persuade a beast to perform a small favor for you, at the GM's discretion.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Speak with Animals</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">thunder</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A wave of thunderous force sweeps out from you. Each creature in a 15-foot cube originating from you must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, a creature takes 2d8 thunder damage and is pushed 10 feet away from you. On a successful save, the creature takes half as much damage and isn't pushed. In addition, unsecured objects that are completely within the area of effect are automatically pushed 10 feet away from you by the spell's effect, and the spell emits a thunderous boom audible out to 300 feet.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Thunderwave</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self (15-foot cube)</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a morsel of food)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>By means of this spell, you use an animal to deliver a message. Choose a Tiny beast you can see within range, such as a squirrel, a blue jay, or a bat. You specify a location, which you must have visited, and a recipient who matches a general description, such as &#34;a man or woman dressed in the uniform of the town guard&#34; or &#34;a red-haired dwarf wearing a pointed hat.&#34; You also speak a message of up to twenty-five words. The target beast travels for the duration of the spell toward the specified location, covering about 50 miles per 24 hours for a flying messenger, or 25 miles for other animals. When the messenger arrives, it delivers your message to the creature that you described, replicating the sound of your voice. The messenger speaks only to a creature matching the description you gave. If the messenger doesn't reach its destination before the spell ends, the message is lost, and the beast makes its way back to where you cast this spell.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: If you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3nd level or higher, the duration of the spell increases by 48 hours for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">24 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Animal Messenger</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Barkskin; (C); AC: 1</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a handful of oak bark)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Sound</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="url" recordname="syrinscape-fantasy:elements/ZXpyZW4tbWFsZS13aXphcmQ6Om1hZ2UtYXJtb3ItYQ/play/"><b>Syrinscape </b></link>: Magical armor - Wizard Spells E</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You touch a willing creature. Until the spell ends, the target's skin has a rough, bark-like appearance, and the target's AC can't be less than 16, regardless of what kind of armor it is wearing.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Barkskin</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00025>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (either a pinch of dried carrot or an agate)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a willing creature to grant it the ability to see in the dark. For the duration, that creature has darkvision out to a range of 60 feet.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Darkvision</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00025>
			<id-00026>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Bear's Endurance; ADVCHK: constitution; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Bull's Strength; ADVCHK: strength; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Cat's Grace; ADVCHK: dexterity; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
					<id-00005>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Eagle's Splendor; ADVCHK: charisma; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">5</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00005>
					<id-00006>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Fox's Cunning; ADVCHK: intelligence; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">6</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00006>
					<id-00007>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Owl's Wisdom; ADVCHK: wisdom; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">7</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00007>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (fur or a feather from a beast)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature and bestow upon it a magical enhancement. Choose one of the following effects; the target gains that effect until the spell ends.</p>
					<p>Bear's Endurance. The target has advantage on Constitution checks. It also gains 2d6 temporary hit points, which are lost when the spell ends.</p>
					<p>Bull's Strength. The target has advantage on Strength checks, and his or her carrying capacity doubles.</p>
					<p>Cat's Grace. The target has advantage on Dexterity checks. It also doesn't take damage from falling 20 feet or less if it isn't incapacitated.</p>
					<p>Eagle's Splendor. The target has advantage on Charisma checks.</p>
					<p>Fox's Cunning. The target has advantage on Intelligence checks.</p>
					<p>Owl's Wisdom. The target has advantage on Wisdom checks.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour.</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Enhance Ability</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Sorcerer</source>
			</id-00026>
			<id-00027>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You sense the presence of any trap within range that is within line of sight. A trap, for the purpose of this spell, includes anything that would inflict a sudden or unexpected effect you consider harmful or undesirable, which was specifically intended as such by its creator. Thus, the spell would sense an area affected by the alarm spell, a glyph of warding, or a mechanical pit trap, but it would not reveal a natural weakness in the floor, an unstable ceiling, or a hidden sinkhole. This spell merely reveals that a trap is present. You don't learn the location of each trap, but you do learn the general nature of the danger posed by a trap you sense.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Find Traps</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00027>
			<id-00028>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">ability</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atkstat type="string">strength</atkstat>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Flame Blade; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (leaf of sumac)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You evoke a fiery blade in your free hand. The blade is similar in size and shape to a scimitar, and it lasts for the duration. If you let go of the blade, it disappears, but you can evoke the blade again as a bonus action. You can use your action to make a melee spell attack with the fiery blade. On a hit, the target takes 3d6 fire damage. The flaming blade sheds bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for every two slot levels above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Flame Blade</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00028>
			<id-00029>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Flaming Sphere; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a bit of tallow, a pinch of brimstone, and a dusting of powdered iron)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A 5-foot-diameter sphere of fire appears in an unoccupied space of your choice within range and lasts for the duration. Any creature that ends its turn within 5 feet of the sphere must make a Dexterity saving throw. The creature takes 2d6 fire damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. As a bonus action, you can move the sphere up to 30 feet. If you ram the sphere into a creature, that creature must make the saving throw against the sphere's damage, and the sphere stops moving this turn. When you move the sphere, you can direct it over barriers up to 5 feet tall and jump it across pits up to 10 feet wide. The sphere ignites flammable objects not being worn or carried, and it sheds bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Flaming Sphere</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Wizard</source>
			</id-00029>
			<id-00030>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Gust of Wind; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a legume seed)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A line of strong wind 60 feet long and 10 feet wide blasts from you in a direction you choose for the spell's duration. Each creature that starts its turn in the line must succeed on a Strength saving throw or be pushed 15 feet away from you in a direction following the line. Any creature in the line must spend 2 feet of movement for every 1 foot it moves when moving closer to you. The gust disperses gas or vapor, and it extinguishes candles, torches, and similar unprotected flames in the area. It causes protected flames, such as those of lanterns, to dance wildly and has a 50 percent chance to extinguish them. As a bonus action on each of your turns before the spell ends, you can change the direction in which the line blasts from you.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Gust of Wind</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self (60-foot line)</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00030>
			<id-00031>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Heat Metal; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a piece of iron and a flame)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose a manufactured metal object, such as a metal weapon or a suit of heavy or medium metal armor, that you can see within range. You cause the object to glow red-hot. Any creature in physical contact with the object takes 2d8 fire damage when you cast the spell. Until the spell ends, you can use a bonus action on each of your subsequent turns to cause this damage again. If a creature is holding or wearing the object and takes the damage from it, the creature must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or drop the object if it can. If it doesn't drop the object, it has disadvantage on attack rolls and ability checks until the start of your next turn. At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heat Metal</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid</source>
			</id-00031>
			<id-00032>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Paralyzed; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a small, straight piece of iron)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose a humanoid that you can see within range. The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be paralyzed for the duration. At the end of each of its turns, the target can make another Wisdom saving throw. On a success, the spell ends on the target.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you can target one additional humanoid for each slot level above 2nd. The humanoids must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hold Person</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00032>
			<id-00033>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature and can end either one disease or one condition afflicting it. The condition can be blinded, deafened, paralyzed, or poisoned.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lesser Restoration</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00033>
			<id-00034>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a bit of fur from a bloodhound)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Describe or name a specific kind of beast or plant. Concentrating on the voice of nature in your surroundings, you learn the direction and distance to the closest creature or plant of that kind within 5 miles, if any are present.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Locate Animals or Plants</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00034>
			<id-00035>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Locate Object; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a forked twig)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Describe or name an object that is familiar to you. You sense the direction to the object's location, as long as that object is within 1,000 feet of you. If the object is in motion, you know the direction of its movement. The spell can locate a specific object known to you, as long as you have seen it up close-within 30 feet-at least once. Alternatively, the spell can locate the nearest object of a particular kind, such as a certain kind of apparel, jewelry, furniture, tool, or weapon. This spell can't locate an object if any thickness of lead, even a thin sheet, blocks a direct path between you and the object.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Locate Object</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger, Wizard</source>
			</id-00035>
			<id-00036>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10</dice>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Moonbeam; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (several seeds of any moonseed plant and a piece of opalescent feldspar)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A silvery beam of pale light shines down in a 5-foot- radius, 40-foot-high cylinder centered on a point within range. Until the spell ends, dim light fills the cylinder. When a creature enters the spell's area for the first time on a turn or starts its turn there, it is engulfed in ghostly flames that cause searing pain, and it must make a Constitution saving throw. It takes 2d10 radiant damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. A shapechanger makes its saving throw with disadvantage. If it fails, it also instantly reverts to its original form and can't assume a different form until it leaves the spell's light. On each of your turns after you cast this spell, you can use an action to move the beam 60 feet in any direction.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d10 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Moonbeam</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00036>
			<id-00037>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Pass without Trace; SKILL: 10, stealth; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (ashes from a burned leaf of mistletoe and a sprig of spruce)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A veil of shadows and silence radiates from you, masking you and your companions from detection. For the duration, each creature you choose within 30 feet of you (including you) has a +10 bonus to Dexterity (Stealth) checks and can't be tracked except by magical means. A creature that receives this bonus leaves behind no tracks or other traces of its passage.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Pass without Trace</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00037>
			<id-00038>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVSAV: poisoned; RESIST: poison</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Sound</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="url" recordname="syrinscape-fantasy:elements/ZXpyZW4tbWFsZS13aXphcmQ6OnByb3RlY3Rpb24/play/"><b>Syrinscape </b></link>: Protection - Wizard Spells E</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You touch a creature. If it is poisoned, you neutralize the poison. If more than one poison afflicts the target, you neutralize one poison that you know is present, or you neutralize one at random. For the duration, the target has advantage on saving throws against being poisoned, and it has resistance to poison damage.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Protection from Poison</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00038>
			<id-00039>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
								<type type="string">piercing,magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Spike Growth; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (seven sharp thorns or seven small twigs, each sharpened to a point)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The ground in a 20-foot radius centered on a point within range twists and sprouts hard spikes and thorns. The area becomes difficult terrain for the duration. When a creature moves into or within the area, it takes 2d4 piercing damage for every 5 feet it travels. The transformation of the ground is camouflaged to look natural. Any creature that can't see the area at the time the spell is cast must make a Wisdom (Perception) check against your spell save DC to recognize the terrain as hazardous before entering it.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spike Growth</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">150 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00039>
			<id-00040>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10,d10</dice>
								<type type="string">lightning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Call Lightning; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A storm cloud appears in the shape of a cylinder that is 10 feet tall with a 60-foot radius, centered on a point you can see 100 feet directly above you. The spell fails if you can't see a point in the air where the storm cloud could appear (for example, if you are in a room that can't accommodate the cloud). When you cast the spell, choose a point you can see within range. A bolt of lightning flashes down from the cloud to that point. Each creature within 5 feet of that point must make a Dexterity saving throw. A creature takes 3d10 lightning damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. On each of your turns until the spell ends, you can use your action to call down lightning in this way again, targeting the same point or a different one. If you are outdoors in stormy conditions when you cast this spell, the spell gives you control over the existing storm instead of creating a new one. Under such conditions, the spell's damage increases by 1d10.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th or higher level, the damage increases by 1d10 for each slot level above 3rd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Call Lightning</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00040>
			<id-00041>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Conjure Animals; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You summon fey spirits that take the form of beasts and appear in unoccupied spaces that you can see within range. Choose one of the following options for what appears:</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="table" recordname="tables.id-02413@Incarnate-5eExpansion">One beast of challenge rating 2 or lower</link>
						<link class="table" recordname="tables.id-02414@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Two beasts of challenge rating 1 or lower</link>
						<link class="table" recordname="tables.id-02415@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Four beasts of challenge rating 1/2 or lower</link>
						<link class="table" recordname="tables.id-02416@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Eight beasts of challenge rating 1/4 or lower</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>Each beast is also considered fey, and it disappears when it drops to 0 hit points or when the spell ends. The summoned creatures are friendly to you and your companions. Roll initiative for the summoned creatures as a group, which has its own turns. They obey any verbal commands that you issue to them (no action required by you). If you don't issue any commands to them, they defend themselves from hostile creatures, but otherwise take no actions. The GM has the creatures' statistics.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using certain higher-level spell slots, you choose one of the summoning options above, and more creatures appear: twice as many with a 5th-level slot, three times as many with a 7th-level slot, and four times as many with a 9th-level slot.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Conjure Animals</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00041>
			<id-00042>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Sound</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="url" recordname="syrinscape-fantasy:elements/ZXpyZW4tbWFsZS13aXphcmQ6OmxpZ2h0/play/"><b>Syrinscape </b></link>: Light bright - Wizard Spells E</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>A 60-foot-radius sphere of light spreads out from a point you choose within range. The sphere is bright light and sheds dim light for an additional 60 feet. If you chose a point on an object you are holding or one that isn't being worn or carried, the light shines from the object and moves with it. Completely covering the affected object with an opaque object, such as a bowl or a helm, blocks the light. If any of this spell's area overlaps with an area of darkness created by a spell of 3rd level or lower, the spell that created the darkness is dispelled.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Daylight</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer</source>
			</id-00042>
			<id-00043>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose one creature, object, or magical effect within range. Any spell of 3rd level or lower on the target ends. For each spell of 4th level or higher on the target, make an ability check using your spellcasting ability. The DC equals 10 + the spell's level. On a successful check, the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher, you automatically end the effects of a spell on the target if the spell's level is equal to or less than the level of the spell slot you used.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dispel Magic</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00043>
			<id-00044>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6,d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning,magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">50</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning,magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You step into a stone object or surface large enough to fully contain your body, melding yourself and all the equipment you carry with the stone for the duration. Using your movement, you step into the stone at a point you can touch. Nothing of your presence remains visible or otherwise detectable by nonmagical senses. While merged with the stone, you can't see what occurs outside it, and any Wisdom (Perception) checks you make to hear sounds outside it are made with disadvantage. You remain aware of the passage of time and can cast spells on yourself while merged in the stone. You can use your movement to leave the stone where you entered it, which ends the spell. You otherwise can't move. Minor physical damage to the stone doesn't harm you, but its partial destruction or a change in its shape (to the extent that you no longer fit within it) expels you and deals 6d6 bludgeoning damage to you. The stone's complete destruction (or transmutation into a different substance) expels you and deals 50 bludgeoning damage to you. If expelled, you fall prone in an unoccupied space closest to where you first entered.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Meld into Stone</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00044>
			<id-00045>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action or 8 hours</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell channels vitality into plants within a specific area. There are two possible uses for the spell, granting either immediate or long-term benefits. If you cast this spell using 1 action, choose a point within range. All normal plants in a 100-foot radius centered on that point become thick and overgrown. A creature moving through the area must spend 4 feet of movement for every 1 foot it moves. You can exclude one or more areas of any size within the spell's area from being affected. If you cast this spell over 8 hours, you enrich the land. All plants in a half-mile radius centered on a point within range become enriched for 1 year. The plants yield twice the normal amount of food when harvested. Poison</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Plant Growth</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">150 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00045>
			<id-00046>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">RESIST: acid; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">RESIST: cold; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">RESIST: fire; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">RESIST: lightning; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
					<id-00005>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">RESIST: thunder; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">5</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00005>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Sound</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="url" recordname="syrinscape-fantasy:elements/ZXpyZW4tbWFsZS13aXphcmQ6OnByb3RlY3Rpb24/play/"><b>Syrinscape </b></link>: Protection - Wizard Spells E</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>For the duration, the willing creature you touch has resistance to one damage type of your choice: acid, cold, fire, lightning, or thunder.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Protection from Energy</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00046>
			<id-00047>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Sleet Storm; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of dust and a few drops of water)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Until the spell ends, freezing rain and sleet fall in a 20-foot-tall cylinder with a 40-foot radius centered on a point you choose within range. The area is heavily obscured, and exposed flames in the area are doused. The ground in the area is covered with slick ice, making it difficult terrain. When a creature enters the spell's area for the first time on a turn or starts its turn there, it must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, it falls prone. If a creature is concentrating in the spell's area, the creature must make a successful Constitution saving throw against your spell save DC or lose concentration.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sleet Storm</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">150 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00047>
			<id-00048>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You imbue plants within 30 feet of you with limited sentience and animation, giving them the ability to communicate with you and follow your simple commands. You can question plants about events in the spell's area within the past day, gaining information about creatures that have passed, weather, and other circumstances. You can also turn difficult terrain caused by plant growth (such as thickets and undergrowth) into ordinary terrain that lasts for the duration. Or you can turn ordinary terrain where plants are present into difficult terrain that lasts for the duration, causing vines and branches to hinder pursuers, for example. Plants might be able to perform other tasks on your behalf, at the GM's discretion. The spell doesn't enable plants to uproot themselves and move about, but they can freely move branches, tendrils, and stalks. If a plant creature is in the area, you can communicate with it as if you shared a common language, but you gain no magical ability to influence it. This spell can cause the plants created by the entangle spell to release a restrained creature.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Speak with Plants</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self (30-foot radius)</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00048>
			<id-00049>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a short reed or piece of straw)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell grants up to ten willing creatures you can see within range the ability to breathe underwater until the spell ends. Affected creatures also retain their normal mode of respiration.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">24 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Water Breathing</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00049>
			<id-00050>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a piece of cork)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell grants the ability to move across any liquid surface-such as water, acid, mud, snow, quicksand, or lava-as if it were harmless solid ground (creatures crossing molten lava can still take damage from the heat). Up to ten willing creatures you can see within range gain this ability for the duration. If you target a creature submerged in a liquid, the spell carries the target to the surface of the liquid at a rate of 60 feet per round.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Water Walk</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Ranger, Sorcerer</source>
			</id-00050>
			<id-00052>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">day</durunit>
						<label type="string">Mikon Specialty; IFT: TYPE(beast,fey); ATK:1d4</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>There is only so much time in school, so Mikons specialize in learning the weaknesses of different types of creatures. All Mikons learn the weaknesses of beasts. At levels 3, 6, 9, 12, 15, 18, and 20 you may learn additional types from: Aberrations, Celestials, Constructs, Dragons, Elementals, Feys, Fiends, Giants, Humanoids, Misons, Monstrosities, Oozes, Plants, Swarms, Undead.</p>
					<p>Knowing the weaknesses not only lets you know their weaknesses, but also grants you a 1d4 increase to your attack rolls.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Passive</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mikon Specialty - beasts, fey</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<source type="string">Mikon</source>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00052>
			<id-00053>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning,magic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Wind Wall; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a tiny fan and a feather of</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A wall of strong wind rises from the ground at a point you choose within range. You can make the wall up to 50 feet long, 15 feet high, and 1 foot thick. You can shape the wall in any way you choose so long as it makes one continuous path along the ground. The wall lasts for the duration. When the wall appears, each creature within its area must make a Strength saving throw. A creature takes 3d8 bludgeoning damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. The strong wind keeps fog, smoke, and other gases at bay. Small or smaller flying creatures or objects can't pass through the wall. Loose, lightweight materials brought into the wall fly upward. Arrows, bolts, and other ordinary projectiles launched at targets behind the wall are deflected upward and automatically miss. (Boulders hurled by giants or siege engines, and similar projectiles, are unaffected.) Creatures in gaseous form can't pass through it.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wind Wall</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00053>
			<id-00054>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">fixed</savedcbase>
						<savedcmod type="number">13</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4,d4</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00004>
					<id-00005>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4,d4,d4</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">5</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00005>
					<id-00006>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4,d4,d4,d4</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">6</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00006>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_racialtrait" recordname="race.id-00013.traits.id-00012@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Underfoot</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Passive</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Underfoot</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00054>
			<id-00055>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">day</durunit>
						<label type="string">Exhaustion Level 3; DISSAV; DISATK</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00004@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Exhaustion</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Exhaustion Level 3</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">5e Rule Coding</source>
			</id-00055>
			<id-00056>
				<actions>
					<id-00004>
						<label type="string">Wildshape; AC: -1</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">1</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Common Transformations</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.p98wildshape_polymorphcheatsheet@Incarnate-5eExpansion">98 Wildshape/Polymorph</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Main Description</h>
					<p>Starting at 2nd Level, you can use your action to magically assume the shape of a beast that you have seen before. You can use this feature twice. You regain expended uses when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>Your druid level determines the beasts you can transform into as shown in the Beast Shapes table. At 2nd level, for example, you can transform into any beast that has a challenge rating of 1/4 or lower that doesn't have a flying or swimming speed.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td colspan="6"><b>Beast Shapes</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td></td>
							<td><b>Max.</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Level</b></td>
							<td><b>CR</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"><b>Limitations</b></td>
							<td><b>Example</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2nd</td>
							<td>1/4</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying or swimming speed</td>
							<td>Wolf</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4th</td>
							<td>1/2</td>
							<td colspan="3">No flying speed</td>
							<td>Crocodile</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8th</td>
							<td><b>1</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"></td>
							<td>Giant eagle</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>You can stay in a beast shape for a number of hours equal to half your druid level (rounded down). You then revert to your normal form unless you expend another use of this feature. You can revert to your normal form earlier by using a bonus action on your turn. You automatically revert if you fall unconscious, drop to 9 hit points, or die.</p>
					<p>While you are transformed the following rules apply:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Your game statistics are replaced by the statistics of the beast, but you retain your alignment, personality, and Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma scores. You also retain all of your skill and saving throw proficiencies, in addition to gaining those of the creature. If the creature has the same proficiency as you and the bonus in its stat block is higher than yours, use the creature's bonus instead of yours. If the creature has any legendary or lair actions, you can't use them.</li>
						<li>When you transform, you assume the beast's hit points and Hit Dice. When you revert to your normal form, you return to the number of hit points you had before you transformed. However if you revert as a result of dropping to 0 hit points, any excess damage carries over to your normal form. For example, if you take 10 damage in animal form and only have 1 hit point left, you revert and take 9 damage. As long as the excess damage doesn't reduce your normal form to 0 hit points, you aren't knocked unconscious.</li>
						<li>You can't cast spells, and your ability to speak or take any action that requires hands is limited to the capabilities f your beast form. Transforming doesn't break your concentration on a spell you've already cast, however, or prevent you from taking actions that are part of a spell, such as <i>call lightning </i>, that you've already cast.</li>
						<li>You retain the benefit of any features from your class, race, or other source and can use them if the new form is physically capable of doing so. However, you can't use any of your special senses, such as darkvision, unless your new form also has that sense.</li>
						<li>You choose whether your equipment falls to the ground in your space, merges into your new form or is worn by it. Worn equipment functions as normal, but the GM decides if it is practical for the new form to ear a piece of equipment based on the creature's shape and size. Your equipment doesn't change size or shape to match the new form and any equipment that the new form can't wear must either fall to the ground or merge with it. Equipment that merges with the form has no effect until you leave the form.</li>
					</list>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape</group>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wild Shape</name>
				<prepared type="number">2</prepared>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00056>
			<id-00057>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">5</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.ape@Incarnate-5eBattles">Ape</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Ape</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fist - Ape</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00057>
			<id-00058>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">5</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.ape@Incarnate-5eBattles">Ape</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Ape</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rock - Ape</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00058>
			<id-00059>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">6</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8,d8</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">STR: [-2STR]; STR: 6; DEX: [-2DEX]; DEX: 4; CON: [-2CON]; CON: 4; AC: -1</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.ape@Incarnate-5eBattles">Ape</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Ape</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Transformation - Ape</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00059>
			<id-00063>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<atkbase type="string">ability</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">fixed</savedcbase>
						<savedcmod type="number">13</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.giantgoat@Incarnate-5eBattles">Giant Goat</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Giant Goat</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Charge - Giant Goat</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00063>
			<id-00064>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">5</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.giantgoat@Incarnate-5eBattles">Giant Goat</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Giant Goat</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ram - Giant Goat</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00064>
			<id-00065>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10,d10</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">STR: [-2STR]; STR: 7; DEX: [-2DEX]; DEX: 1; CON: [-2CON]; CON: 2; AC: 0</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.giantgoat@Incarnate-5eBattles">Giant Goat</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Giant Goat</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Transformation - Giant Goat</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00065>
			<id-00066>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">4</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">piercing</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Grappled; Restrained; NOTE: escape DC 12</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.crocodile@Incarnate-5eBattles">Crocodile</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Crocodile</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bite - Crocodile</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00066>
			<id-00067>
				<actions>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10,d10</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">STR: [-2STR]; STR: 5; DEX: [-2DEX]; DEX: 0; CON: [-2CON]; CON: 3; AC: 1</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.crocodile@Incarnate-5eBattles">Crocodile</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Crocodile</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Transformation - Crocodile</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00067>
			<id-00068>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">11</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.giantseahorse@Incarnate-5eBattles">Giant Sea Horse</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Giant Sea Horse</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Charge - Giant Sea Horse</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00068>
			<id-00069>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">3</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.giantseahorse@Incarnate-5eBattles">Giant Sea Horse</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Giant Sea Horse</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ram - Giant Sea Horse</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00069>
			<id-00070>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10,d10</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">STR: [-2STR]; STR: 2; DEX: [-2DEX]; DEX: 5; CON: [-2CON]; CON: 1; AC: 0</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.giantseahorse@Incarnate-5eBattles">Giant Sea Horse</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Giant Sea Horse</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Transformation - Giant Sea Horse</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00070>
			<id-00071>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">4</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">piercing</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">fixed</savedcbase>
						<savedcmod type="number">11</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">poison</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00004>
					<id-00005>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Note: Only if target is knocked unconscious; poisoned; paralyzed</label>
						<order type="number">5</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00005>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.giantwasp@Incarnate-5eBattles">Giant Wasp</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Giant Wasp</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sting - Giant Wasp</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00071>
			<id-00072>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8,d8</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">STR: [-2STR]; STR: 0; DEX: [-2DEX]; DEX: 4; CON: [-2CON]; CON: 0; AC: -1</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.giantwasp@Incarnate-5eBattles">Giant Wasp</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Giant Wasp</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Transformation - Giant Wasp</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00072>
			<id-00073>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">4</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">piercing</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.reefshark@Incarnate-5eBattles">Reef Shark</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Reef Shark</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bite - Reef Shark</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00073>
			<id-00074>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8,d8,d8</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">STR: [-2STR]; STR: 4; DEX: [-2DEX]; DEX: 3; CON: [-2CON]; CON: 3; AC: 0</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.reefshark@Incarnate-5eBattles">Reef Shark</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Reef Shark</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Transformation - Reef Shark</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00074>
			<id-00075>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">6</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.warhorse@Incarnate-5eBattles">Warhorse</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Warhorse</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hooves - Warhorse</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00075>
			<id-00076>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">fixed</savedcbase>
						<savedcmod type="number">14</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.warhorse@Incarnate-5eBattles">Warhorse</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Warhorse</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Trampling Charge - Warhorse</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00076>
			<id-00077>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10,d10</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">STR: [-2STR]; STR: 8; DEX: [-2DEX]; DEX: 2; CON: [-2CON]; CON: 3; AC: -1</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="reference.npcdata.warhorse@Incarnate-5eBattles">Warhorse</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Warhorse</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Transformation - Warhorse</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00077>
			<id-00078>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">DODGE</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You focus entirely on avoiding attacks. Until the end of your next turn, any attack roll made against you has disadvantage if you can see the attacker, and you make Dexterity saving throws with advantage. You lose this benefit if you are incapacitated or if your speed drops to 0.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="referencemanualpage" recordname="referencemanual2.SRD_PRO_00071@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Actions in Combat</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dodge</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00078>
			<id-00079>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Help - check; ADVCHK</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Help - attack; ADVATK</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can lend your aid to another creature in the completion of a task. When you take the Help action, the creature you aid gains advantage on the next ability check it makes to perform the task you are helping with, provided that it makes the check before the start of your next turn.</p>
					<p>Alternatively, you can aid a friendly creature in attacking a creature within 5 feet of you. You feint, distract the target, or in some other way team up to make your ally's attack more effective. If your ally attacks the target beforre your next turn, the first attack roll is made with advantage.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="referencemanualpage" recordname="referencemanual2.SRD_PRO_00071@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Actions in Combat</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Help</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00079>
			<id-00080>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">5</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">slashing</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.lion@Incarnate-5eBattles">Lion</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Lion</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bite - Lion</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Polymorph Code</source>
			</id-00080>
			<id-00081>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">5</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">piercing</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.lion@Incarnate-5eBattles">Lion</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Lion</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Claw - Lion</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Polymorph Code</source>
			</id-00081>
			<id-00082>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">fixed</savedcbase>
						<savedcmod type="number">13</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">prone; NOTE: lion may make bit attack as bonus action</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.lion@Incarnate-5eBattles">Lion</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Lion</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Pounce - Lion</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Polymorph Code</source>
			</id-00082>
			<id-00083>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10,d10,d10</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">STR: [-2STR]; STR: 7; DEX: [-2DEX]; DEX: 5; CON: [-2CON]; CON: 3; AC: -1</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.lion@Incarnate-5eBattles">Lion</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Lion</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Transformation - Lion</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Polymorph Code</source>
			</id-00083>
			<id-00085>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of sand, which the spell consumes)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can transform one gallon of inert liquid or a liquid with a DC less than 12 into water. This can include common bear, alchemist's fire, and serpent venom.</p>
					<p>At Higher Levels: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher you may turn a liquid of 2 higher DC per level above third according to the table below:</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Spell Slot</td>
							<td>DC possible</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2</td>
							<td>14</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>3</td>
							<td>16</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4</td>
							<td>18</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>5</td>
							<td>20</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>6</td>
							<td>22</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>7</td>
							<td>24</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8</td>
							<td>26</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>9</td>
							<td>28</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Transmute Into Water</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00085>
			<id-00086>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a willing beast. For the duration of the spell, you can use your action to see through the beast's eyes and hear what it hears, and continue to do so until you use your action to return to your normal senses. While perceiving through the beast's senses, you gain the benefits of any special senses possessed by that creature, though you are blinded and deafened to your own surroundings.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Beast Sense</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00086>
			<id-00087>
				<actions>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Static Attraction; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">DMGO: 2d6 lightning; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of ash from a tree hit by a lightning bolt)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You point your finger at a creature you can see in range and a tiny spark jumps from your hand to them. What initially seems to be no big deal, becomes a very big deal though. That small spark charges them so that the latent static energy of the area is attracted to them. For the duration, at the start of each of their turns they take 2d6 lightning damage. When that creature dies you may use your bonus action to move the tiny spark from their dead body to another creature within range.</p>
					<p>If the target leaves range, even if only for a moment, then the spell dissipates.</p>
					<p>This attraction also attracts other lightning based damage. Any lightning attacks within 30 feet of an effected creature are re-centered on that creature.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Static Attraction</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00087>
			<id-00088>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (A collar worth at least 25 GP which the spell consumes)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The beast you touch gains the ability to comprehend and speak one language of your choice for the duration or until the collar you place around it is broken or removed. At the end of one hour the energy of the spell disintegrates the collar. The knowledge and awareness of many beasts is limited by their intelligence, but at a minimum, beasts can give you information about nearby locations and monsters, including whatever they can perceive or have perceived within the past day. You might be able to persuade a beast to perform a small favor for you, at the GM's discretion.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels: </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher and use a collar meeting the growing cost as shown in the table below, the duration increases as shown in that table.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Spell Slot</td>
							<td>Cost</td>
							<td>Duration</td>
							<td colspan="2">Name</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>3rd</td>
							<td>50 GP</td>
							<td>1 week</td>
							<td colspan="2">Minor Collar of Talking Beast</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4th</td>
							<td>100 GP</td>
							<td>2 weeks</td>
							<td colspan="2">Lesser Collar of Talking Beast</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>5th</td>
							<td>150 GP</td>
							<td>1 month</td>
							<td colspan="2">Collar of Talking Beast</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>6th</td>
							<td>250 GP</td>
							<td>3 months</td>
							<td colspan="2">Greater Collar of Talking Beast</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>7th</td>
							<td>500 GP</td>
							<td>6 months</td>
							<td colspan="2">Superior Collar of Talking Beast</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8th</td>
							<td>1,000 GP</td>
							<td>1 year</td>
							<td colspan="2">Supreme Collar of Talking Beast</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>9th</td>
							<td>2,000 GP</td>
							<td>permanent</td>
							<td colspan="2">Legendary Collar of Talking Beast</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<h>Item Code</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-01055@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Minor Collar of Talking Beast</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-01056@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Lesser Collar of Talking Beast</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-01057@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Collar of Talking Beast</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-01058@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Greater Collar of Talking Beast</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-01059@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Superior Collar of Talking Beast</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-01060@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Supreme Collar of Talking Beast</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-01054@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Legendary Collar of Talking Beast</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 day</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Talking Beast</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00088>
			<id-00089>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of barley, which the spell consumes)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a keg of water which transforms into common beer.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00090@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Keg of Superior Beer</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher and provide the required material component, you may choose a different type of liquid to transform the water into according to the table below:</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Spell Slot</td>
							<td colspan="2">Liquid Type</td>
							<td colspan="2">Material Component</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>3</td>
							<td colspan="2">Assassin's Blood</td>
							<td colspan="2">Exotic herbs worth at least 13 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>3</td>
							<td colspan="2">Alchemist's Fire</td>
							<td colspan="2">Ground Demon Horn worth at least 15 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>3</td>
							<td colspan="2">Small Cask of Common Wine</td>
							<td colspan="2">Cluster of grapes worth at least 3 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>3</td>
							<td colspan="2">Small Keg of Supreme Beer</td>
							<td colspan="2">Pinch of fine barley worth at least 5 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4</td>
							<td colspan="2">Common Berserker Juice</td>
							<td colspan="2">Ground Demon Horn worth at least 75 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4</td>
							<td colspan="2">Torpor</td>
							<td colspan="2">Exotic herbs worth at least 50 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4</td>
							<td colspan="2">Greater Alchemist's Fire</td>
							<td colspan="2">Ground Demon Horn worth at least 25 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4</td>
							<td colspan="2">Small Cask of Greater Wine</td>
							<td colspan="2">Cluster of grapes worth at least 9 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4</td>
							<td colspan="2">Small Keg of Common Mead</td>
							<td colspan="2">Honey worth at least 25 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4</td>
							<td colspan="2">Small Keg of Legendary Beer</td>
							<td colspan="2">Pinch of fine barley worth at least 15 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>5</td>
							<td colspan="2">Greater Berserker Juice</td>
							<td colspan="2">Ground Demon Horn worth at least 150 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>5</td>
							<td colspan="2">Superior Alchemist's Fire</td>
							<td colspan="2">Ground Demon Horn worth at least 50 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>5</td>
							<td colspan="2">Small Cask of Superior Wine</td>
							<td colspan="2">Cluster of Grapes worth at least 20 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>5</td>
							<td colspan="2">Small Keg of Celestial Beer</td>
							<td colspan="2">Pinch of fine barley worth at least 25 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>5</td>
							<td colspan="2">Small Keg of Greater Mead</td>
							<td colspan="2">Honey worth at least 50 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>6</td>
							<td colspan="2">Superior Berserker Juice</td>
							<td colspan="2">Ground Demon Horn worth at least 300 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>6</td>
							<td colspan="2">Truth Serum</td>
							<td colspan="2">Exotic herbs worth at least 200 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>6</td>
							<td colspan="2">Small Cast of Supreme Wine</td>
							<td colspan="2">Cluster of grapes worth at least 50 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>6</td>
							<td colspan="2">Small Keg of Superior Mead</td>
							<td colspan="2">Honey worth at least 125 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>6</td>
							<td colspan="2">Supreme Alchemist's Fire</td>
							<td colspan="2">Ground Demon horn worth at least 100 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>7</td>
							<td colspan="2">Supreme Berserker Juice</td>
							<td colspan="2">Ground Balor Horn worth at least 600 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>7</td>
							<td colspan="2">Midnight Tears</td>
							<td colspan="2">Exotic Herbs worth at least 200 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>7</td>
							<td colspan="2">Legendary Alchemist's Fire</td>
							<td colspan="2">Ground Balor Horn worth at least 200 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>7</td>
							<td colspan="2">Small Cask of Legendary Wine</td>
							<td colspan="2">Cluster of grapes worth at least 250 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>7</td>
							<td colspan="2">Small Keg of Supreme Mead</td>
							<td colspan="2">Honey worth at least 250 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8</td>
							<td colspan="2">Legendary Berserker Juice</td>
							<td colspan="2">Ground Pit Fiend Horn worth at least 1,250 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8</td>
							<td colspan="2">Infernal Alchemist's Fire</td>
							<td colspan="2">Ground Balor Horn worth at least 400 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8</td>
							<td colspan="2">Small Cask of Celestial Wine</td>
							<td colspan="2">Cluster of grapes worth at least 500 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>8</td>
							<td colspan="2">Small Keg of Legendary Mead</td>
							<td colspan="2">Honey worth at least 500 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>9</td>
							<td colspan="2">Infernal Berserker Juice</td>
							<td colspan="2">Ground Pit Fiend Horn worth at least 2,500 GP</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>9</td>
							<td colspan="2">Small Keg of Celestial Mead</td>
							<td colspan="2">Honey worth at least 1,250 GP</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>Note: if the quantity of liquid is different (keg to flask, etc.) then the container magically shrinks as the liquid contracts.</p>
					<p>Convenient Links</p>
					<p>Level 3</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00027@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Alchemist's Fire (Flask)</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00163@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Assassin's Blood (Ingested)</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00116@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Cask of Common Wine</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00091@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Keg of Supreme Beer</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>Level 4</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00821@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Common Berserker Juice</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00074@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Greater Alchemist's Fire (Flask)</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00117@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Cask of Greater Wine</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00264@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Keg of Common Mead</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00092@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Keg of Legendary Beer</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>Level 5</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00822@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Greater Berserker Juice</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00121@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Cask of Superior Wine</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00085@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Keg of Celestial Beer</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00266@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Keg of Greater Mead</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00080@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Superior Alchemist's Fire (Flask)</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00174@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Torpor (Ingested)</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>Level 6</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00124@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Cask of Supreme Wine</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00297@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Keg of Superior Mead</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00083@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Supreme Alchemist's Fire (Flask)</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00824@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Superior Berserker Juice</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00175@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Truth Serum (Ingested)</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>Level 7</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00084@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Legendary Alchemist's Fire (Flask)</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00169@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Midnight Tears (Ingested)</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00349@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Cask of Legendary Wine</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00350@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Keg of Supreme Mead</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00825@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Supreme Berserker Juice</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>Level 8</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00073@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Infernal Alchemist's Fire (Flask)</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00826@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Legendary Berserker Juice</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00130@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Cask of Celestial Wine</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00351@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Keg of Legendary Mead</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>Level 9</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00820@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Infernal Berserker Juice</link>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00298@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Small Keg of Celestial Mead</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Transmute Water</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00089>
			<id-00090>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Blinded; Incapacitated; RESIST: all, !psychic</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of graveyard dirt)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a willing creature and put it into a cataleptic state that is indistinguishable from death. For the spell's duration, or until you use an action to touch the target and dismiss the spell, the target appears dead to all outward inspection and to spells used to determine the target's status. The target is blinded and incapacitated, and its speed drops to 0. The target has resistance to all damage except psychic damage. If the target is diseased or poisoned when you cast the spell, or becomes diseased or poisoned while under the spell's effect, the disease and poison have no effect until the spell ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Feign Death</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Necromancy</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Eldritch Knight, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00090>
			<id-00091>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">5</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">piercing</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.brownbear@Incarnate-5eBattles">Brown Bear</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Brown Bear</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bite - Brown Bear</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Polymorph Code</source>
			</id-00091>
			<id-00092>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkbase type="string">fixed</atkbase>
						<atkmod type="number">5</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">slashing</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.brownbear@Incarnate-5eBattles">Brown Bear</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Brown Bear</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Claws - Brown Bear</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Polymorph Code</source>
			</id-00092>
			<id-00093>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">12</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10,d10,d10</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">STR: [-2STR]; STR: 9; DEX: [-2DEX]; DEX: 0; CON: [-2CON]; CON: 6; AC: 0</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.brownbear@Incarnate-5eBattles">Brown Bear</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Wildshape Brown Bear</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Transformation - Brown Bear</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Polymorph Code</source>
			</id-00093>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">3</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: Cook's Utensils</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Clubs, daggers, darts, javelins, maces, quarterstaffs, scimitars, sickles, slings, spears</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Tool: Herbalism kit</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Armor: Light armor, medium armor, shields (druids will not wear armor or use shields made of metal)</name>
			</id-00004>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Mikon</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>race.id-00013@Incarnate-5eExpansion</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<senses type="string">Darkvision 60</senses>
		<size type="string">Tiny</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">7</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">7</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">7</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">20</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">20</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00006_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Agile</name>
				<source type="string">Mikon</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Being so tiny their race has learned to use their agility to compensate. This ability to dodge out of the way of the foe gives them a +2 to AC as long as they are unarmored or wearing custom made light armor.</p>
					<p>Any armor they wear must be custom made to their size.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00006>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mikon Specialty - beasts, fey</name>
				<source type="string">Mikon</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Action Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.mikonspecialty@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Mikon Specialty</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>There is only so much time in school, so Mikons specialize in learning the weaknesses of different types of creatures. All Mikons learn the weaknesses of beasts. At levels 3, 6, 9, 12, 15, 18, and 20 you may learn additional types from: Aberrations, Celestials, Constructs, Dragons, Elementals, Feys, Fiends, Giants, Humanoids, Misons, Monstrosities, Oozes, Plants, Swarms, Undead.</p>
					<p>Knowing the weaknesses not only lets you know their weaknesses, but also grants you a 1d4 increase to your attack rolls.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sprint</name>
				<source type="string">Mikon</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When push comes to shove, Mikon can fly like the wind. They may use a bonus action to enter a spirit. The sprint lasts for 1 minute and allows them to double their regular movement speed. At the end of the sprint they suffer one level of exhaustion.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00004@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Exhaustion</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tiny Capacity</name>
				<source type="string">Mikon</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>As one of the tinniest of creatures, your carrying capacity is limited even further than normal. Your carrying capacity is now 2 times your Strength score.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tiny Weapons</name>
				<source type="string">Mikon</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>As one of the smallest of creatures you cannot use traditional weapons. You are proficient with tiny weapons of any category that your class is normally proficient with. These include:</p>
					<p><b>Simple Melee Weapons:</b></p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-01022@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Acupuncture Needle</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Martial Melee Weapons:</b></p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00178@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Azinga</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Simple Ranged Weapons:</b></p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00179@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Mikon Crossbow</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>Mikon may exchange any number of weapons from their class for the same number of tiny weapons.</p>
					<p>Note: You cannot exchange ammunition for weapons.</p>
					<p>Warning: Acupuncture Needles are extremely expensive. Their alloi has a little bit of adamantine mixed into it so that it does not shatter on contact with iron and steel weapons. They can only be made by very talented smiths. Their availability will vary based on the world as the GM sees fit.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Underfoot</name>
				<source type="string">Mikon</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Action Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.underfoot@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Underfoot</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>Although Mikon are hard to see, they often get underfoot. When someone walks over their space and does not specifically say that they avoid stepping on you, then you are at risk for taking trampling damage. You may use your reaction to dive out of the way (dexterity save DC 13) taking bludgeoning damage according to the following table:</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Size</b></td>
							<td><b>Damage</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Small</td>
							<td>1d4</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Medium</td>
							<td>2d4</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Large</td>
							<td>3d4</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Huge</td>
							<td>4d4</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Gargantuan</td>
							<td>5d5</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>For a creature who has not seen you, stepping on you in this way is part of their regular movement and does not cost an action, bonus action, or free action.</p>
					<p>If a creature has seen you, then they may expend half their movement speed to jump up and down on top of you as a bonus action.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00010>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Accupuncture Needle</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00001</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ammo type="number">0</ammo>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">2</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Mikon Crossbow</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Amunition (range 40/120), loading</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00009</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">1</type>
			</id-00002>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">5 lbs</weight>
	</character>
</root>
