<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:3">
	<paladinhumancityguardoathofdevotion>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">4</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">15</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">-1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">9</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">13</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">11</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<age type="string">32 Middle Aged Adult</age>
		<alignment type="string">Lawful Good</alignment>
		<background type="string">City Guard</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>background.id-00007@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">My honor is my life.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">2</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d10</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<name type="string">Paladin</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>class.propaladin@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">15</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">EP</name>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">6</armor>
				<dexbonus type="string">no</dexbonus>
				<disstealth type="number">1</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">2</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">19</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">80</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">160</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">480</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">143.4</load>
			<max type="number">240</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">300</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">400</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">City Guard - Starting Items</name>
				<source type="string">City Guard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Parcel</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="treasureparcel" recordname="treasureparcels.id-00031@Incarnate-Engine">Starting Items - City Guard</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">One of the Guard</name>
				<source type="string">City Guard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When in a city or town you can always find food and a place to sleep with the local guards garrison. The local Guards will be hesitant to start a fight with you and are likely to come to your aid in a fight, the guards will also believe you except in the face of overwhelming evidence or under the command of a superior. For this effect to apply you must be in a city that you would fit in as a Guard, this is decided by the GM.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lay on Hands</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.layonhands@Incarnate-Engine">Lay on Hands</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>Your blessed touch can heal wounds. You have a pool of healing power that replenishes when you take a long rest. With that pool, you can restore a total number of hit points equal to your paladin level x 5.</p>
					<p>As an action, you can touch a creature and draw power from the pool to restore a number of hit points to that creature, up to the maximum amount remaining in your pool.</p>
					<p>Alternatively, you can expend 5 hit points from your pool of healing to cure the target of one disease or neutralize one poison affecting it. You can cure multiple diseases and neutralize multiple poisons with a single use of Lay on Hands, expending hit points separately for each one.</p>
					<p>This feature has no effect on undead and constructs.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Sense</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>The presence of strong evil registers on your senses like a noxious odor, and a powerful good rings like heavenly music in your ears. As an action, you can open your awareness to detect such forces. Until the end of your next turn, you know the location of any celestial, fiend, or undead within 60 feet of you that is not behind total cover. You know the type (celestial, fiend, or undead) of any being whose presence you sense, but not its identity. Within the same radius you also detect the presence of any place or object that has been consecrated or desecrated, as with the <i>hallow </i>spell.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to 1 + your Charisma modifier. When you finish a long rest, you regain all expended uses.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Smite</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.divinesmite@Incarnate-Engine">Divine Smite</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, when you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one spell slot to deal radiant damage to the target, in addition to the weapon's damage. The extra damage is 2d8 for a 1st-level spell slot, plus 1d8 for each spell level higher than 1st, to a maximum of 5d8. The damage increases by 1d8 if the target is an undead or a fiend.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>By 2nd level, you have learned to draw on divine magic through meditation and prayer to cast spells as a cleric does.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="lists.spells.paladin@Incarnate-Engine">Paladin Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Paladin table shows how many spell slots you have cast your spells. To cast one of your paladin spells of 1st level or higher, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. you regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of paladin spells that are available for you to cast, choosing from the paladin spell list. When you do so, choose a number of paladin spells equal to your Charisma modifier + half your paladin level, rounded down (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you are a 5th-level paladin, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With a Charisma of 14, your list of prepared spells can include four spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination. If you prepare the 1st-level spell <i>cure wounds </i>, you can cast it using a 1st-level or a 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of paladin spells requires time spent in prayer and meditation: at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<h>Spellcasting Ability</h>
					<p>Charisma is your spellcasting ability for your paladin spells, since their power derives from the strength of your convictions. You use your Charisma whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Charisma modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a paladin spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<list>
						<li><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</li>
						<li><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</li>
					</list>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a holy symbol as a spellcasting focus for your paladin spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style - Defense</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you adopt a style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the following options. You can't take a Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.</p>
					<p><b>Defense</b></p>
					<p>While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.fightingstyledefense@Incarnate-Engine">Fighting Style - Defense</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Dueling</b></p>
					<p>When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.fightingstyledueling@Incarnate-Engine">Fighting Style - Dueling</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Great Weapon Fighting</b></p>
					<p>When you roll a 1 or 2 on a damage die for an attack you make with a melee weapon that you are wielding with two hands, you can reroll the die and must use the new roll. The weapon must have the two-handed or versatile property for you to gain this benefit.</p>
					<p><b>Protection</b></p>
					<p>When a creature you can see attacks a target other than you that is within 5 feet of you, you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on the attack roll. You must be wielding a shield.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.fightingstyleprotection@Incarnate-Engine">Fighting Style - Protection</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Oath of Devotion</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>The Oath of Devotion binds a paladin to the loftiest ideals of justice, virtue, and order. Sometimes called cavaliers, white knights, or holy warriors, these paladins meet the ideal of the knight in shining armor, acting with honor in pursuit of justice and the greater good. They hold themselves to the highest standards of conduct, and some, for better or worse, hold the rest of the world to the same standards. Many who swear this oath are devoted to gods of law and good and use their gods' tenets as the measure of their devotion. They hold angels-the perfect servants of good-as their ideals, and incorporate images of angelic wings into their helmets or coats of arms.</p>
					<p><b>Tenets of Devotion</b></p>
					<p>Through the exact words and strictures of the Oath of Devotion vary, paladins of this oath share these tenets.</p>
					<p><i>Honesty. </i>Don't lie or cheat. Let your word be your promise.</p>
					<p><i>Courage. </i>Never fear to act, though caution is wise.</p>
					<p><i>Compassion. </i>Aid others, protect the weak, and punish those who threaten them. Show mercy to your foes, but temper it with wisdom.</p>
					<p><i>Honor. </i>Treat others with fairness, and let your honorable deeds be an example to them. Do as much good as possible while causing the least amount of harm.</p>
					<p><i>Duty. </i>Be responsible for your actions and their consequences, protect those entrusted to your care, and obey those who have just authority over you.</p>
					<p><b>Oath Spells</b></p>
					<p>You gain oath spells at the paladin levels listed.</p>
					<p><u>Oath of Devotion Spells</u></p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Paladin</b></td>
							<td colspan="4"></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>3rd</td>
							<td colspan="4"><i>protection from evil and good </i>, <i>sanctuary</i></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>5th</td>
							<td colspan="4"><i>lesser restoration </i>, <i>zone of truth</i></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>9th</td>
							<td colspan="4"><i>beacon of hope </i>, <i>dispel magic</i></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>13th</td>
							<td colspan="4"><i>freedom of movement </i>, <i>guardian of faith</i></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>17th</td>
							<td colspan="4"><i>commune </i>, <i>flame strike</i></td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00026@Incarnate-Engine">Tenets of Devotion</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00022@Incarnate-Engine">Oath Spells (Devotion)</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00012@Incarnate-Engine">Channel Divinity (Devotion)</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00009@Incarnate-Engine">Aura of Devotion</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00023@Incarnate-Engine">Purity of Spirit</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00019@Incarnate-Engine">Holy Nimbus</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tenets of Devotion</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specialization type="string">Oath of Devotion</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Through the exact words and strictures of the Oath of Devotion vary, paladins of this oath share these tenets.</p>
					<p><i>Honesty. </i>Don't lie or cheat. Let your word be your promise.</p>
					<p><i>Courage. </i>Never fear to act, though caution is wise.</p>
					<p><i>Compassion. </i>Aid others, protect the weak, and punish those who threaten them. Show mercy to your foes, but temper it with wisdom.</p>
					<p><i>Honor. </i>Treat others with fairness, and let your honorable deeds be an example to them. Do as much good as possible while causing the least amount of harm.</p>
					<p><i>Duty. </i>Be responsible for your actions and their consequences, protect those entrusted to your care, and obey those who have just authority over you.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Channel Divinity (Devotion)</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specialization type="string">Oath of Devotion</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you take this oath at 3rd level, you gain the following two Channel Divinity options.</p>
					<p>When you use your Channel Divinity, you choose which effect to create. You must then finish a short or long rest to use your Channel Divinity again.</p>
					<p>Some Channel Divinity effects require saving throws. When you use such an effect from this class, the DC equals your paladin spell save DC.</p>
					<p><b>Sacred Weapon. </b>As an action, you can imbue one weapon that you are holding with positive energy, using your Channel Divinity. For 1 minute, you add your Charisma modifier to attack rolls made with that weapon (with a minimum bonus of +1). The weapon also emits bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light 20 feet beyond that. If the weapon is not already magical, it becomes magical for the duration.</p>
					<p>You can end this effect on your turn as part of any other action. If you are no longer holding or carrying this weapon, or if you fall unconscious, this effect ends.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.sacredweapon@Incarnate-Engine">Sacred Weapon</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Turn the Unholy. </b>As an action, you present your holy symbol and speak a prayer censuring fiends and undead, using your Channel Divinity. Each fiend or undead that can see or hear you within 30 feet of you must make a Wisdom saving throw. If the creature fails its saving throw, it is turned for 1 minute or until it takes damage.</p>
					<p>A turned creature must spend its turns trying to move as far away from you as it can, and it can't willingly move to a space within 30 feet of you. It also can't take reactions. For its action, it can use only the Dash action or try to escape from an effect that prevents it from moving. If there's nowhere to move, the creature can use the Dodge action.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.turntheunholy@Incarnate-Engine">Turn the Unholy</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Health</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.divinehealth@Incarnate-Engine">Divine Health</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>By 3rd level, the divine magic flowing through you makes you immune to disease.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Oath Spells (Devotion)</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specialization type="string">Oath of Devotion</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain oath spells at the paladin levels listed.</p>
					<h>Oath of Devotion Spells</h>
					<p><u>Oath of Devotion Spells</u></p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.protectionfromevilandgood@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 3rd - Protection from Evil and Good</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.sanctuary@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 3rd - Sanctuary</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.lesserrestoration@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 5th - Lesser Restoration</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.beaconofhope@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 9th - Beacon of Hope</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.dispelmagic@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 9th - Dispel Magic</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.freedomofmovement@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 13th - Freedom of Movement</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.guardianoffaith@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 13th - Guardian of Faith</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.commune@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 17th - Commune</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.flamestrike@Incarnate-Engine">Spell: 17th - Flame Strike</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00012>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I will never let injustice pass me by.</flaws>
		<height type="string">6'5&#34;</height>
		<hp>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">28</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Service - Our lot is to lay down our lives for others. (Good)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">-1</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This necklace marks that you are from a particular city and that you were a guard there.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">City Insignia on a Necklace</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Each location and city has their own unifrom so this outfit lets people know where you are from (or at least where you got your clothes) at a glance.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Guard's Unifrom</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">3 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>If you have a pair of shackles, you should really have a key. Ideally you would like a key to that particular pair of shackles, but any key can still be good for a bluff.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Key, to Shackles</name>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">3 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This signiture cloak in the colors of the guard's city make it easy to tell who is in the guard, even on a cold snowy day.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cloak, Guard's</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tiny leather pouch is perfect for keeping your coins close at hand. Just watch out for someone trying to cut it off of your belt.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Coin Pouch - Small</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This pair of shackles is made of good stout iron. It is well forged and has 10 hit points. It takes a DC 20 strength check to break them.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shackles</name>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Shield</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A well crafted shield.</nonidentified>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Shield</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">15 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 slashing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Longsword</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Longsword</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A sharp longsword.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10)</properties>
				<rarity type="string">common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">5</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 piercing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Javelin</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Javelin</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A strong javelin.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Thrown (range 30/120)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">7</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tin box contains a cup and simple cutlery. The box clamps together, and one side can be used as a cooking pan and the other as a plate or shallow bowl.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mess Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Equipment Kits</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<ac type="number">16</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">75 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Made of interlocking metal rings, chain mail includes a layer of quilted fabric worn underneath the mail to prevent chafing and to cushion the impact of blows. The suit includes gauntlets.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Chain Mail</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Chain Mail</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Some well-crafted chain mail armor.</nonidentified>
				<stealth type="string">Disadvantage</stealth>
				<strength type="string">Str 13</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Heavy Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">55</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A holy symbol is a representation of a god or pantheon. It might be an amulet depicting a symbol representing a deity, the same symbol carefully engraved or inlaid as an emblem on a shield, or a tiny box holding a fragment of a sacred relic. A cleric or paladin can use a holy symbol as a spellcasting focus. To use the symbol in this way, the caster must hold it in hand, wear it visibly, or bear it on a shield.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Amulet</name>
				<subtype type="string">Holy Symbol</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00019>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Elvish</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Dwarvish</name>
			</id-00003>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">3</level>
		<name type="string">Paladin - Human - City Guard - Oath of Devotion</name>
		<perception type="number">10</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I like the night patrols best, very peaceful or very not.\nI enjoy being strong and able to protect others.</personalitytraits>
		<powerdisplaymode type="string">action</powerdisplaymode>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<savemod type="number">0</savemod>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<uses type="number">0</uses>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Passive</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Channel Divinity</name>
			</id-00004>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">3</max>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">preparation</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">5</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00021@Incarnate-Engine">Lay on Hands</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lay on Hands</name>
				<prepared type="number">15</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The presence of strong evil registers on your senses like a noxious odor, and a powerful good rings like heavenly music in your ears. As an action, you can open your awareness to detect such forces. Until the end of your next turn, you know the location of any celestial, fiend, or undead within 60 feet of you that is not behind total cover. You know the type (celestial, fiend, or undead) of any being whose presence you sense, but not its identity. Within the same radius you also detect the presence of any place or object that has been consecrated or desecrated, as with the <i>hallow </i>spell.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to 1 + your Charisma modifier. When you finish a long rest, you regain all expended uses.</p>
				</description>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Sense</name>
				<prepared type="number">3</prepared>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Protection from Evil and Good; IMMUNE: charmed,frightened,possessed;(C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">IF: TYPE(aberration, celestial, elemental, fey, fiend, undead); IFT: CUSTOM(Protection from Evil and Good);DISATK; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (holy water or powdered silver and iron, which the spell consumes)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Until the spell ends, one willing creature you touch is protected against certain types of creatures: aberrations, celestials, elementals, fey, fiends, and undead. The protection grants several benefits. Creatures of those types have disadvantage on attack rolls against the target. The target also can't be charmed, frightened, or possessed by them. If the target is already charmed, frightened, or possessed by such a creature, the target has advantage on any new saving throw against the relevant effect.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Protection from Evil and Good - Devotion</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Paladin, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">NOTE: Sanctuary</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a small silver mirror)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You ward a creature within range against attack. Until the spell ends, any creature who targets the warded creature with an attack or a harmful spell must first make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, the creature must choose a new target or lose the attack or spell. This spell doesn't protect the warded creature from area effects, such as the explosion of a fireball. If the warded creature makes an attack or casts a spell that affects an enemy creature, this spell ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sanctuary - Devotion</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature and can end either one disease or one condition afflicting it. The condition can be blinded, deafened, paralyzed, or poisoned.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lesser Restoration - Devotion</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Beacon of Hope; ADVSAV: wisdom; ADVSAV: death; NOTE: Receive Max Healing; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell bestows hope and vitality. Choose any number of creatures within range. For the duration, each target has advantage on Wisdom saving throws and death saving throws, and regains the maximum number of hit points possible from any healing.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Beacon of Hope - Devotion</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Cleric Life Domain</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose one creature, object, or magical effect within range. Any spell of 3rd level or lower on the target ends. For each spell of 4th level or higher on the target, make an ability check using your spellcasting ability. The DC equals 10 + the spell's level. On a successful check, the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher, you automatically end the effects of a spell on the target if the spell's level is equal to or less than the level of the spell slot you used.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dispel Magic - Devotion</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a leather strap, bound around the arm or a similar appendage)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a willing creature. For the duration, the target's movement is unaffected by difficult terrain, and spells and other magical effects can neither reduce the target's speed nor cause the target to be paralyzed or restrained. The target can also spend 5 feet of movement to automatically escape from nonmagical restraints, such as manacles or a creature that has it grappled. Finally, being underwater imposes no penalties on the target's movement or attacks.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Freedom of Movement - Devotion</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">8</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">NOTE: Guardian of Faith</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">20</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A Large spectral guardian appears and hovers for the duration in an unoccupied space of your choice that you can see within range. The guardian occupies that space and is indistinct except for a gleaming sword and shield emblazoned with the symbol of your deity. Any creature hostile to you that moves to a space within 10 feet of the guardian for the first time on a turn must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw. The creature takes 20 radiant damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. The guardian vanishes when it has dealt a total of 60 damage.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Guardian of Faith - Devotion</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric Life Domain</source>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 minute</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (incense and a vial of holy or unholy water)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You contact your deity or a divine proxy and ask up to three questions that can be answered with a yes or no. You must ask your questions before the spell ends. You receive a correct answer for each question. Divine beings aren't necessarily omniscient, so you might receive &#34;unclear&#34; as an answer if a question pertains to information that lies beyond the deity's knowledge. In a case where a one-word answer could be misleading or contrary to the deity's interests, the GM might offer a short phrase as an answer instead. If you cast the spell two or more times before finishing your next long rest, there is a cumulative 25 percent chance for each casting after the first that you get no answer. The GM makes this roll in secret.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">5</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Commune - Devotion</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
							<id-00002>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00002>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (pinch of sulfur)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A vertical column of divine fire roars down from the heavens in a location you specify. Each creature in a 10-foot-radius, 40-foot-high cylinder centered on a point within range must make a Dexterity saving throw. A creature takes 4d6 fire damage and 4d6 radiant damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 6th level or higher, the fire damage or the radiant damage (your choice) increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 5th.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">5</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Flame Strike - Devotion</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">charisma</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create a magical zone that guards against deception in a 15-foot-radius sphere centered on a point of your choice within range. Until the spell ends, a creature that enters the spell's area for the first time on a turn or starts its turn there must make a Charisma saving throw. On a failed save, a creature can't speak a deliberate lie while in the radius. You know whether each creature succeeds or fails on its saving throw. An affected creature is aware of the spell and can thus avoid answering questions to which it would normally respond with a lie. Such a creature can be evasive in its answers as long as it remains within the boundaries of the truth.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Zone of Truth - Devotion</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Paladin</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">day</durunit>
						<label type="string">Divine Health; IMMUNE: disease</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00014@Incarnate-Engine">Divine Health</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Passive</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Health</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">ATK: 1, melee; DMGTYPE: magic</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00012@Incarnate-Engine">Channel Divinity (Devotion)</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Channel Divinity</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sacred Weapon</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcbase type="string">ability</savedcbase>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savedcstat type="string">charisma</savedcstat>
						<savemagic type="number">0</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Turned</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.propaladin.features.id-00012@Incarnate-Engine">Channel Divinity (Devotion)</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Channel Divinity</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Turn the Unholy</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">ATK: 1d4; SAVE: 1d4; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a sprinkling of holy water)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You bless up to three creatures of your choice within range. Whenever a target makes an attack roll or a saving throw before the spell ends, the target can roll a d4 and add the number rolled to the attack roll or saving throw.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bless</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Paladin</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You speak a one-word command to a creature you can see within range. The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or follow the command on its next turn. The spell has no effect if the target is undead, if it doesn't understand your language, or if your command is directly harmful to it. Some typical commands and their effects follow. You might issue a command other than one described here. If you do so, the GM determines how the target behaves. If the target can't follow your command, the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>Approach </b>. The target moves toward you by the shortest and most direct route, ending its turn if it moves within 5 feet of you.</p>
					<p><b>Drop </b>. The target drops whatever it is holding and then ends its turn.</p>
					<p><b>Flee </b>. The target spends its turn moving away from you by the fastest available means.</p>
					<p><b>Grovel </b>. The target falls prone and then ends its turn. Halt. The target doesn't move and takes no actions. A flying creature stays aloft, provided that it is able to do so. If it must move to stay aloft, it flies the minimum distance needed to remain in the air.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can affect one additional creature for each slot level above 1st. The creatures must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Command</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Paladin</source>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch regains a number of hit points equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cure Wounds</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Detect Evil and Good; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you know if there is an aberration, celestial, elemental, fey, fiend, or undead within 30 feet of you, as well as where the creature is located. Similarly, you know if there is a place or object within 30 feet of you that has been magically consecrated or desecrated. The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Evil and Good</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Paladin</source>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Detect Magic; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any. The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Magic</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Detect Poison and Disease; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a yew leaf)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you can sense the presence and location of poisons, poisonous creatures, and diseases within 30 feet of you. You also identify the kind of poison, poisonous creature, or disease in each case. The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Poison and Disease</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Divine Favor; DMG: 1d4 radiant; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your prayer empowers you with divine radiance. Until the spell ends, your weapon attacks deal an extra 1d4 radiant damage on a hit.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Favor</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Heroism; IMMUNE: frightened;(C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A willing creature you touch is imbued with bravery. Until the spell ends, the creature is immune to being frightened and gains temporary hit points equal to your spellcasting ability modifier at the start of each of its turns. When the spell ends, the target loses any remaining temporary hit points from this spell.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heroism</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Paladin</source>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>All nonmagical food and drink within a 5-foot-radius sphere centered on a point of your choice within range is purified and rendered free of poison and disease.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Purify Food and Drink</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin</source>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00025>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Shield of Faith; AC: 2; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a small parchment with a bit of holy text written on it)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A shimmering field appears and surrounds a creature of your choice within range, granting it a +2 bonus to AC for the duration.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield of Faith</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Paladin</source>
			</id-00025>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">2</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: Horn (Instrument)</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple weapons, martial weapons</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Armor: All armor, shields</name>
			</id-00003>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Human</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>race.id-00010@Incarnate-Engine</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token"></token>
		<traitlist>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">slashing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Longsword</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00008</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Javelin</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Thrown (range 30/120)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00009</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Javelin</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Thrown (range 30/120)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00009</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00003>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">229 Pounds</weight>
	</paladinhumancityguardoathofdevotion>
</root>
