<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:4">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">12</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
				<save type="number">6</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">18</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">12</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">38</age>
		<alignment type="string">Neutral Evil</alignment>
		<background type="string">Dimir Operative</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>reference.backgrounddata.dimiroperative@DD Guildmaster's Guide to Ravnica</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">I spend as much time as I can in the Ismeri Library because I'm certain an information hub operates behind its facade. I want its secrets!</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d6</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<name type="string">Wizard</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.wizard@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">226</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">46</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">86</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">808</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">0</armor>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">12</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<deity type="string">Erebus</deity>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">50</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">100</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">300</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">78.25</load>
			<max type="number">150</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">150</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">100</expneeded>
		<featlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Linguist</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have studied languages and codes, gaining the following benefits:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Increase your Intelligence score by 1, to a maximum of 20.</li>
						<li>You learn three languages of your choice.</li>
						<li>You can ably create written ciphers. Others can't decipher a code you create unless you teach them, they succeed on an Intelligence check (DC equal to your Intelligence score + your proficiency bonus), or they use magic to decipher it.</li>
					</list>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Arcane Recovery</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have learned to regain some of your magical energy by studying your spellbook. Once per day when you finish a short rest, you can choose expended spell slots to recover. The spell slots can have a combined level that is equal to or less than half your wizard level (rounded up), and none of the slots can be 6th level or higher.</p>
					<p>For example, if you're a 4th-level wizard, you can recover up to two levels worth of spell slots. You can recover either a 2nd-level spell slot or two 1st-level spell slots.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>As a student of arcane magic, you have a spellbook containing spells that show the first glimmerings of your true power. See chapter 10 for the general rules of spellcasting and chapter 11 for the wizard spell list.</p>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you know three cantrips of your choice from the wizard spell list. You learn additional wizard cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Wizard table.</p>
					<p><b>Spellbook</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you have a spellbook containing six 1st-level wizard spells of your choice.</p>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Wizard table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of wizard spells that are available for you to cast. To do so, choose a number of wizard spells from your spellbook equal to your Intelligence modifier + your wizard level (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you're a 3rd-level wizard, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With an Intelligence of 16, your list of prepared spells can include six spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination, chosen from your spellbook. If you prepare the 1st-level spell magic missile, you can cast it using a 1st-level or a 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of wizard spells requires time spent studying your spellbook and memorizing the incantations and gestures you must make to cast the spell: at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Intelligence is your spellcasting ability for your wizard spells, since you learn your spells through dedicated study and memorization. You use your Intelligence whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability.</p>
					<p>In addition, you use your Intelligence modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a wizard spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Intelligence modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Intelligence modifier</p>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast a wizard spell as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag and you have the spell in your spellbook. You don't need to have the spell prepared.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use an arcane focus (found in chapter 5) as a spellcasting focus for your wizard spells.</p>
					<p><b>Learning Spells of 1st Level and Higher</b></p>
					<p>Each time you gain a wizard level, you can add two wizard spells of your choice to your spellbook. Each of these spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots, as shown on the Wizard table. On your</p>
					<p>adventures, you might find other spells that you can add to your spellbook (see the &#34;Your Spellbook&#34; sidebar).</p>
					<h>Your Spellbook</h>
					<p>The spells that you add to your spellbook as you gain levels reflect the arcane research you conduct on your own, as well as intellectual breakthroughs you have had about the nature of the multiverse. You might find other spells during your adventures. You could discover a spell recorded on a scroll in an evil wizard's chest, for example, or in a dusty tome in an ancient library.</p>
					<p><b><i>Copying a Spell into the book. </i></b>When you find a wizard spell of 1st level or higher, you can add it to your spellbook if it is of a level for which you have spell slots and if you can spare the time to decipher and copy it. The spells copied into a spellbook must be of a spell level the wizard can prepare.</p>
					<p>Copying a spell into your spellbook involves reproducing the basic form of the spell, then deciphering the unique system of notation used by the wizard who wrote it. You must practice the spell until you understand the sounds or gestures required, then transcribe it into your spellbook using your own notation.</p>
					<p>For each level of the spell, the process takes 2 hours and costs 50gp. The cost represents material components you expend as you experiment with the spell to master it, as well as the fine inks you need to record it. Once you have spent this time and money, you can prepare the spell just like your other spells.</p>
					<p><b><i>Replacing the Book. </i></b>You can copy a spell from your own spellbook into another book-for example, if you want to make a backup copy of your spellbook. This is just like copying a new spell into your spellbook, but faster and easier, since you understand your own notation and already know how to cast the spell. You need spend only 1 hour and 10 gp for each level of the copied spell. If you lose your spellbook, you can use the same procedure to transcribe the spells that you have prepared into a new spellbook. Filling out the remainder of your spellbook requires you to find new spells to do so, as normal. For this reason, many wizards keep backup spellbooks in a safe place.</p>
					<p><b><i>The Book's Appearance </i></b>Your spellbook is a unique compilation of spells, with its own decorative flourishes and margin notes. It might be a plain, functional leather volume that you received as a gift from your master, a finely bound gilt-edged tome you found in an ancient library, or even a loose collection of notes scrounged together after you lost your previous spellbook in a mishap.</p>
					<p>A spellbook doesn't contain cantrips.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">School of Enchantment</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>As a member of the School of Enchantment, you have honed your ability to magically entrance and beguile other people and monsters. Some enchanters are peacemakers who bewitch the violent to lay down their arms and charm the cruel into showing mercy. Others are tyrants who magically bind the unwilling into their service. Most enchanters fall somewhere in between.</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.enchantmentsavant2@DD PHB Deluxe">Enchantment Savant</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.hypnoticgaze2@DD PHB Deluxe">Hypnotic Gaze</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.instinctivecharm6@DD PHB Deluxe">Instinctive Charm</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.splitenchantment10@DD PHB Deluxe">Split Enchantment</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.altermemories14@DD PHB Deluxe">Alter Memories</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Enchantment Savant</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<specialization type="string">School of Enchantment</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning when you select this school at 2nd level, the gold and time you must spend to copy an enchantment spell into your spellbook is halved.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hypnotic Gaze</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<specialization type="string">School of Enchantment</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level when you choose this school, your soft words and enchanting gaze can magically enthrall another creature. A s an action, choose one creature that you can see within 5 feet of you. If the target can see or hear you, it must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw against your wizard spell save DC or be charmed by you until the end of your next turn. The charmed creature's speed drops to 0, and the creature is incapacitated and visibly dazed.</p>
					<p>On subsequent turns, you can use your action to maintain this effect, extending its duration until the end of your next turn. However, the effect ends if you move more than 5 feet away from the creature, if the creature can neither see nor hear you, or if the creature takes damage.</p>
					<p>Once the effect ends, or if the creature succeeds on its initial saving throw against this effect, you can't use this feature on that creature again until you finish a long rest.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dimir Guild Spells</name>
				<source type="string">Dimir Operative</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Prerequisite: Spellcasting or Pact Magic class feature</p>
					<p>For you, the spells on the Dimir Guild Spells table are added to the spell list of your spellcasting class. (If you are a multiclass character with multiple spell lists, these spells are added to all of them.)</p>
					<h>DIMIR GUILD SPELLS</h>
					<p>#ts</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Spell Level</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"><b>Spells</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Cantrip</td>
							<td colspan="3">encode thoughts, mage hand</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>1st</td>
							<td colspan="3">disguise self, sleep</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2nd</td>
							<td colspan="3">detect thoughts, pass without trace</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>3rd</td>
							<td colspan="3">gaseous form, meld into stone, nondetection</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4th</td>
							<td colspan="3">arcane eye, freedom of movement</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>5th</td>
							<td colspan="3">modify memory</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>#te</p>
					<p>Your magic is meant to be subtle and undetectable, but it might pull shadows or clouds of mist around you as you cast your spells. Using the encode thoughts cantrip described below, you can turn a creature's thoughts (including your own) into a thought strand that others can potentially read, share, or steal. These thought strands are treated as valuable currency among the Dimir.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">False Identity</name>
				<source type="string">Dimir Operative</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have more than one identity. The one you wear most of the time makes you appear to be a member of a guild other than House Dimir. You have documentation, established acquaintances, and disguises that allow you to assume that persona and fit into the secondary guild.</p>
					<p>Whenever you choose, you can drop this identity and blend into the guildless masses of the city.</p>
					<p>Consider why you're embedded in the secondary guild. Create a story with your DM, inspired by rolling on the following table or choosing a reason that suits you.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I have trouble trusting anyone but myself.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<hero type="number">0</hero>
		<herodice type="string">d6</herodice>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">1</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">22</total>
			<wounds type="number">16</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Secrets. I collect secrets and never reveal them. (Any)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">2</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>An arcane focus is a special item-an orb, a crystal, a rod, a specially constructed staff, a wand-like length of wood, or some similar item-designed to channel the power of arcane spells. A sorcerer, warlock, or wizard can use such an item as a spellcasting focus, as described in chapter 10.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Crystal</name>
				<subtype type="string">Arcane Focus</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d4 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">7</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tin box contains a cup and simple cutlery. The box clamps together, and one side can be used as a cooking pan and the other as a plate or shallow bowl.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mess Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Equipment Kits</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack (Empty)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">50 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Essential for wizards, a spellbook is a leather-bound tome with 100 blank vellum pages suitable for recording spells.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellbook</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">3</count>
				<damage type="string">1d4 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dart</name>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Ranged Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">0.25</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Common</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string">Dimir Insignia</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>As an action, you can splash the contents of this vial onto a creature within 5 feet of you or throw the vial up to 20 feet, shattering it on impact. In either case, make a ranged attack against a creature or object, treating the acid as an improvised weapon. On a hit, the target takes 2d6 acid damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Acid (Vial)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00017>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string">Vial of fish scales</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string">vial of seaweed</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string">vial of jellyfish stingers</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string">a glass bottle of unidefntified slime</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string">A dark set of commoner's clothes</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A book might contain poetry, historical accounts, information pertaining to a particular field of lore, diagrams and notes on gnomish contraptions, or just about anything else that can be represented using text or pictures. A book of spells is a spellbook (described later in this section).</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Book</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2,700 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 bludgeoning</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Sound</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00011@Incarnate-Syrinscape"><b>Syrinscape : Staff</b></link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>This staff can be wielded as a magic quarterstaff that grants a +2 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with it. It also has the following additional properties. When one of these properties is used, it can't be used again until the next dawn.</p>
					<p><b>Lightning </b>. When you hit with a melee attack using the staff, you can cause the target to take an extra 2d6 lightning damage.</p>
					<p><b>Thunder </b>. When you hit with a melee attack using the staff, you can cause the staff to emit a crack of thunder, audible out to 300 feet. The target you hit must succeed on a DC 17 Constitution saving throw or become stunned until the end of your next turn.</p>
					<p><b>Lightning Strike </b>. You can use an action to cause a bolt of lightning to leap from the staff's tip in a line that is 5 feet wide and 120 feet long. Each creature in that line must make a DC 17 Dexterity saving throw, taking 9d6 lightning damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.</p>
					<p><b>Thunderclap </b>. You can use an action to cause the staff to issue a deafening thunderclap, audible out to 600 feet. Each creature within 60 feet of you (not including you) must make a DC 17 Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, a creature takes 2d6 thunder damage and becomes deafened for 1 minute.</p>
					<p>On a successful save, a creature takes half damage and isn't deafened.</p>
					<p><b>Thunder and Lightning </b>. You can use an action to use the Lightning Strike and Thunderclap properties at the same time. Doing so doesn't expend the daily use of those properties, only the use of this one.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Staff of Thunder and Lightning</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Staff</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A magical staff.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d8)</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Very Rare (requires attunement)</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Arcane Focus</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">200 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Action Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.potionofsuperiorhealing@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Potion of Superior Healing</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You regain hit points when you drink this potion.</p>
					<p>The number of hit points depends on the potion's rarity, as shown in the Potions of Healing table. Whatever its potency, the potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</p>
					<h>Potions of Healing</h>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Potion of .</td>
							<td>Rarity</td>
							<td>HP Regained</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Superior healing</td>
							<td>Rare</td>
							<td>8d4 + 8</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Superior Potion of Healing</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Potion</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">The potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Rare</rarity>
				<type type="string">Potion</type>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00024>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Draconic</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Undercommon</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00005>
				<name type="string">Goblin</name>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<name type="string">Orc</name>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<name type="string">Abyssal</name>
			</id-00007>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">4</level>
		<name type="string">Kruger</name>
		<notes type="string">has a second identity known Krieger the Surgeon, a biomancer\nFound a gem dragon wyrmling corpse and noted its appearance\nhas a thought strand of the Hydromancer's spellbook and can read it via comprehend languages</notes>
		<pc_label_hero type="string">Hero Point</pc_label_hero>
		<perception type="number">11</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I'm good at hiding my true thoughts and feelings.\nI am always calm, no matter what the situation. I never raise my voice or let my emotions control me.</personalitytraits>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">3</prepared>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
			</id-00001>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">4</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">preparation</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Unconscious</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of fine sand, rose petals, or a cricket)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell sends creatures into a magical slumber.</p>
					<p>Roll 5d8; the total is how many hit points of creatures this spell can affect. Creatures within 20 feet of a point you choose within range are affected in ascending order of their current hit points (ignoring unconscious creatures).</p>
					<p>Starting with the creature that has the lowest current hit points, each creature affected by this spell falls unconscious until the spell ends, the sleeper takes damage, or someone uses an action to shake or slap the sleeper awake. Subtract each creature's hit points from the total before moving on to the creature with the next lowest hit points. A creature's hit points must be equal to or less than the remaining total for that creature to be affected.</p>
					<p>Undead and creatures immune to being charmed aren't affected by this spell.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, roll an additional 2d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sleep</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">90 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Warlock (Archfey), Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Putting a finger to your head, you pull a memory, an idea, or a message from your mind and transform it into a tangible string of glowing energy called a thought strand, which persists for the duration or until you cast this spell again. The thought strand appears in an unoccupied space within 5 feet of you as a Tiny, weightless, semisolid object that can be held and carried like a ribbon. It is otherwise stationary.</p>
					<p>If you cast this spell while concentrating on a spell or an ability that allows you to read or manipulate the thoughts of others (such as detect thoughts or modify memory), you can transform the thoughts or memories you read, rather than your own, into a thought strand.</p>
					<p>Casting this spell while holding a thought strand allows you to instantly receive whatever memory, idea, or message the thought strand contains. (Casting detect thoughts on the strand has the same effect.)</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Up to 8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Encode Thoughts</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A spectral, floating hand appears at a point you choose within range. The hand lasts for the duration or until you dismiss it as an action. The hand vanishes if it is ever more than 30 feet away from you or if you cast this spell again.</p>
					<p>You can use your action to control the hand. You can use the hand to manipulate an object, open an unlocked door or container, stow or retrieve an item from an open container, or pour the contents out of a vial. You can move the hand up to 30 feet each time you use it.</p>
					<p>The hand can't attack, activate magic items, or carry more than 10 pounds.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mage Hand</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You make yourself-including your clothing, armor, weapons, and other belongings on your person-look different until the spell ends or until you use your action to dismiss it. You can seem 1 foot shorter or taller and can appear thin, fat, or in between. You can't change your body type, so you must adopt a form that has the same basic arrangement of limbs. Otherwise, the extent of the illusion is up to you.</p>
					<p>The changes wrought by this spell fail to hold up to physical inspection. For example, if you use this spell to add a hat to your outfit, objects pass through the hat, and anyone who touches it would feel nothing or would feel your head and hair. If you use this spell to appear thinner than you are, the hand of someone who reaches out to touch you would bump into you while it was seemingly still in midair.</p>
					<p>To discern that you are disguised, a creature can use its action to inspect your appearance and must succeed on an Intelligence (Investigation) check against your spell save DC.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Disguise Self</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Trickery Domain, Eldritch Knight, Eldritch Invocations, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">8</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">AC: 3</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a piece of cured leather)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a willing creature who isn't wearing armor, and a protective magical force surrounds it until the spell ends. The target's base AC becomes 13 + its Dexterity modifier. The spell ends if the target dons armor or if you dismiss the spell as an action.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mage Armor</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Eldritch Invocations, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 hour</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (10 gp worth of charcoal, incense, and herbs that must be consumed by fire in a brass brazier)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain the service of a familiar, a spirit that takes an animal form you choose: bat, cat, crab, frog (toad), hawk, lizard, octopus, owl, poisonous snake, fish (quipper), rat, raven, sea horse, spider, or weasel. Appearing in an unoccupied space within range, the familiar has the statistics of the chosen form, though it is a celestial, fey, or fiend (your choice) instead of a beast.</p>
					<p>Your familiar acts independently of you, but it always obeys your commands. In combat, it rolls its own initiative and acts on its own turn. A familiar can't attack, but it can take other actions as normal.</p>
					<p>When the familiar drops to 0 hit points, it disappears, leaving behind no physical form. It reappears after you cast this spell again</p>
					<p>While your familiar is within 100 feet of you, you can communicate with it telepathically. Additionally, as an action, you can see through your familiar's eyes and hear what it hears until the start of your next turn, gaining the benefits of any special senses that the familiar has. During this time, you are deaf and blind with regard to your own senses.</p>
					<p>As an action, you can temporarily dismiss your familiar. It disappears into a pocket dimension where it awaits your summons. Alternatively, you can dismiss it forever. As an action while it is temporarily dismissed, you can cause it to reappear in any unoccupied space within 30 feet of you.</p>
					<p>You can't have more than one familiar at a time. If you cast this spell while you already have a familiar, you instead cause it to adopt a new form. Choose one of the forms from the above list. Your familiar transforms into the chosen creature.</p>
					<p>Finally, when you cast a spell with a range of touch, your familiar can deliver the spell as if it had cast the spell. Your familiar must be within 100 feet of you, and it must use its reaction to deliver the spell when you cast it. If the spell requires an attack roll, you use your attack modifier for the roll.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Find Familiar</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">AC: 5</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 reaction, which you take when you are hit by an attack or targeted by the magic missile spell</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>An invisible barrier of magical force appears and protects you. Until the start of your next turn, you have a +5 bonus to AC, including against the triggering attack, and you take no damage from magic missile.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<type type="string">force</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create three glowing darts of magical force. Each dart hits a creature of your choice that you can see within range. A dart deals 1d4 + 1 force damage to its target. The darts all strike simultaneously, and you can direct them to hit one creature or several.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the spell creates one more dart for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Magic Missile</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of soot and salt)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you understand the literal meaning of any spoken language that you hear. You also understand any written language that you see, but you must be touching the surface on which the words are written. It takes about 1 minute to read one page of text.</p>
					<p>This spell doesn't decode secret messages in a text or a glyph, such as an arcane sigil, that isn't part of a written language.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Comprehend Languages</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<label type="string">Charmed</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<label type="string">Incapacitated</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level when you choose this school, your soft words and enchanting gaze can magically enthrall another creature. A s an action, choose one creature that you can see within 5 feet of you. If the target can see or hear you, it must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw against your wizard spell save DC or be charmed by you until the end of your next turn. The charmed creature's speed drops to 0, and the creature is incapacitated and visibly dazed.</p>
					<p>On subsequent turns, you can use your action to maintain this effect, extending its duration until the end of your next turn. However, the effect ends if you move more than 5 feet away from the creature, if the creature can neither see nor hear you, or if the creature takes damage.</p>
					<p>Once the effect ends, or if the creature succeeds on its initial saving throw against this effect, you can't use this feature on that creature again until you finish a long rest.</p>
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hypnotic Gaze</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<specialization type="string">School of Enchantment</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, M (a snake's tongue and either a bit of honeycomb or a drop of sweet oil)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You suggest a course of activity (limited to a sentence or two) and magically influence a creature you can see within range that can hear and understand you.</p>
					<p>Creatures that can't be charmed are immune to this effect. The suggestion must be worded in such a manner as to make the course of action sound reasonable.</p>
					<p>Asking the creature to stab itself, throw itself onto a spear, immolate itself, or do some other obviously harmful act ends the spell.</p>
					<p>The target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, it pursues the course of action you described to the best of its ability. The suggested course of action can continue for the entire duration. If the suggested activity can be completed in a shorter time, the spell ends when the subject finishes what it was asked to do. You can also specify conditions that will trigger a special activity during the duration. For example, you might suggest that a knight give her warhorse to the first beggar she meets. If the condition isn't met before the spell expires, the activity isn't performed.</p>
					<p>If you or any of your companions damage the target, the spell ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Suggestion</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Knowledge Domain, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a copper piece)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you can read the thoughts of certain creatures. When you cast the spell and as your action on each turn until the spell ends, you can focus your mind on any one creature that you can see within 30 feet of you. If the creature you choose has an Intelligence of 3 or lower or doesn't speak any language, the creature is unaffected.</p>
					<p>You initially learn the surface thoughts of the creature-what is most on its mind in that moment. As an action, you can either shift your attention to another creature's thoughts or attempt to probe deeper into the same creature's mind. If you probe deeper, the target must make a Wisdom saving throw. If it fails, you gain insight into its reasoning (if any), its emotional state, and something that looms large in its mind (such as something it worries over, loves, or hates). If it succeeds, the spell ends. Either way, the target knows that you are probing into its mind, and unless you shift your attention to another creature's thoughts, the creature can use its action on its turn to make an Intelligence check contested by your Intelligence check; if it succeeds, the spell ends.</p>
					<p>Questions verbally directed at the target creature naturally shape the course of its thoughts, so this spell is particularly effective as part of an interrogation. You can also use this spell to detect the presence of thinking creatures you can't see. When you cast the spell or as your action during the duration, you can search for thoughts within 30 feet of you. The spell can penetrate barriers, but 2 feet of rock, 2 inches of any metal other than lead, or a thin sheet of lead blocks you. You can't detect a creature with an Intelligence of 3 or lower or one that doesn't speak any language.</p>
					<p>Once you detect the presence of a creature in this way, you can read its thoughts for the rest of the duration as described above, even if you can't see it, but it must still be within range.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Thoughts</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Warlock (Great Old One), Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (ashes from a burned leaf of mistletoe and a sprig of spruce)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A veil of shadows and silence radiates from you, masking you and your companions from detection. For the duration, each creature you choose within 30 feet of you (including you) has a +10 bonus to Dexterity (Stealth) checks and can't be tracked except by magical means. A creature that receives this bonus leaves behind no tracks or other traces of its passage.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Pass without Trace</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric Trickery Domain, Druid, Druid Grassland Circle, Monk, Ranger</source>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">cold</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a piece of ice or a small white rock chip)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A flurry of magic snowballs erupts from a point you choose within range. Each creature in a 5-foot-radius sphere centered on that point must make a Dexterity saving throw. A creature takes 3d6 cold damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.</p>
					<p>At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Snilloc's Snowball Swarm</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">90 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a piece of string and a bit of wood)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell creates an invisible, mindless, shapeless force that performs simple tasks at your command until the spell ends. The servant springs into existence in an unoccupied space on the ground within range. It has AC 10, 1 hit point, and a Strength of 2, and it can't attack. If it drops to 0 hit points, the spell ends.</p>
					<p>Once on each of your turns as a bonus action, you can mentally command the servant to move up to 15 feet and interact with an object. The servant can perform simple tasks that a human servant could do, such as fetching things, cleaning, mending, folding clothes, lighting fires, serving food, and pouring wine. Once you give the command, the servant performs the task to the best of its ability until it completes the task, then waits for your next command.</p>
					<p>If you command the servant to perform a task that would move it more than 60 feet away from you, the spell ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Unseen Servant</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">S, M (a bit of fleece)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create a sound or an image of an object within range that lasts for the duration. The illusion also ends if you dismiss it as an action or cast this spell again.</p>
					<p>If you create a sound, its volume can range from a whisper to a scream. It can be your voice, someone else's voice, a lion's roar, a beating of drums, or any other sound you choose. The sound continues unabated throughout the duration, or you can make discrete sounds at different times before the spell ends.</p>
					<p>If you create an image of an object-such as a chair, muddy footprints, or a small chest-it must be no larger than a 5-foot cube. The image can't create sound, light, smell, or any other sensory effect. Physical interaction with the image reveals it to be an illusion, because things can pass through it.</p>
					<p>If a creature uses its action to examine the sound or image, the creature can determine that it is an illusion with a successful Intelligence (Investigation) check against your spell save DC. If a creature discerns the illusion for what it is, the illusion becomes faint to the creature.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Minor Illusion</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Monk, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<type type="string">cold</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A frigid beam of blue-white light streaks toward a creature within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, it takes 1d8 cold damage, and its speed is reduced by 10 feet until the start of your next turn.</p>
					<p>The spell's damage increases by 1d8 when you reach 5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ray of Frost</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00018>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">2</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Daggers, darts, slings, quarterstaffs, light crossbows</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Tool: Disguise kit</name>
			</id-00002>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Human-Variant</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.human_variant@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00007_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Skills</name>
				<source type="string">Human-Variant</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain proficiency in one skill of your choice.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Feat</name>
				<source type="string">Human-Variant</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain one feat of your choice.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00002</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00002</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dart</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00012</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<attackbonus type="number">2</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Staff of Thunder and Lightning</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d8)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00023</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00004>
		</weaponlist>
	</character>
</root>
