<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:3">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">-1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">9</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">15</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">4</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">15</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">268 (ageless)</age>
		<alignment type="string">Lawful Neutral</alignment>
		<background type="string">Doctor</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>background.id-00009@Incarnate-5eExpansion</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">I owe everything to my home village/clan, for pooling their resources to have me educated.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d8</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<name type="string">Cleric</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>class.procleric@Incarnate-5eExpansion</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">35</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">23</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">EP</name>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">28</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">6</armor>
				<dexbonus type="string">no</dexbonus>
				<disstealth type="number">1</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">2</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">18</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">75</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">150</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">450</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">150.1</load>
			<max type="number">225</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">373</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">400</expneeded>
		<featlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Doctor</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Doctor</h>
					<p>Prerequisites: Intelligence or Wisdom 13 or higher</p>
					<p>You are an expert at helping a body heal itself.</p>
					<list>
						<li>You may tend to up to 6 creatures over the course of a short rest as 'light work'. Creatures you tend to may use your proficiency bonus in place of their constitution modifier when they expend hit dice to regain hit points.</li>
						<li>As an action you may expend a use of a healers kit to tend to a creature and end one disease or condition affecting that creature, or restore the creature's hit point maximum to its original value. The condition can be blinded, deafened, paralyzed or poisoned. Conditions from permanent injuries cannot be removed until the injury is cured. The creature cannot benefit from this feat again until it finishes a short or long rest.</li>
						<li>You may use 5 minutes to examine an individual. This allows you to identify one poison or disease affecting that creature that you were previously unaware of. You must be within 5 feet of the creature and be able to clearly see the target.</li>
						<li>If you take an hour each day to tend to a creature while they are recovering, that creatures recovery time is reduced by half.</li>
					</list>
					<linklist>
						<link class="url" recordname="http://www.dandwiki.com/wiki/Doctor_(5e_Feat)">Online copy</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Burden of Life</name>
				<source type="string">Doctor</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Due to your vow, you are expected to cure the ill, regardless of morals or prejudice, even if they are your enemy. It is considered a horrid evil to intentionally kill a doctor for no reason. As such, intelligent enemies are less likely to target you, (Provided they are not frighteningly evil in a manner that would be inappropriate for younger audiences) and even your enemy patients will at least not attack immediately while under your care. What happens after they leave your care...? Well you can't decide their fate. Restored individuals may be grateful, or feel some form of life-debt to you. Enemies may repay you by specifically choosing not to kill you, or they may give free information, or a scout you once saved may turn a blind eye to your presence.</p>
					<p>Provided you stay true to your vow, (as best as you can) you can make use of any hospital or medical facility, (typically located in churches, noble estates, universities, and other places of higher learning) as temporary residence for yourself, your patient(s), and your companions if there is room for them. Doctors will put you up at a lifestyle one step below their own if you can maintain a good relationship with them.</p>
					<p>However, if ever you are proven to have broken your vow, you will be fully and publicly discredited as a doctor, and other doctors who pay attention to medical society will recognize you as such. You and all who are with you will be turned away from mundane medicine and the places it is provided. Because you swore on your life, breaking your vow is technically a personal death sentence, though no doctor true to his vows is free to enact it upon you. Even so, more enlightened nations are likely to have laws regarding the treatment of doctors and their vows, and enlightened does not necessarily mean &#34;kind&#34; or &#34;gentle&#34;.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Life Domain</name>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>The Life domain focuses on the vibrant positive energy - one of the fundamental forces of the universe - that sustains all life. The gods of life promote vitality and health through healing the sick and wounded, caring for those in need, and driving away the forces of death and undeath. Almost any non-evil deity can claim influence over this domain, particularly agricultural deities, sun gods, gods of healing or endurance, and gods of home and community.</p>
					<h>Life Domain Spells</h>
					<p><b>Cleric Level - Spell</b></p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.bless@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Spell: 1st - Bless</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.curewounds@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Spell: 1st - Cure Wounds</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.lesserrestoration@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Spell: 3rd - Lesser Restoration</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.spiritualweapon@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Spell: 3rd - Spiritual Weapon</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.beaconofhope@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Spell: 5th - Beacon of Hope</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.revivify@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Spell: 5th - Revivify</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.deathward@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Spell: 7th - Death Ward</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.guardianoffaith@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Spell: 7th - Guardian of Faith</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.masscurewounds@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Spell: 9th - Mass Cure Wounds</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.raisedead@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Spell: 9th - Raise Dead</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Features</h>
					<p>1</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.procleric.features.id-00007@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Bonus Proficiency (Life)</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.procleric.features.id-00013@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Disciple of Life</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>2</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.procleric.features.id-00011@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Channel Divinity: </link><b><i>Preserve Life</i></b></linklist>
					<p>6</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.procleric.features.id-00006@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Blessed Healer</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>8</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.procleric.features.id-00017@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Divine Strike</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>17</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.procleric.features.id-00019@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Supreme Healing</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Disciple of Life</name>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
				<specialization type="string">Life Domain</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.discipleoflife@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Disciple of Life</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>Also starting at 1st level, your healing spells are more effective. Whenever you use a spell of 1st level or higher to restore hit points to a creature, the creature regains additional hit points equal to 2 + the spell's level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bonus Proficiency (Life)</name>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
				<specialization type="string">Life Domain</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you choose this domain at 1st level, you gain proficiency with heavy armor.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>As a conduit for divine power, you can cast cleric spells.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="lists.spells.cleric@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Cleric Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you know three cantrips of your choice from the cleric spell list. You learn additional cleric cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Cleric table.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00036@Incarnate-5eExpansion">The Cleric</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Cleric table shows how many spells slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of cleric spells that are available for you to cast, choosing from the cleric spell list. When you do so, choose a number of cleric spells equal to your Wisdom modifier + your cleric level (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you are a 3rd-level cleric, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With a Wisdom of 16, your list of prepared spells can include six spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination. If you prepare the 1st-level spell <i>cure wounds </i>, you can cast it using a 1st-level or 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of cleric spells requires time spent in prayer and meditation: at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Wisdom is your spellcasting ability for your cleric spells. The power of your spells comes from your devotion to your deity. You use your Wisdom whenever a cleric spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you sue your Wisdom modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a cleric spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<list>
						<li><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</li>
						<li><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</li>
					</list>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast a cleric spell as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag and you have the spell prepared.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a holy symbol (see &#34;Equipment&#34;) as a spellcasting focus for your cleric spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Channel Divinity: Preserve Life</name>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
				<specialization type="string">Life Domain</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can use your Channel Divinity to heal the badly injured.</p>
					<p>As an action, you present your holy symbol and evoke healing energy that can restore a number of hit points equal to five times your cleric level. Choose any creatures within 30 feet of you, and divide those hitpoints among them. This feature can restore a creature to no more than half of its hit point maximum. You can't use this feature on an undead or construct.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Channel Divinity</name>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you gain the ability to channel divine energy directly from your deity, using that energy to fuel magical effects. You start with two such effects: Turn Undead and an effect determined by your domain. Some domains grant you additional effects as you advance in levels, as noted in the domain description.</p>
					<p>When you use your Channel Divinity, you choose which effect to create. You must then finish a short or long rest to use your Channel Divinity again.</p>
					<p>Some Channel Divinity effects require saving throws. When you use such an effect from this class, the DC equals your cleric spell save DC.</p>
					<p>Beginning at 6th level, you can use your Channel Divinity twice between rests, and beginning at 18th level, you can use it three times between rests. When you finish a short or long rest, you regain your expended uses.</p>
					<p><b>Channel Divinity: Turn Undead</b></p>
					<p>As an action, you present your holy symbol and speak a prayer censuring the undead. Each undead that can see or hear you within 30 feet of you must make a Wisdom saving throw. If the creature fails its saving throw, it is turned for 1 minute or until it takes any damage.</p>
					<p>A turned creature must spend its turns trying to move as far away from you as it can, and it can't willingly move to a space within 30 feet of you. It also can't take reactions. For its action it can use only the Dash action or try to escape from an effect that prevents it from moving. If there's nowhere to move, the creature can use the Dodge action.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I feel contempt for many of my patients.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">4' 10&#34;</height>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">24</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Honor - I swore my oath, and now I must live by its tenets. (Lawful)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">-1</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 bludgeoning</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mace</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Mace</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A strong mace, got anything to smash?</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">-</properties>
				<rarity type="string">common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ac type="number">16</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">75 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Made of interlocking metal rings, chain mail includes a layer of quilted fabric worn underneath the mail to prevent chafing and to cushion the impact of blows. The suit includes gauntlets.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Chain Mail</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Chain Mail</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Some well-crafted chain mail armor.</nonidentified>
				<stealth type="string">Disadvantage</stealth>
				<strength type="string">Str 13</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Heavy Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">55</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Crossbow Bolts (20)</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Crossbow Bolts (20)</nonid_name>
				<subtype type="string">Ammunition</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">1.5</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 piercing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Crossbow, Light</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Crossbow, Light</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A light crossbow.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Ammunition (range 80/320), loading, two-handed</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Ranged Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack (Empty)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tin box contains a cup and simple cutlery. The box clamps together, and one side can be used as a cooking pan and the other as a plate or shallow bowl.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mess Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Equipment Kits</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Shield</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A well crafted shield.</nonidentified>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Shield</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A holy symbol is a representation of a god or pantheon. It might be an amulet depicting a symbol representing a deity, the same symbol carefully engraved or inlaid as an emblem on a shield, or a tiny box holding a fragment of a sacred relic. A cleric or paladin can use a holy symbol as a spellcasting focus. To use the symbol in this way, the caster must hold it in hand, wear it visibly, or bear it on a shield.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Amulet</name>
				<subtype type="string">Holy Symbol</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">3 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">5</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Even in a culture with many people who smell most strongly, there is some use for soap. Some people even believe that it can help prevent disease!</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bar of Soap</name>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">3 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A small cloth tent that when pitched can fit 2 men.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tent, 2-man</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This is a medical book that has specialized in one field:</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="table" recordname="tables.id-01881@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Medical Book - Field</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Book, Medical</name>
				<rarity type="string">Very Rare</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">20 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>a stethoscope, some splints, a bone saw, and a magnifying glass.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Doctor's Tools</name>
				<rarity type="string">Very Rare</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Artisan's Tools</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Common</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 CP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tiny leather pouch is perfect for keeping your coins close at hand. Just watch out for someone trying to cut it off of your belt.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Coin Pouch - Small</name>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">7</weight>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Blanket</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00022>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Celestial</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Dwarvish</name>
			</id-00003>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">3</level>
		<name type="string">Micheal</name>
		<notes type="string">Specialty: Therapy</notes>
		<perception type="number">12</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I am cold and calculating in my every word and action, even when furious or frightened.</personalitytraits>
		<powerdisplaymode type="string">action</powerdisplaymode>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">3</prepared>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Effect</name>
			</id-00002>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">4</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">2</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">combat</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">level</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have a pool of hit points equal to your character level. As an action you can touch a character and heal them with this pool. Whether you use the entire amount of the pool or not you can only use this ability once per long rest.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Celestial Soothing</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00005>
						<apply type="string">action</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Disciple of Life (Level 1 Spell Slot); HEAL: 3</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00005>
					<id-00006>
						<apply type="string">action</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Disciple of Life (Level 2 Spell Slot); HEAL: 4</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00006>
					<id-00007>
						<apply type="string">action</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Disciple of Life (Level 3 Spell Slot); HEAL: 5</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00007>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="class.procleric.features.id-00013@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Disciple of Life</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Disciple of Life</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>-</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spare the Dying</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Necromancy</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch one willing creature. Once before the spell ends, the target can roll a d4 and add the number rolled to one ability check of its choice. It can roll the die before or after making the ability check. The spell then ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Guidance</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You manifest a minor wonder, a sign of supernatural power, within range. You create one of the following magical effects within range:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Your voice booms up to three times as loud as normal for 1 minute.</li>
						<li>You cause flames to flicker, brighten, dim, or change color for 1 minute.</li>
						<li>You cause harmless tremors in the ground for 1 minute.</li>
						<li>You create an instantaneous sound that originates from a point of your choice within range, such as a rumble of thunder, the cry of a raven, or ominous whispers.</li>
						<li>You instantaneously cause an unlocked door or window to fly open or slam shut.</li>
						<li>You alter the appearance of your eyes for 1 minute.</li>
					</list>
					<p>If you cast this spell multiple times, you can have up to three of its 1-minute effects active at a time, and you can dismiss such an effect as an action.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Thaumaturgy</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">charisma</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">ATK: -1d4; SAVE: -1d4; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a drop of blood)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Up to three creatures of your choice that you can see within range must make Charisma saving throws. Whenever a target that fails this saving throw makes an attack roll or a saving throw before the spell ends, the target must roll a d4 and subtract the number rolled from the attack roll or saving throw.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bane</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">ATK: 1d4; SAVE: 1d4; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a sprinkling of holy water)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You bless up to three creatures of your choice within range. Whenever a target makes an attack roll or a saving throw before the spell ends, the target can roll a d4 and add the number rolled to the attack roll or saving throw.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bless</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Paladin</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You speak a one-word command to a creature you can see within range. The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or follow the command on its next turn. The spell has no effect if the target is undead, if it doesn't understand your language, or if your command is directly harmful to it. Some typical commands and their effects follow. You might issue a command other than one described here. If you do so, the GM determines how the target behaves. If the target can't follow your command, the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>Approach </b>. The target moves toward you by the shortest and most direct route, ending its turn if it moves within 5 feet of you.</p>
					<p><b>Drop </b>. The target drops whatever it is holding and then ends its turn.</p>
					<p><b>Flee </b>. The target spends its turn moving away from you by the fastest available means.</p>
					<p><b>Grovel </b>. The target falls prone and then ends its turn. Halt. The target doesn't move and takes no actions. A flying creature stays aloft, provided that it is able to do so. If it must move to stay aloft, it flies the minimum distance needed to remain in the air.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can affect one additional creature for each slot level above 1st. The creatures must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Command</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Paladin</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a drop of water if creating water or a few grains of sand if destroying it)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You either create or destroy water.</p>
					<p><b>Create Water </b>. You create up to 10 gallons of clean water within range in an open container. Alternatively, the water falls as rain in a 30-foot cube within range, extinguishing exposed flames in the area.</p>
					<p><b>Destroy Water </b>. You destroy up to 10 gallons of water in an open container within range. Alternatively, you destroy fog in a 30-foot cube within range.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you create or destroy 10 additional gallons of water, or the size of the cube increases by 5 feet, for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Create or Destroy Water</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch regains a number of hit points equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cure Wounds</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you know if there is an aberration, celestial, elemental, fey, fiend, or undead within 30 feet of you, as well as where the creature is located. Similarly, you know if there is a place or object within 30 feet of you that has been magically consecrated or desecrated. The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Evil and Good</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Paladin</source>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any. The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Magic</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a yew leaf)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you can sense the presence and location of poisons, poisonous creatures, and diseases within 30 feet of you. You also identify the kind of poison, poisonous creature, or disease in each case. The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Poison and Disease</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">GRANTADVATK</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A flash of light streaks toward a creature of your choice within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes 4d6 radiant damage, and the next attack roll made against this target before the end of your next turn has advantage, thanks to the mystical dim light glittering on the target until then.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Guiding Bolt</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature of your choice that you can see within range regains hit points equal to 1d4 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d4 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Healing Word</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10,d10,d10</dice>
								<type type="string">necrotic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Make a melee spell attack against a creature you can reach. On a hit, the target takes 3d10 necrotic damage.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d10 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Inflict Wounds</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Necromancy</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">IFT: TYPE(aberration, celestial, elemental, fey, fiend, undead); GRANTDISATK; IMMUNE: charmed,frightened,possessed; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (holy water or powdered silver and iron, which the spell consumes)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Until the spell ends, one willing creature you touch is protected against certain types of creatures: aberrations, celestials, elementals, fey, fiends, and undead. The protection grants several benefits. Creatures of those types have disadvantage on attack rolls against the target. The target also can't be charmed, frightened, or possessed by them. If the target is already charmed, frightened, or possessed by such a creature, the target has advantage on any new saving throw against the relevant effect.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Protection from Evil and Good</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Paladin, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>All nonmagical food and drink within a 5-foot-radius sphere centered on a point of your choice within range is purified and rendered free of poison and disease.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Purify Food and Drink</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin</source>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">NOTE: Sanctuary</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a small silver mirror)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You ward a creature within range against attack. Until the spell ends, any creature who targets the warded creature with an attack or a harmful spell must first make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, the creature must choose a new target or lose the attack or spell. This spell doesn't protect the warded creature from area effects, such as the explosion of a fireball. If the warded creature makes an attack or casts a spell that affects an enemy creature, this spell ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sanctuary</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">AC: 2; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a small parchment with a bit of holy text written on it)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A shimmering field appears and surrounds a creature of your choice within range, granting it a +2 bonus to AC for the duration.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield of Faith</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Paladin</source>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">5</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a tiny strip of white cloth)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your spell bolsters your allies with toughness and resolve. Choose up to three creatures within range. Each target's hit point maximum and current hit points increase by 5 for the duration.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, a target's hit points increase by an additional 5 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Aid</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Paladin</source>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 minute</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (specially marked sticks, bones, or similar tokens worth at least 25 GP)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>By casting gem-inlaid sticks, rolling dragon bones, laying out ornate cards, or employing some other divining tool, you receive an omen from an otherworldly entity about the results of a specific course of action that you plan to take within the next 30 minutes. The GM chooses from the following possible omens:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Weal, for good results</li>
						<li>Woe, for bad results</li>
						<li>Weal and woe, for both good and bad results</li>
						<li>Nothing, for results that aren't especially good or bad</li>
					</list>
					<p>The spell doesn't take into account any possible circumstances that might change the outcome, such as the casting of additional spells or the loss or gain of a companion. If you cast the spell two or more times before completing your next long rest, there is a cumulative 25 percent chance for each casting after the first that you get a random reading. The GM makes this roll in secret.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Augury</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Blinded; NOTE: End of Round Save</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Deafened; NOTE: End of Round Save</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can blind or deafen a foe. Choose one creature that you can see within range to make a Constitution saving throw. If it fails, the target is either blinded or deafened (your choice) for the duration. At the end of each of its turns, the target can make a Constitution saving throw. On a success, the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Blindness/Deafness</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Necromancy</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Sorcerer, Wizard</source>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">charisma</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You attempt to suppress strong emotions in a group of people. Each humanoid in a 20-foot-radius sphere centered on a point you choose within range must make a Charisma saving throw; a creature can choose to fail this saving throw if it wishes. If a creature fails its saving throw, choose one of the following two effects. You can suppress any effect causing a target to be charmed or frightened. When this spell ends, any suppressed effect resumes, provided that its duration has not expired in the meantime. Alternatively, you can make a target indifferent about creatures of your choice that it is hostile toward. This indifference ends if the target is attacked or harmed by a spell or if it witnesses any of its friends being harmed. When the spell ends, the creature becomes hostile again, unless the GM rules otherwise.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Calm Emotions</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric</source>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00025>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (ruby dust worth 50 GP, which the spell consumes)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A flame, equivalent in brightness to a torch, springs forth from an object that you touch. The effect looks like a regular flame, but it creates no heat and doesn't use oxygen. A continual flame can be covered or hidden but not smothered or quenched.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Until dispelled</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Continual Flame</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Wizard</source>
			</id-00025>
			<id-00026>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: constitution; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: strength; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: dexterity; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">4</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
					<id-00005>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: charisma; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">5</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00005>
					<id-00006>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: intelligence; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">6</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00006>
					<id-00007>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVCHK: wisdom; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">7</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00007>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (fur or a feather from a beast)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature and bestow upon it a magical enhancement. Choose one of the following effects; the target gains that effect until the spell ends.</p>
					<p>Bear's Endurance. The target has advantage on Constitution checks. It also gains 2d6 temporary hit points, which are lost when the spell ends.</p>
					<p>Bull's Strength. The target has advantage on Strength checks, and his or her carrying capacity doubles.</p>
					<p>Cat's Grace. The target has advantage on Dexterity checks. It also doesn't take damage from falling 20 feet or less if it isn't incapacitated.</p>
					<p>Eagle's Splendor. The target has advantage on Charisma checks.</p>
					<p>Fox's Cunning. The target has advantage on Intelligence checks.</p>
					<p>Owl's Wisdom. The target has advantage on Wisdom checks.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour.</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Enhance Ability</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Sorcerer</source>
			</id-00026>
			<id-00027>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You sense the presence of any trap within range that is within line of sight. A trap, for the purpose of this spell, includes anything that would inflict a sudden or unexpected effect you consider harmful or undesirable, which was specifically intended as such by its creator. Thus, the spell would sense an area affected by the alarm spell, a glyph of warding, or a mechanical pit trap, but it would not reveal a natural weakness in the floor, an unstable ceiling, or a hidden sinkhole. This spell merely reveals that a trap is present. You don't learn the location of each trap, but you do learn the general nature of the danger posed by a trap you sense.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Find Traps</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Ranger</source>
			</id-00027>
			<id-00028>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of salt and one copper piece placed on each of the corpse's eyes, which must remain there for the duration)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a corpse or other remains. For the duration, the target is protected from decay and can't become undead. The spell also effectively extends the time limit on raising the target from the dead, since days spent under the influence of this spell don't count against the time limit of spells such as raise dead.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">10 days</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Gentle Repose</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Necromancy</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Wizard</source>
			</id-00028>
			<id-00029>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Paralyzed; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a small, straight piece of iron)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose a humanoid that you can see within range. The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be paralyzed for the duration. At the end of each of its turns, the target can make another Wisdom saving throw. On a success, the spell ends on the target.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you can target one additional humanoid for each slot level above 2nd. The humanoids must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hold Person</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00029>
			<id-00030>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature and can end either one disease or one condition afflicting it. The condition can be blinded, deafened, paralyzed, or poisoned.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lesser Restoration</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00030>
			<id-00031>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a forked twig)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Describe or name an object that is familiar to you. You sense the direction to the object's location, as long as that object is within 1,000 feet of you. If the object is in motion, you know the direction of its movement. The spell can locate a specific object known to you, as long as you have seen it up close-within 30 feet-at least once. Alternatively, the spell can locate the nearest object of a particular kind, such as a certain kind of apparel, jewelry, furniture, tool, or weapon. This spell can't locate an object if any thickness of lead, even a thin sheet, blocks a direct path between you and the object.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Locate Object</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger, Wizard</source>
			</id-00031>
			<id-00032>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">10 minutes</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Up to six creatures of your choice that you can see within range each regain hit points equal to 2d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Prayer of Healing</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00032>
			<id-00033>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">ADVSAV: poisoned; RESIST: poison</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature. If it is poisoned, you neutralize the poison. If more than one poison afflicts the target, you neutralize one poison that you know is present, or you neutralize one at random. For the duration, the target has advantage on saving throws against being poisoned, and it has resistance to poison damage.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Protection from Poison</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00033>
			<id-00034>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, no sound can be created within or pass through a 20-foot-radius sphere centered on a point you choose within range. Any creature or object entirely inside the sphere is immune to thunder damage, and creatures are deafened while entirely inside it. Casting a spell that includes a verbal component is impossible there.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Silence</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Ranger</source>
			</id-00034>
			<id-00035>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
								<type type="string">force</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create a floating, spectral weapon within range that lasts for the duration or until you cast this spell again. When you cast the spell, you can make a melee spell attack against a creature within 5 feet of the weapon. On a hit, the target takes force damage equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. As a bonus action on your turn, you can move the weapon up to 20 feet and repeat the attack against a creature within 5 feet of it. The weapon can take whatever form you choose. Clerics of deities who are associated with a particular weapon make this spell's effect resemble that weapon.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels </b>: When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for every two slot levels above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spiritual Weapon</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Cleric Life Domain</source>
			</id-00035>
			<id-00036>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">AC: 1; SAVE: 1; RESIST: all</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pair of platinum rings worth at least 50 GP each, which you and the target must wear for the duration)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell wards a willing creature you touch and creates a mystic connection between you and the target until the spell ends. While the target is within 60 feet of you, it gains a +1 bonus to AC and saving throws, and it has resistance to all damage. Also, each time it takes damage, you take the same amount of damage. The spell ends if you drop to 0 hit points or if you and the target become separated by more than 60 feet. It also ends if the spell is cast again on either of the connected creatures. You can also dismiss the spell as an action.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Warding Bond</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00036>
			<id-00037>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">charisma</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create a magical zone that guards against deception in a 15-foot-radius sphere centered on a point of your choice within range. Until the spell ends, a creature that enters the spell's area for the first time on a turn or starts its turn there must make a Charisma saving throw. On a failed save, a creature can't speak a deliberate lie while in the radius. You know whether each creature succeeds or fails on its saving throw. An affected creature is aware of the spell and can thus avoid answering questions to which it would normally respond with a lie. Such a creature can be evasive in its answers as long as it remains within the boundaries of the truth.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Zone of Truth</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Paladin</source>
			</id-00037>
			<id-00038>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Turned</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you gain the ability to channel divine energy directly from your deity, using that energy to fuel magical effects. You start with two such effects: Turn Undead and an effect determined by your domain. Some domains grant you additional effects as you advance in levels, as noted in the domain description.</p>
					<p>When you use your Channel Divinity, you choose which effect to create. You must then finish a short or long rest to use your Channel Divinity again.</p>
					<p>Some Channel Divinity effects require saving throws. When you use such an effect from this class, the DC equals your cleric spell save DC.</p>
					<p>Beginning at 6th level, you can use your Channel Divinity twice between rests, and beginning at 18th level, you can use it three times between rests. When you finish a short or long rest, you regain your expended uses.</p>
					<p><b>Channel Divinity: Turn Undead</b></p>
					<p>As an action, you present your holy symbol and speak a prayer censuring the undead. Each undead that can see or hear you within 30 feet of you must make a Wisdom saving throw. If the creature fails its saving throw, it is turned for 1 minute or until it takes any damage.</p>
					<p>A turned creature must spend its turns trying to move as far away from you as it can, and it can't willingly move to a space within 30 feet of you. It also can't take reactions. For its action it can use only the Dash action or try to escape from an effect that prevents it from moving. If there's nowhere to move, the creature can use the Dodge action.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Effect</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Channel Divinity</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<usesperiod type="string">enc</usesperiod>
			</id-00038>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">2</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: Medicine Kit</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple weapons</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Armor: Light armor, medium armor, shields, heavy armor</name>
			</id-00003>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Suva</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>race.id-00014@Incarnate-5eExpansion</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<size type="string">medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">4</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">35</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">35</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00006_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Battle Ready</name>
				<source type="string">Suva</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can now draw or stow 2 weapons instead of one and you are proficient with acrobatics.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fiery Devotion</name>
				<source type="string">Suva</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against being charmed or frightened as long as you are within 5ft of an ally.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Celestial Soothing</name>
				<source type="string">Suva</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.celestialsoothing@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Celestial Soothing</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You have a pool of hit points equal to your character level. As an action you can touch a character and heal them with this pool. Whether you use the entire amount of the pool or not you can only use this ability once per long rest.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Compassionate Tone</name>
				<source type="string">Suva</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You are proficient in charisma (persuasion) checks.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00004>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Mace</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00001</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">20</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Crossbow, Light</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00004</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">1</type>
			</id-00002>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">108 lb</weight>
	</character>
</root>
