<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:4">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">13</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">5</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">12</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">-1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">8</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">5</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">17</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">160</age>
		<background type="string">Soldier</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>reference.backgrounddata.soldier@DD 5E Basic Rules - Player</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">Those who fight beside me are those worth dying for.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">0</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d10</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<name type="string">Fighter</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.fighter@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">783</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">36</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">60</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">6</armor>
				<dexbonus type="string">no</dexbonus>
				<disstealth type="number">1</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">16</total>
			</ac>
			<special type="string">precision attack \nsweeping atatck\nriposte</special>
		</defenses>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">85</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">170</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">510</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">139.5</load>
			<max type="number">255</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">379</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">400</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Military Rank</name>
				<source type="string">Soldier</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have a military rank from your career as a soldier. Soldiers loyal to your former military organization still recognize your authority and influence, and they defer to you if they are of a lower rank. You can invoke your rank to exert influence over other soldiers and requisition simple equipment or horses for temporary use. You can also usually gain access to friendly military encampments and fortresses where your rank is recognized.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Second Wind</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have a limited well of stamina that you can draw on to protect yourself from harm. On your turn, you can use a bonus action to regain hit points equal to 1d10 + your fighter level.</p>
					<p>Once you use this feature, you must finish a short or long rest before you can use it again.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You adopt a particular style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the following options. You can't take a Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.</p>
					<p><b>Archery</b></p>
					<p>You gain a +2 bonus to attack rolls you make with ranged weapons.</p>
					<p><b>Defense</b></p>
					<p>While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC.</p>
					<p><b>Dueling</b></p>
					<p>When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.</p>
					<p><b>Great Weapon Fighting</b></p>
					<p>When you roll a 1 or 2 on a damage die for an attack you make with a melee weapon that you are wielding with two hands, you can reroll the die and must use the new roll, even if the new roll is a 1 or a 2. The weapon must have the two-handed or versatile property for you to gain this benefit.</p>
					<p><b>Protection</b></p>
					<p>When a creature you can see attacks a target other than you that is within 5 feet of you, you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on the attack roll. You must be wielding a shield.</p>
					<p><b>Two-Weapon Fighting</b></p>
					<p>When you engage in two-weapon fighting, you can add your ability modifier to the damage of the second attack.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Action Surge</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can push yourself beyond your normal limits for a moment. On your turn, you can take one additional action on top of your regular action and a possible bonus action.</p>
					<p>Once you use this feature, you must finish a short or long rest before you can use it again. Starting at 17th level, you can use it twice before a rest, but only once on the same turn.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Battle Master</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Those who emulate the archetypal Battle Master employ martial techniques passed down through generations. To a Battle Master, combat is an academic field, sometimes including subjects beyond battle such as weapon smithing and calligraphy. Not every fighter absorbs the lessons of history, theory, and artistry that are reflected in the Battle Master archetype, but those who do are well-rounded fighters of great skill and knowledge.</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.combatsuperiority3@DD PHB Deluxe">Combat Superiority</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.studentofwar3@DD PHB Deluxe">Student of War</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.knowyourenemy7@DD PHB Deluxe">Know Your Enemy</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.improvedcombatsuperiority10@DD PHB Deluxe">Improved Combat Superiority</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.relentless15@DD PHB Deluxe">Relentless</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Student of War</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specialization type="string">Battle Master</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level, you gain proficiency with one type of artisan's tools of your choice.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Combat Superiority</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specialization type="string">Battle Master</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you choose this archetype at 3rd level, you learn maneuvers that are fueled by special dice called superiority dice.</p>
					<p><b>Maneuvers. </b>You learn three maneuvers of your choice, which are detailed under &#34;Maneuvers&#34; below. Many maneuvers enhance an attack in some way. You can use only one maneuver per attack.</p>
					<p>You learn two additional maneuvers of your choice at 7th, 10th, and 15th level. Each time you learn new maneuvers, you can also replace one maneuver you know with a different one.</p>
					<p><b>Maneuvers</b></p>
					<p>The maneuvers are presented in alphabetical order.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Maneuver</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"><b>Description</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Commander's Strike</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you take the Attack action on your turn, you can forgo one of your attacks and use a bonus action to direct one of your companions to strike. When you do so, choose a friendly creature who can see or hear you and expend one superiority die. That creature can immediately use its reaction to make one weapon attack, adding the superiority die to the attack's damage roll.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Disarming Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to disarm the target, forcing it to drop one item of your choice that it's holding. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and the target must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, it drops the object you choose. The object lands at its feet.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Distracting Strike</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to distract the creature, giving your allies an opening. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll. The next attack roll against the target by an attacker other than you has advantage if the attack is made before the start of your next turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Evasive Footwork</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you move, you can expend one superiority die, rolling the die and adding the number rolled to your AC until you stop moving.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Feinting Attack.</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">You can expend one superiority die and use a bonus action on your turn to feint, choosing one creature within 5 feet of you as your target. You have advantage on your next attack roll against that creature. If that attack hits, add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll. The advantage is lost if not used on the turn you gain it.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Goading Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to goad the target into attacking you. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and the target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, the target has disadvantage on all attack rolls against targets other than you until the end of your next turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Lunging Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you make a melee weapon attack on your turn, you can expend one superiority die to increase your reach for that attack by 5 feet. If you hit, you add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Maneuvering Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to maneuver one of your comrades into a more advantageous position. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and you choose a friendly creature who can see or hear you. That creature can use its reaction to move up to half its speed without provoking opportunity attacks from the target of your attack.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Menacing Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to frighten the target. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and the target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, it is frightened of you until the end of your next turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Parry</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When another creature damages you with a melee attack, you can use your reaction and expend one superiority die to reduce the damage by the number you roll on your superiority die + your Dexterity modifier.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Precision Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you make a weapon attack roll against a creature, you can expend one superiority die to add it to the roll. You can use this maneuver before or after making the attack roll, but before any effects of the attack are applied.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Pushing Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to drive the target back. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and if the target is Large or smaller, it must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, you push the target up to 15 feet away from you.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Rally</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">On your turn, you can use a bonus action and expend one superiority die to bolster the resolve of one of your companions. When you do so, choose a friendly creature who can see or hear you. That creature gains temporary hit points equal to the superiority die roll + your Charisma modifier.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Riposte</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When a creature misses you with a melee attack, you can use your reaction and expend one superiority die to make a melee weapon attack against the creature. If you hit, you add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Sweeping Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to damage another creature with the same attack. Choose another creature within 5 feet of the original target and within your reach. If the original attack roll would hit the second creature, it takes damage equal to the number you roll on your superiority die. The damage is of the same type dealt by the original attack.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Trip Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to knock the target down. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and if the target is Large or smaller, it must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, you knock the target prone.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p><b>Superiority Dice. </b>You have four superiority dice, which are d8s. A superiority die is expended when you use it. You regain all of your expended superiority dice when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>You gain another superiority die at 7th level and one more at 15th level.</p>
					<p><b>Saving Throws. </b>Some of your maneuvers require your target to make a saving throw to resist the maneuver's effects. The saving throw DC is calculated as follows:</p>
					<p><b>Maneuver save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Strength or Dexterity modifier (your choice)</p>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I made a terrible mistake in battle that cost many lives and I would do anything to keep that mistake secret.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">5'0</height>
		<hero type="number">3</hero>
		<herodice type="string">d6</herodice>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">31</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Nation. My city, nation, or people are all that matter. (Any)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">1</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<ac type="number">16</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">75 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Made of interlocking metal rings, chain mail includes a layer of quilted fabric worn underneath the mail to prevent chafing and to cushion the impact of blows. The suit includes gauntlets.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Chain Mail</name>
				<stealth type="string">Disadvantage</stealth>
				<strength type="string">Str 13</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Heavy Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">55</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">20 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d10 slashing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Glaive</name>
				<properties type="string">Heavy, reach, two-handed</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">2d6 bludgeoning</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Maul</name>
				<properties type="string">Heavy, two-handed</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Crossbow, Light</name>
				<properties type="string">Ammunition (range 80/320), loading, two-handed</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Ranged Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">12 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Includes a backpack, a crowbar, a hammer, 10 pitons, 10 torches, a tinderbox, 10 days of rations, and a waterskin. The pack also has 50 feet of hempen rope strapped to the side of it.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dungeoneer's Pack</name>
				<subtype type="string">Equipment Packs</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">61.5</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Azer head</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">900 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you use an action to toss one of these stones into the air, the stone orbits your head at a distance of 1d3 feet and confers a benefit to you. Thereafter, another creature must use an action to grasp or net the stone to separate it from you, either by making a successful attack roll against AC 24 or a successful DC 24 Dexterity (Acrobatics) check. You can use an action to seize and stow the stone, ending its effect.</p>
					<p>A stone has AC 24, 10 hit points, and resistance to all damage. It is considered to be an object that is being worn while it orbits your head.</p>
					<p><b>Reserve (Rare) </b>. This vibrant purple prism stores spells cast into it, holding them until you use them.</p>
					<p>The stone can store up to 3 levels worth of spells at a time. When found, it contains 1d4 - 1 levels of stored spells chosen by the GM.</p>
					<p>Any creature can cast a spell of 1st through 3rd level into the stone by touching it as the spell is cast.</p>
					<p>The spell has no effect, other than to be stored in the stone. If the stone can't hold the spell, the spell is expended without effect. The level of the slot used to cast the spell determines how much space it uses.</p>
					<p>While this stone orbits your head, you can cast any spell stored in it. The spell uses the slot level, spell save DC, spell attack bonus, and spellcasting ability of the original caster, but is otherwise treated as if you cast the spell. The spell cast from the stone is no longer stored in it, freeing up space.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Magic Stone from a Forgotten Time (Reserve)</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">an old stone with strange writing in a forgotten language</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">-</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Rare (requires attunement)</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Magical Stone</subtype>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">150 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>While you wear these boots, your steps make much less sound. You also have a +2 on Dexterity (Stealth) checks that rely on moving quietly.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rubber Soled Boots</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Boots</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A pair of delicately made boots with funny soles.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00008>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Dwarvish</name>
			</id-00002>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">3</level>
		<name type="string">Ragmyr Axebane</name>
		<pc_label_hero type="string">Hero Point</pc_label_hero>
		<perception type="number">12</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I can stare down a hell hound without flinching.</personalitytraits>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Class</name>
			</id-00002>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">standard</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Dwarven Resilience; RESIST: poison; Advantage on saving throws vs. poison</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against poison, and you have resistance against poison damage (explained in chapter 9).</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dwarf: Dwarven Resilience</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Racial</school>
				<source type="string">Dwarf</source>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10</dice>
								<stat type="string">fighter</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have a limited well of stamina that you can draw on to protect yourself from harm. On your turn, you can use a bonus action to regain hit points equal to 1d10 + your fighter level.</p>
					<p>Once you use this feature, you must finish a short or long rest before you can use it again.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class</group>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Second Wind</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
			</id-00003>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">2</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: One type of gaming set, vehicles (land)</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple weapons, martial weapons</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Armor: All armor, shields</name>
			</id-00003>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Mountain Dwarf</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.dwarf@DD 5E Basic Rules - Player</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<senses type="string">Darkvision 60</senses>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">25</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">25</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00013_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dwarven Resilience</name>
				<source type="string">Dwarf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against poison, and you have resistance against poison damage (explained in chapter 9).</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Stonecunning</name>
				<source type="string">Dwarf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Whenever you make an Intelligence (History) check related to the origin of stonework, you are considered proficient in the History skill and add double your proficiency bonus to the check, instead of your normal proficiency bonus.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dwarven Combat Training</name>
				<source type="string">Dwarf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have proficiency with the battleaxe, handaxe, light hammer, and warhammer.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tool Proficiency</name>
				<source type="string">Dwarf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain proficiency with the artisan's tools of your choice: smith's tools, brewer's supplies, or mason's tools.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dwarven Armor Training</name>
				<source type="string">Mountain Dwarf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have proficiency with light and medium armor.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00005>
		</traitlist>
		<weapon>
			<critdicebonus>
				<melee type="number">0</melee>
				<ranged type="number">0</ranged>
			</critdicebonus>
			<critrange>
				<melee type="number">20</melee>
				<ranged type="number">20</ranged>
			</critrange>
		</weapon>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">1</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d10</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
						<type type="string">slashing, radiant</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dwarven Blessed Glaive</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Heavy, reach, two-handed, REROLL 2</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00002</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
						<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Maul</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Heavy, two-handed, REROLL 2</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00003</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<ammo type="number">4</ammo>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">20</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Crossbow, Light</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Ammunition (range 80/320), loading, two-handed</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00004</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">1</type>
			</id-00003>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">200</weight>
	</character>
</root>
