<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:3">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">11</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">15</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">6</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">13</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">4</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">13</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">49</age>
		<alignment type="string">chaotic neutral</alignment>
		<appearance type="string">Skin: Light Tan, Eye Color: Grey, Hair Color: Grey</appearance>
		<background type="string">Charlatan</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>reference.backgrounddata.charlatan@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">I owe everything to my mentor-a horrible person who's probably rotting in jail somewhere.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d6</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">1</hdused>
				<level type="number">6</level>
				<name type="string">Wizard</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>class.prowizard@Incarnate-5eExpansion</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">946</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">EP</name>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">341</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">334</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<dci type="string">9318734835</dci>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">2</armor>
				<disstealth type="number">0</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">14</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<deity type="string">Hades</deity>
		<effectlist>
		</effectlist>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">65</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">130</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">390</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">93.306</load>
			<max type="number">195</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">674</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">700</expneeded>
		<featlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spell Sniper (PHB: Warlock Cantrip: Eldritch Blast)</name>
				<prerequisite type="string">The ability to cast at least one spell</prerequisite>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p><i>Prerequisite: The ability to cast at least one spell</i></p>
					<p>You have learned techniques to enhance your attacks with certain kinds of spells, gaining the following benefits:</p>
					<list>
						<li>When you cast a spell that requires you to make an attack roll, the spell's range is doubled.</li>
						<li>Your ranged spell attacks ignore half cover and three-quarters cover.</li>
						<li>You learn one cantrip that requires an attack roll. Choose the cantrip from the bard, cleric, druid, sorcerer, warlock, or wizard spell list. Your spellcasting ability for this cantrip depends on the spell list you chose from: Charisma for bard, sorcerer, or warlock; Wisdom for cleric or druid; or Intelligence for wizard.</li>
					</list>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">False Identity (second identity: Book Author writting 'Cat in a Hat')</name>
				<source type="string">Charlatan</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have created a second identity that includes documentation, established acquaintances, and disguises that allow you to assume that persona.</p>
					<p>Additionally, you can forge documents including official papers and personal letters, as long as you have seen an example of the kind of document or the handwriting you are trying to copy.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">L1 Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>As a student of arcane magic, you have a spellbook containing spells that show the first glimmerings of your true power. See chapter 10 for the general rules of spellcasting and chapter 11 for the wizard spell list.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="reference.spelllists.wizard@DD PHB Deluxe">Wizards Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you know three cantrips of your choice from the wizard spell list. You learn additional wizard cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Wizard table.</p>
					<p><b>Spellbook</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you have a spellbook containing six 1st-level wizard spells of your choice.</p>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Wizard table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of wizard spells that are available for you to cast. To do so, choose a number of wizard spells from your spellbook equal to your Intelligence modifier + your wizard level (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you're a 3rd-level wizard, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With an Intelligence of 16, your list of prepared spells can include six spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination, chosen from your spellbook. If you prepare the 1st-level spell magic missile, you can cast it using a 1st-level or a 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of wizard spells requires time spent studying your spellbook and memorizing the incantations and gestures you must make to cast the spell: at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Intelligence is your spellcasting ability for your wizard spells, since you learn your spells through dedicated study and memorization. You use your Intelligence whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability.</p>
					<p>In addition, you use your Intelligence modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a wizard spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Intelligence modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Intelligence modifier</p>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast a wizard spell as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag and you have the spell in your spellbook. You don't need to have the spell prepared.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use an arcane focus (found in chapter 5) as a spellcasting focus for your wizard spells.</p>
					<p><b>Learning Spells of 1st Level and Higher</b></p>
					<p>Each time you gain a wizard level, you can add two wizard spells of your choice to your spellbook. Each of these spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots, as shown on the Wizard table. On your adventures, you might find other spells that you can add to your spellbook (see the &#34;Your Spellbook&#34; sidebar).</p>
					<h>Your Spellbook</h>
					<p>The spells that you add to your spellbook as you gain levels reflect the arcane research you conduct on your own, as well as intellectual breakthroughs you have had about the nature of the multiverse. You might find other spells during your adventures. You could discover a spell recorded on a scroll in an evil wizard's chest, for example, or in a dusty tome in an ancient library.</p>
					<p><b><i>Copying a Spell into the book. </i></b>When you find a wizard spell of 1st level or higher, you can add it to your spellbook if it is of a level for which you have spell slots and if you can spare the time to decipher and copy it. The spells copied into a spellbook must be of a spell level the wizard can prepare.</p>
					<p>Copying a spell into your spellbook involves reproducing the basic form of the spell, then deciphering the unique system of notation used by the wizard who wrote it. You must practice the spell until you understand the sounds or gestures required, then transcribe it into your spellbook using your own notation.</p>
					<p>For each level of the spell, the process takes 2 hours and costs 50gp. The cost represents material components you expend as you experiment with the spell to master it, as well as the fine inks you need to record it. Once you have spent this time and money, you can prepare the spell just like your other spells.</p>
					<p><b><i>Replacing the Book. </i></b>You can copy a spell from your own spellbook into another book-for example, if you want to make a backup copy of your spellbook. This is just like copying a new spell into your spellbook, but faster and easier, since you understand your own notation and already know how to cast the spell. You need spend only 1 hour and 10 gp for each level of the copied spell. If you lose your spellbook, you can use the same procedure to transcribe the spells that you have prepared into a new spellbook. Filling out the remainder of your spellbook requires you to find new spells to do so, as normal. For this reason, many wizards keep backup spellbooks in a safe place.</p>
					<p><b><i>The Book's Appearance </i></b>Your spellbook is a unique compilation of spells, with its own decorative flourishes and margin notes. It might be a plain, functional leather volume that you received as a gift from your master, a finely bound gilt-edged tome you found in an ancient library, or even a loose collection of notes scrounged together after you lost your previous spellbook in a mishap.</p>
					<p>A spellbook doesn't contain cantrips.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">L1 Arcane Recovery (recover spell slots of combined lvl is =&#62; 1/2 wiz lvl, rnd up)</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have learned to regain some of your magical energy by studying your spellbook. Once per day when you finish a short rest, you can choose expended spell slots to recover. The spell slots can have a combined level that is equal to or less than half your wizard level (rounded up), and none of the slots can be 6th level or higher.</p>
					<p>For example, if you're a 4th-level wizard, you can recover up to two levels worth of spell slots. You can recover either a 2nd-level spell slot or two 1st-level spell slots.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">L2 School of Evocation</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You focus your study on magic that creates powerful elemental effects such as bitter cold, searing flame, rolling thunder, crackling lightning, and burning acid. Some evokers find employment in military forces, serving as artillery to blast enemy armies from afar. Others use their spectacular power to protect the weak, while some seek their own gain as bandits, adventurers, or aspiring tyrants.</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.evocationsavant2@DD PHB Deluxe">Evocation Savant</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.sculptspells2@DD PHB Deluxe">Sculpt Spells</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.potentcantrip6@DD PHB Deluxe">Potent Cantrip</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.empoweredevocation10@DD PHB Deluxe">Empowered Evocation</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.overchannel14@DD PHB Deluxe">Overchannel</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">L4 Ability Score Improvement: Spell Sniper Feat</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">L2 Evocation Savant (gp &#38; time = 1/2 for evo spell copying)</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<specialization type="string">School of Evocation</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning when you select this school at 2nd level, the gold and time you must spend to copy an evocation spell into your spellbook is halved.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">L2 Sculpt Spells</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<specialization type="string">School of Evocation</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning at 2nd level, you can create pockets of relative safety within the effects of your evocation spells. When you cast an evocation spell that affects other creatures that you can see, you can choose a number of them equal to 1 + the spell's level. The chosen creatures automatically succeed on their saving throws against the spell, and they take no damage if they would normally take half damage on a successful save.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">L2 Arcane Tradition (school of evocation)</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">1</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>The study of wizardry is ancient, stretching back to the earliest mortal discoveries of magic. It is firmly established in fantasy gaming worlds, with various traditions dedicated to its complex study.</p>
					<p>The most common arcane traditions in the multiverse revolve around the schools of magic. Wizards through the ages have cataloged thousands of spells, grouping them into either categories called schools. In some places, these traditions are literally schools. In other institutions, schools are more like academic departments, with rival faculties competing for students and funding. even wizards who train apprentices in the solitude of their own towers use the division of magic into schools as a learning device, since the spells of each school require mastery of different techniques.</p>
					<p>When you reach 2nd level, you choose an arcane tradition, shaping your practice of magic through one of many schools, such as Evocation.</p>
					<p>Your choice grants you features at 2nd level and again at 6th, 10th, and 14th level.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classability" recordname="class.prowizard.abilities.id-00002@Incarnate-5eExpansion">School of Big Sticks</link>
						<link class="reference_classability" recordname="class.prowizard.abilities.id-00001@Incarnate-5eExpansion">School of Evocation</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">L2 Arcane Deflection (hit by attack, reaction +2 AC; +4 to that saving throw)</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<specialization type="string">War Magic</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you have learned to weave your magic to fortify yourself against harm. When you are hit by an attack or you fail a saving throw, you can use your reaction to gain a +2 bonus to your AC against that attack or a +4 bonus to that saving throw.</p>
					<p>When you use this feature, you can't cast spells other than cantrips until the end of your next turn.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">L2 Tactical Wit (bonus to INIT+3)</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<specialization type="string">War Magic</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, your keen ability to assess tactical situations allows you to act quickly in battle. You can give yourself a bonus to your initiative rolls equal to your Intelligence modifier.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">L2 War Magic</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>A variety of arcane colleges specialize in training wizards for war. The tradition of War Magic blends principles of evocation and abjuration, rather than specializing in either of those schools. It teaches techniques that empower a caster's spells, while also providing methods for wizards to bolster their own defenses.</p>
					<p>Followers of this tradition are known as war mages. They see their magic as both a weapon and armor, a resource superior to any piece of steel. War mages act fast in battle, using their spells to seize tactical control of a situation. Their spells strike hard, while their defensive skills foil their opponents' attempts to counterattack. War mages are also adept at turning other spellcasters' magical energy against them.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="imagewindow" recordname="reference.imagedata.img_warmage_jpg@*"><b>Image: </b></link>War Mage</linklist>
					<p>In great battles, a war mage often works with evokers, abjurers, and other types of wizards. Evokers, in particular, sometimes tease war mages for splitting their attention between offense and defense. A war mage's typical response: &#34;What good is being able to throw a mighty fireball if I die before I can cast it?&#34;</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.arcanedeflection2@*">Arcane Deflection</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.tacticalwit2@*">Tactical Wit</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.powersurge6@*">Power Surge</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.durablemagic10@*">Durable Magic</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.wizard.features.deflectingshroud14@*">Deflecting Shroud</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<name type="string">Item: Ring of Radiant Resistance</name>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<level type="number">6</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">L6 Potent Cantrip</name>
				<source type="string">Wizard</source>
				<specialization type="string">School of Evocation</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 6th level, your damaging cantrips affect even creatures that avoid the brunt of the effect. When a creature succeeds on a saving throw against your cantrip, the creature takes half the cantrip's damage (if any) but suffers no additional effects from the cantrip.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00013>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I'm convinced that no one could ever fool me the way I fool others.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">5' 9&#34;</height>
		<hero type="number">0</hero>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<hdmod type="number">0</hdmod>
			<max type="number">20</max>
			<maxtemporary type="number">0</maxtemporary>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">38</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Independence. I am a free spirit- no one tells me what to do. (Chaotic)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">3</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">5</total>
		</initiative>
		<inspiration type="number">1</inspiration>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This pouch of cosmetics, hair dye, and small props lets you create disguises that change your physical appearance. Proficiency with this kit lets you add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make to create a visual disguise.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Disguise Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Kits / Sets</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">15 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small box contains a variety of papers and parchments, pens and inks, seals and sealing wax, gold and silver leaf, and other supplies necessary to create convincing forgeries of physical documents. Proficiency with this kit lets you add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make to create a physical forgery of a document.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Forgery Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Kits / Sets</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">back</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">15 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">worn</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Fine</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">belt pouch</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Signet Ring</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A cloth or leather pouch can hold up to 20 sling bullets or 50 blowgun needles, among other things. A compartmentalized pouch for holding spell components is called a component pouch (described earlier in this section).</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">belt</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Belt Pouch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 SP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Skill Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_skill" recordname="skill.id-00263@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Dice Set</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<istemplate type="number">0</istemplate>
				<location type="string">belt Pouch</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dice Set</name>
				<subtype type="string">Gaming Set</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">0.2</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">900 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have resistance to one damage type while wearing this ring.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.typeresistanceradiant@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Type Resistance (Radiant)</link>
					</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>9</td>
							<td>Radiant</td>
							<td>Topaz</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">worn</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ring of Radiant Resistance</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Ring</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A topaz ring.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">rare (requires attunement)</rarity>
				<type type="string">Ring</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Soap</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sealing Wax</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.03</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ink (1-ounce Bottle)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.06</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ink Pen</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.02</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Flask Or Tankard</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This ring may be attuned to two creatures at a time, one primary, one secondary. To bind as a primary you must make a competing wisdom save against the current primary owner. If you attune and do not win the competition then you bind to the secondary slot. You cannot choose to unatune it, but someone else may attune to it taking over the secondary slot. You may only attempt to take primary ownership during an equinox.</p>
					<p><b>Binding of Engagement: </b>This ring is attached to your life essence. It magically shrinks to perfectly fit one of your fingers. No one but the primary binding can remove it from you. If you loose the finger/hand/arm then the ring detaches itself and flies to seek out your life essence and reattach itself to you.</p>
					<p><b>Farwatching: </b>the primary individual can see true vision through the ring for 30 ft.</p>
					<p><b>Farspeaking: </b>the primary individual can speak telepathically to the secondary binding.</p>
					<p><b>Prestige 0: at the volcano</b></p>
					<p>Intimidation + 2</p>
					<p><b>Prestige 1: redirected a river to the volcano</b></p>
					<p>Deception + 2</p>
					<p><b>Prestige 2:</b></p>
					<p>Strength + 4</p>
					<p><b>Prestige 3:</b></p>
					<p>Once per day you may scan a 1,000 ft. radius for gold in value of more than 1,000 GP. If there is a source of that degree it points you in the right direction. If there are multiple sources of that strength then it points you towards the closest source.</p>
					<p><b>Prestige 4:</b></p>
					<p>Once per short rest you may cast a lvl 7 darkness from the ring.</p>
					<p>This ring allows you to see normally in dim light, darkness, and magical darkness.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">worn</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ring of Hades - Prestige 1</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Ring of Hades</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Has a cornucopia and a three headed dog on the ring.</nonidentified>
				<weight type="number">0.001</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 bludgeoning</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">hand, right</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Quarterstaff</name>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d8)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard Adventuring Gear</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">7</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard Adventuring Gear</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">9</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard Adventuring Gear</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">priceless</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.heartstone@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Heartstone</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>By concentrating on this stone for 1 minute you are teleported into the Nexus, a place of safety for most adventurers. (It is your ticket back, so guard it with your life.)</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">belt Pouch</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heartstone</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Heartstone</nonid_name>
				<rarity type="string">legendary</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard Adventuring Gear</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tin box contains a cup and simple cutlery. The box clamps together, and one side can be used as a cooking pan and the other as a plate or shallow bowl.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mess Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard Adventuring Gear</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rope, whether made of hemp or silk, has 2 hit points and can be burst with a DC 17 Strength check.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard Adventuring Gear</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">100 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Linked Spell</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.levitate@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Levitate</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>A spell scroll bears the words of a single spell, written in a mystical cipher. If the spell is on your class's spell list, you can read the scroll and cast its spell without providing any material components.</p>
					<p>Otherwise, the scroll is unintelligible. Casting the spell by reading the scroll requires the spell's normal casting time. Once the spell is cast, the words on the scroll fade, and it crumbles to dust. If the casting is interrupted, the scroll is not lost.</p>
					<p>If the spell is on your class's spell list but of a higher level than you can normally cast, you must make an ability check using your spellcasting ability to determine whether you cast it successfully. The DC equals 10 + the spell's level. On a failed check, the spell disappears from the scroll with no other effect.</p>
					<p>The level of the spell on the scroll determines the spell's saving throw DC and attack bonus, as well as the scroll's rarity, as shown in the Spell Scroll table.</p>
					<p>Spell Scroll</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Spell Level</td>
							<td>Rarity</td>
							<td>Save DC</td>
							<td>Attack Bonus</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2nd</td>
							<td>Uncommon</td>
							<td>13</td>
							<td>+5</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>A wizard spell on a spell scroll can be copied just as spells in spellbooks can be copied. When a spell is copied from a spell scroll, the copier must succeed on an Intelligence (Arcana) check with a DC equal to 10 + the spell's level. If the check succeeds, the spell is successfully copied. Whether the check succeeds or fails, the spell scroll is destroyed.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">belt Pouch</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Scroll of Levitate</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Scroll</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Simple Scroll</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Scroll</type>
				<weight type="number">0.3</weight>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00025>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">50 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Essential for wizards, a spellbook is a leather-bound tome with 100 blank vellum pages suitable for recording spells.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellbook</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard Adventuring Gear</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00025>
			<id-00026>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">100 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Linked Spell</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.gentlerepose@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Gentle Repose</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>A spell scroll bears the words of a single spell, written in a mystical cipher. If the spell is on your class's spell list, you can read the scroll and cast its spell without providing any material components.</p>
					<p>Otherwise, the scroll is unintelligible. Casting the spell by reading the scroll requires the spell's normal casting time. Once the spell is cast, the words on the scroll fade, and it crumbles to dust. If the casting is interrupted, the scroll is not lost.</p>
					<p>If the spell is on your class's spell list but of a higher level than you can normally cast, you must make an ability check using your spellcasting ability to determine whether you cast it successfully. The DC equals 10 + the spell's level. On a failed check, the spell disappears from the scroll with no other effect.</p>
					<p>The level of the spell on the scroll determines the spell's saving throw DC and attack bonus, as well as the scroll's rarity, as shown in the Spell Scroll table.</p>
					<p>Spell Scroll</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Spell Level</td>
							<td>Rarity</td>
							<td>Save DC</td>
							<td>Attack Bonus</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>2nd</td>
							<td>Uncommon</td>
							<td>13</td>
							<td>+5</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>A wizard spell on a spell scroll can be copied just as spells in spellbooks can be copied. When a spell is copied from a spell scroll, the copier must succeed on an Intelligence (Arcana) check with a DC equal to 10 + the spell's level. If the check succeeds, the spell is successfully copied. Whether the check succeeds or fails, the spell scroll is destroyed.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">belt Pouch</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Scroll of Gentle Repose</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Scroll</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Simple Scroll</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Scroll</type>
				<weight type="number">0.3</weight>
			</id-00026>
			<id-00027>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">200 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Linked Spell</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.arcaneeye@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Arcane Eye</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>A spell scroll bears the words of a single spell, written in a mystical cipher. If the spell is on your class's spell list, you can read the scroll and cast its spell without providing any material components.</p>
					<p>Otherwise, the scroll is unintelligible. Casting the spell by reading the scroll requires the spell's normal casting time. Once the spell is cast, the words on the scroll fade, and it crumbles to dust. If the casting is interrupted, the scroll is not lost.</p>
					<p>If the spell is on your class's spell list but of a higher level than you can normally cast, you must make an ability check using your spellcasting ability to determine whether you cast it successfully. The DC equals 10 + the spell's level. On a failed check, the spell disappears from the scroll with no other effect.</p>
					<p>The level of the spell on the scroll determines the spell's saving throw DC and attack bonus, as well as the scroll's rarity, as shown in the Spell Scroll table.</p>
					<p>Spell Scroll</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Spell Level</td>
							<td>Rarity</td>
							<td>Save DC</td>
							<td>Attack Bonus</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>4th</td>
							<td>Rare</td>
							<td>15</td>
							<td>+7</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>A wizard spell on a spell scroll can be copied just as spells in spellbooks can be copied. When a spell is copied from a spell scroll, the copier must succeed on an Intelligence (Arcana) check with a DC equal to 10 + the spell's level. If the check succeeds, the spell is successfully copied. Whether the check succeeds or fails, the spell scroll is destroyed.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Scroll of Arcane Eye</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Scroll</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Fine Scroll</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Rare</rarity>
				<type type="string">Scroll</type>
				<weight type="number">0.3</weight>
			</id-00027>
			<id-00028>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">20 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>An arcane focus is a special item-an orb, a crystal, a rod, a specially constructed staff, a wand-like length of wood, or some similar item-designed to channel the power of arcane spells. A sorcerer, warlock, or wizard can use such an item as a spellcasting focus, as described in chapter 10.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">hand, left</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Orb</name>
				<subtype type="string">Arcane Focus</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00028>
			<id-00029>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">100 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This lens allows a closer look at small objects. It is also useful as a substitute for flint and steel when starting fires. Lighting a fire with a magnifying glass requires light as bright as sunlight to focus, tinder to ignite, and about 5 minutes for the fire to ignite. A magnifying glass grants advantage on any ability check made to appraise or inspect an item that is small or highly detailed.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">belt pouch</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Magnifying Glass</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.025</weight>
			</id-00029>
			<id-00030>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">150 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Linked Spell</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.stinkingcloud@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Stinking Cloud</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>A spell scroll bears the words of a single spell, written in a mystical cipher. If the spell is on your class's spell list, you can read the scroll and cast its spell without providing any material components.</p>
					<p>Otherwise, the scroll is unintelligible. Casting the spell by reading the scroll requires the spell's normal casting time. Once the spell is cast, the words on the scroll fade, and it crumbles to dust. If the casting is interrupted, the scroll is not lost.</p>
					<p>If the spell is on your class's spell list but of a higher level than you can normally cast, you must make an ability check using your spellcasting ability to determine whether you cast it successfully. The DC equals 10 + the spell's level. On a failed check, the spell disappears from the scroll with no other effect.</p>
					<p>The level of the spell on the scroll determines the spell's saving throw DC and attack bonus, as well as the scroll's rarity, as shown in the Spell Scroll table.</p>
					<p>Spell Scroll</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Spell Level</td>
							<td>Rarity</td>
							<td>Save DC</td>
							<td>Attack Bonus</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>3rd</td>
							<td>Uncommon</td>
							<td>15</td>
							<td>+7</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p>A wizard spell on a spell scroll can be copied just as spells in spellbooks can be copied. When a spell is copied from a spell scroll, the copier must succeed on an Intelligence (Arcana) check with a DC equal to 10 + the spell's level. If the check succeeds, the spell is successfully copied. Whether the check succeeds or fails, the spell scroll is destroyed.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Scroll of Stinking Cloud</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Scroll</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Scroll</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Scroll</type>
				<weight type="number">0.3</weight>
			</id-00030>
			<id-00031>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">worn</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Robes</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00031>
			<id-00032>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">100 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Effect Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.potionofgreaterhealing@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Potion of Greater Healing</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You regain hit points when you drink this potion.</p>
					<p>The number of hit points depends on the potion's rarity, as shown in the Potions of Healing table. Whatever its potency, the potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</p>
					<h>Potions of Healing</h>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>Potion of .</td>
							<td>Rarity</td>
							<td>HP Regained</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Greater healing</td>
							<td>Uncommon</td>
							<td>4d4 + 4</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Potion of Greater Healing</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Dim Potion</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">The potion's red liquid glimmers when agitated.</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Uncommon</rarity>
				<type type="string">Potion</type>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00032>
			<id-00033>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Knife (Small)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.25</weight>
			</id-00033>
			<id-00034>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">300 GP</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The medallion has 3 charges. While wearing it, you can use an action and expend 1 charge to cast the detect thoughts spell (save DC 13) from it. The medallion regains 1d3 expended charges daily at dawn.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.detectthoughts@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Detect Thoughts</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Medallion of Thoughts</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Medallion</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">-</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">uncommon (requires attunement)</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">-</subtype>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00034>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Dwarvish</name>
			</id-00002>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">6</level>
		<name type="string">Resu Cigam</name>
		<notes type="string">He likes to talk to his hat.\nCharlatan Scam: I put on new identities like clothes.\nSPELLBOOK: A tome full of black pages whose writing is visible only in dim light or darkness\nECCENTRICITIES: When you want people to leave you alone, you start talking to yourself. That usually does the trick.\nAMBITIONS: You will become the greatest wizard the world has seen in generations.</notes>
		<pc_label_hero type="string">Hero Point</pc_label_hero>
		<perception type="number">11</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I lie about almost everything, even when there's no good reason to.</personalitytraits>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">4</prepared>
				<savemod type="number">0</savemod>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<uses type="number">0</uses>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Potions</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Actions</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Class Feature</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<name type="string">Items</name>
			</id-00005>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">4</max>
				<used type="number">2</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">1</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">3</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">preparation</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You hurl a mote of fire at a creature or object within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes 1d10 fire damage. A flammable object hit by this spell ignites if it isn't being worn or carried.</p>
					<p>This spell's damage increases by 1d10 when you reach 5th level (2d10), 11th level (3d10), and 17th level (4d10).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fire Bolt (120x2)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
								<type type="string">thunder</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Booming Blade; If target moves takes 1d8 thunder</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, M (a weapon)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>As part of the action used to cast this spell, you must make a melee attack with a weapon against one creature within the spell's range, otherwise the spell fails. On a hit, the target suffers the attack's normal effects, and it becomes sheathed in booming energy until the start of your next turn. If the target willingly moves before then, it immediately takes 1d8 thunder damage, and the spell ends.</p>
					<p>This spell's damage increases when you reach higher levels. At 5th level, the melee attack deals an extra 1d8 thunder damage to the target, and the damage the target takes for moving increases to 2d8. Both damage rolls increase by 1d8 at 11th level and 17th level.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">0</locked>
				<name type="string">Booming Blade (5)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">5 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10</dice>
								<type type="string">force</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A beam of crackling energy streaks toward a creature within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes 1d10 force damage.</p>
					<p>The spell creates more than one beam when you reach higher levels: two beams at 5th level, three beams at 11th level, and four beams at 17th level. You can direct the beams at the same target or at different ones. Make a separate attack roll for each beam.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Eldritch Blast (120x2)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Warlock</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Mage Hand</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A spectral, floating hand appears at a point you choose within range. The hand lasts for the duration or until you dismiss it as an action. The hand vanishes if it is ever more than 30 feet away from you or if you cast this spell again.</p>
					<p>You can use your action to control the hand. You can use the hand to manipulate an object, open an unlocked door or container, stow or retrieve an item from an open container, or pour the contents out of a vial. You can move the hand up to 30 feet each time you use it.</p>
					<p>The hand can't attack, activate magic items, or carry more than 10 pounds.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mage Hand (30)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Tactical Wit; INIT: [INT]</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, your keen ability to assess tactical situations allows you to act quickly in battle. You can give yourself a bonus to your initiative rolls equal to your Intelligence modifier.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class Feature</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wizard: Tactical Wit</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<specialization type="string">War Magic</specialization>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">action</apply>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Arcane Deflection; AC: 2; SAVE: 4</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you have learned to weave your magic to fortify yourself against harm. When you are hit by an attack or you fail a saving throw, you can use your reaction to gain a +2 bonus to your AC against that attack or a +4 bonus to that saving throw.</p>
					<p>When you use this feature, you can't cast spells other than cantrips until the end of your next turn.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class Feature</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wizard: Arcane Deflection (R)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<specialization type="string">War Magic</specialization>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<type type="string">force</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create three glowing darts of magical force. Each dart hits a creature of your choice that you can see within range. A dart deals 1d4 + 1 force damage to its target. The darts all strike simultaneously, and you can direct them to hit one creature or several.</p>
					<p>At Higher Levels.</p>
					<p>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the spell creates one more dart for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Magic Missile (120)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Minor Illusion</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">S, M (a bit of fleece)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create a sound or an image of an object within range that lasts for the duration. The illusion also ends if you dismiss it as an action or cast this spell again.</p>
					<p>If you create a sound, its volume can range from a whisper to a scream. It can be your voice, someone else's voice, a lion's roar, a beating of drums, or any other sound you choose. The sound continues unabated throughout the duration, or you can make discrete sounds at different times before the spell ends.</p>
					<p>If you create an image of an object-such as a chair, muddy footprints, or a small chest-it must be no larger than a 5-foot cube. The image can't create sound, light, smell, or any other sensory effect. Physical interaction with the image reveals it to be an illusion, because things can pass through it.</p>
					<p>If a creature uses its action to examine the sound or image, the creature can determine that it is an illusion with a successful Intelligence (Investigation) check against your spell save DC. If a creature discerns the illusion for what it is, the illusion becomes faint to the creature.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Minor Illusion (30)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Monk, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>As you hold your hands with thumbs touching and fingers spread, a thin sheet of flames shoots forth from your outstretched fingertips. Each creature in a 15-foot cone must make a Dexterity saving throw. A creature takes 3d6 fire damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.</p>
					<p>The fire ignites any flammable objects in the area that aren't being worn or carried.</p>
					<p>At Higher Levels.</p>
					<p>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Burning Hands (S-15)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self (15-foot cone)</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric Light Domain, Eldritch Knight, Warlock (Fiend), Monk, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Charm Person; Charmed</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You attempt to charm a humanoid you can see within range. It must make a Wisdom saving throw, and does so with advantage if you or your companions are fighting it. If it fails the saving throw, it is charmed by you until the spell ends or until you or your companions do anything harmful to it. The charmed creature regards you as a friendly acquaintance. When the spell ends, the creature knows it was charmed by you.</p>
					<p>At Higher Levels.</p>
					<p>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st. The creatures must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Charm Person (30)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Trickery Domain, Druid, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Detect Magic (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any.</p>
					<p>The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Magic (S) (C)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Eldritch Knight, Eldritch Invocations, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Shield; AC: 5</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 reaction, which you take when you are hit by an attack or targeted by the magic missile spell</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>An invisible barrier of magical force appears and protects you. Until the start of your next turn, you have a +5 bonus to AC, including against the triggering attack, and you take no damage from magic missile.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield (R) (S)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Briefly surrounded by silvery mist, you teleport up to 30 feet to an unoccupied space that you can see.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Misty Step(B) (S)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid Coast Circle, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Diguise Self</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You make yourself-including your clothing, armor, weapons, and other belongings on your person-look different until the spell ends or until you use your action to dismiss it. You can seem 1 foot shorter or taller and can appear thin, fat, or in between. You can't change your body type, so you must adopt a form that has the same basic arrangement of limbs. Otherwise, the extent of the illusion is up to you.</p>
					<p>The changes wrought by this spell fail to hold up to physical inspection. For example, if you use this spell to add a hat to your outfit, objects pass through the hat, and anyone who touches it would feel nothing or would feel your head and hair. If you use this spell to appear thinner than you are, the hand of someone who reaches out to touch you would bump into you while it was seemingly still in midair.</p>
					<p>To discern that you are disguised, a creature can use its action to inspect your appearance and must succeed on an Intelligence (Investigation) check against your spell save DC.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Disguise Self (S)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Trickery Domain, Eldritch Knight, Eldritch Invocations, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4,d4</dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<group type="string">Potions</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">Potion of Healing (SELF)</name>
				<prepared type="number">3</prepared>
				<usesperiod type="string">once</usesperiod>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 minute</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pearl worth at least 100 gp and an owl feather)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You choose one object that you must touch throughout the casting of the spell. If it is a magic item or some other magic-imbued object, you learn its properties and how to use them, whether it requires attunement to use, and how many charges it has, if any. You learn whether any spells are affecting the item and what they are. If the item was created by a spell, you learn which spell created it.</p>
					<p>If you instead touch a creature throughout the casting, you learn what spells, if any, are currently affecting it.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Identify (RIT) (T) ($)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Knowledge Domain, Eldritch Knight, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Sleep; Unconscious</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of fine sand, rose petals, or a cricket)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell sends creatures into a magical slumber.</p>
					<p>Roll 5d8; the total is how many hit points of creatures this spell can affect. Creatures within 20 feet of a point you choose within range are affected in ascending order of their current hit points (ignoring unconscious creatures).</p>
					<p>Starting with the creature that has the lowest current hit points, each creature affected by this spell falls unconscious until the spell ends, the sleeper takes damage, or someone uses an action to shake or slap the sleeper awake. Subtract each creature's hit points from the total before moving on to the creature with the next lowest hit points. A creature's hit points must be equal to or less than the remaining total for that creature to be affected.</p>
					<p>Undead and creatures immune to being charmed aren't affected by this spell.</p>
					<p>At Higher Levels.</p>
					<p>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, roll an additional 2d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sleep (90)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">90 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Warlock (Archfey), Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Invisibility (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Invisibility (C); Invisible</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (an eyelash encased in gum arabic)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch becomes invisible until the spell ends. Anything the target is wearing or carrying is invisible as long as it is on the target's person. The spell ends for a target that attacks or casts a spell.</p>
					<p>At Higher Levels.</p>
					<p>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Invisibility (T) (C)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Druid Grassland Circle, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose an object that you can see within range. The object can be a door, a box, a chest, a set of manacles, a padlock, or another object that contains a mundane or magical means that prevents access.</p>
					<p>A target that is held shut by a mundane lock or that is stuck or barred becomes unlocked, unstuck, or unbarred. If the object has multiple locks, only one of them is unlocked.</p>
					<p>If you choose a target that is held shut with arcane lock, that spell is suppressed for 10 minutes, during which time the target can be opened and shut normally. When you cast the spell, a loud knock, audible from as far away as 300 feet, emanates from the target object.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Knock (60)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">8</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Suggestion (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">8</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">Suggestion (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, M (a snake's tongue and either a bit of honeycomb or a drop of sweet oil)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You suggest a course of activity (limited to a sentence or two) and magically influence a creature you can see within range that can hear and understand you.</p>
					<p>Creatures that can't be charmed are immune to this effect. The suggestion must be worded in such a manner as to make the course of action sound reasonable.</p>
					<p>Asking the creature to stab itself, throw itself onto a spear, immolate itself, or do some other obviously harmful act ends the spell.</p>
					<p>The target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, it pursues the course of action you described to the best of its ability. The suggested course of action can continue for the entire duration. If the suggested activity can be completed in a shorter time, the spell ends when the subject finishes what it was asked to do. You can also specify conditions that will trigger a special activity during the duration. For example, you might suggest that a knight give her warhorse to the first beggar she meets. If the condition isn't met before the spell expires, the activity isn't performed.</p>
					<p>If you or any of your companions damage the target, the spell ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Suggestion (30) (C)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Knowledge Domain, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 minute</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a small crystal bead)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A 10-foot-radius immobile dome of force springs into existence around and above you and remains stationary for the duration. The spell ends if you leave its area.</p>
					<p>Nine creatures of Medium size or smaller can fit inside the dome with you. The spell fails if its area includes a larger creature or more than nine creatures. Creatures and objects within the dome when you cast this spell can move through it freely. All other creatures and objects are barred from passing through it. Spells and other magical effects can't extend through the dome or be cast through it. The atmosphere inside the space is comfortable and dry, regardless of the weather outside.</p>
					<p>Until the spell ends, you can command the interior to become dimly lit or dark. The dome is opaque from the outside, of any color you choose, but it is transparent from the inside.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">8 hours</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Leomund's Tiny Hut (S-10)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self (10-foot-radius hemisphere)</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Dodge</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">Action</castingtime>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you take the Dodge action, you focus entirely on avoiding attacks. Until the start of your next turn, any attack roll made against you has disadvantage if you can see the attacker, and you make Dexterity saving throws with advantage. You lose this benefit if you are incapacitated (as explained in the appendix) or if your speed drops to 0.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Actions</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dodge</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Actions</school>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">action</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Help; ADVCHK: all</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">Action</castingtime>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can lend your aid to another creature in the completion of a task. When you take the Help action, the creature you aid gains advantage on the next ability check it makes to perform the task you are helping with, pjrovided that it makes the check before the start of your next turn.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Actions</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Help</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Actions</school>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Hide</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">Action</castingtime>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you take the Hide action, you make a Dexterity (Stealth) check in an attempt to hide, following the rules in chapter 7 for hiding. If you succeed, you gain certain benefits, as described in the &#34;Unseen Attackers and Targets&#34; section later in this chapter.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Actions</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hide</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Action</school>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00025>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Ready</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">Action</castingtime>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Sometimes you want to get the jump on a foe or wait for a particular circumstance before you act. To do so, you can take the Ready action on your turn so that you can act later in the round using your reaction. For more information see &#34;Actions in Combat, Ch 9&#34;</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Actions</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ready</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Actions</school>
			</id-00025>
			<id-00026>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6,d6,d6,d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a tiny ball of bat guano and sulfur)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A bright streak flashes from your pointing finger to a point you choose within range and then blossoms with a low roar into an explosion of flame. Each creature in a 20-foot-radius sphere centered on that point must make a Dexterity saving throw. A target takes 8d6 fire damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.</p>
					<p>The fire spreads around corners. It ignites flammable objects in the area that aren't being worn or carried.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 3rd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fireball (150x2)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">150 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric Light Domain, Eldritch Knight, Warlock (Fiend), Monk, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00026>
			<id-00027>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Ring of Radiant Resistance; RESIST: radiant</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<cost type="string">501 - 5,000 gp</cost>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You have resistance to radiant damage type while wearing this ring</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Items</group>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ring of Radiant Resistance</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Gold Ring</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A delicately made gold ring with a topaz setting.</nonidentified>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<properties type="string">Magic</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Rare (Requires Attunement)</rarity>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<spells>
					<id-00001>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class></class>
							<recordname></recordname>
						</link>
						<name type="string">Ring of Radiant Resistance</name>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class></class>
							<recordname></recordname>
						</link>
						<name type="string">Signet Ring</name>
					</id-00002>
				</spells>
				<type type="string">Ring</type>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00027>
			<id-00028>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Hypnotic Pattern (C); Incapacitated</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Hypnotic Pattern (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">S, M (a glowing stick of incense or a crystal vial filled with phosphorescent material)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create a twisting pattern of colors that weaves through the air inside a 30-foot cube within range. The pattern appears for a moment and vanishes. Each creature in the area who sees the pattern must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, the creature becomes charmed for the duration. While charmed by this spell, the creature is incapacitated and has a speed of 0.</p>
					<p>The spell ends for an affected creature if it takes any damage or if someone else uses an action to shake the creature out of its stupor.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hypnotic Pattern (120) (C)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Illusion</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00028>
			<id-00029>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 reaction, which you take when you see a creature within 60 feet of you casting a spell</castingtime>
				<components type="string">S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You attempt to interrupt a creature in the process of casting a spell. If the creature is casting a spell of 3rd level or lower, its spell fails and has no effect. If it is casting a spell of 4th level or higher, make an ability check using your spellcasting ability. The DC equals 10 + the spell's level. On a success, the creature's spell fails and has no effect.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher, the interrupted spell has no effect if its level is less than or equal to the level of the spell slot you used.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Counterspell (R) (60)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00029>
			<id-00032>
				<actions>
					<id-00004>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Heartstone; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="item" recordname="item.id-00044@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Heartstone</link>
					</linklist>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Items</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heartstone</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00032>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">3</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: Disguise kit</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Daggers, darts, slings, quarterstaffs, light crossbows</name>
			</id-00002>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Human</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.human@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">2</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">2</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Disquise kit</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00019>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">tokens/human_male_spellcaster_A_01.png@Character Pogs</token>
		<traitlist>
		</traitlist>
		<vit>
			<max type="number">14</max>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</vit>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00003>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Quarterstaff</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00016</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00003>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">165</weight>
	</character>
</root>
