<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:4">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">5</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Adventure log 1, we got to the weartown and then picked up the ale, following that we droped it off at the base town and then headed out for delivering letter to a dragon and kil followers of tiamat</name>
			</id-00001>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">21</age>
		<alignment type="string">CG</alignment>
		<background type="string">Knight of the Order</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>reference.backgrounddata.knightoftheorder@D&#38;D Sword Coast Adventurer's Guide - Player's Guide</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">Those who fight beside me are those worth dying for.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">2</casterlevelinvmult>
				<hddie type="dice">d10</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<name type="string">Paladin</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.paladin@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<hddie type="dice">d8</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">1</hdused>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<name type="string">Bard</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.bard@DD Xanathar's Guide to Everything Players</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00002>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">200</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">6</armor>
				<dexbonus type="string">no</dexbonus>
				<disstealth type="number">1</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">1</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">2</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">19</total>
			</ac>
			<special type="string">heals 8 at the end of a short rest</special>
		</defenses>
		<deity type="string">Corellon Larethian</deity>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">80</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">160</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">480</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">129.01</load>
			<max type="number">240</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">76</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">0</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Knightly Regard</name>
				<source type="string">Knight of the Order</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You receive shelter and succor from members of your knightly order and those who are sympathetic to its aims. If your order is a religious one, you can gain aid from temples and other religious communities of your deity. Knights of civic orders can get help from the community - whether a lone settlement or a great nation - that they serve, and knights of philosophical orders can find help from those they have aided in pursuit of their ideals, and those who share those ideals.</p>
					<p>This help comes in the form of shelter and meals, and healing when appropriate, as well as occasionally risky assistance, such as a band of local citizens rallying to aid a sorely pressed knight in a fight, or those who support the order helping to smuggle a knight out of town when he or she is being hunted unjustly.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lay on Hands</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Action Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.layonhands@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Lay on Hands</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>Your blessed touch can heal wounds. You have a pool of healing power that replenishes when you take a long rest. With that pool, you can restore a total number of hit points equal to your paladin level x 5.</p>
					<p>As an action, you can touch a creature and draw power from the pool to restore a number of hit points to that creature, up to the maximum amount remaining in your pool.</p>
					<p>Alternatively, you can expend 5 hit points from your pool of healing to cure the target of one disease or neutralize one poison affecting it. You can cure multiple diseases and neutralize multiple poisons with a single use of Lay on Hands, expending hit points separately for each one.</p>
					<p>This feature has no effect on undead and constructs.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Sense</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>The presence of strong evil registers on your senses like a noxious odor, and a powerful good rings like heavenly music in your ears. As an action, you can open your awareness to detect such forces. Until the end of your next turn, you know the location of any celestial, fiend, or undead within 60 feet of you that is not behind total cover. You know the type (celestial, fiend, or undead) of any being whose presence you sense, but not its identity. Within the same radius you also detect the presence of any place or object that has been consecrated or desecrated, as with the <i>hallow </i>spell.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to 1 + your Charisma modifier. When you finish a long rest, you regain all expended uses.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Paladin Starting Items</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p><b>Click the shield below to open you choices for paladin starting items.</b></p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_weapontable" recordname="lists.startingequipment.paladin@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Paladin Starting Equipment Options</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>Note: You only get these if your 1st level is in Paladin.</p>
					<p><b>Summary</b></p>
					<p>You start with the following equipment, in addition to the equipment granted by your background:</p>
					<list>
						<li>You get either 1) a shield and a martial weapon OR 2) two martial weapons.</li>
						<li>You get either 1) 5 javelins OR 2) a simple melee weapon.</li>
						<li>You get a priest's pack or an explorer's pack.</li>
						<li>You get chainmail.</li>
						<li>You get a holy symbol.</li>
					</list>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Smite</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Action Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.divinesmite@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Divine Smite</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, when you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one spell slot to deal radiant damage to the target, in addition to the weapon's damage. The extra damage is 2d8 for a 1st-level spell slot, plus 1d8 for each spell level higher than 1st, to a maximum of 5d8. The damage increases by 1d8 if the target is an undead or a fiend.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>By 2nd level, you have learned to draw on divine magic through meditation and prayer to cast spells as a cleric does.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="lists.spells.paladin@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Paladin Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b></p>
					<p>The Paladin table shows how many spell slots you have cast your spells. To cast one of your paladin spells of 1st level or higher, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. you regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00042@Incarnate-5eExpansion">The Paladin</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>You prepare the list of paladin spells that are available for you to cast, choosing from the paladin spell list. When you do so, choose a number of paladin spells equal to your Charisma modifier + half your paladin level, rounded down (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you are a 5th-level paladin, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With a Charisma of 14, your list of prepared spells can include four spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination. If you prepare the 1st-level spell <i>cure wounds </i>, you can cast it using a 1st-level or a 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of paladin spells requires time spent in prayer and meditation: at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<h>Spellcasting Ability</h>
					<p>Charisma is your spellcasting ability for your paladin spells, since their power derives from the strength of your convictions. You use your Charisma whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Charisma modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a paladin spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<list>
						<li><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</li>
						<li><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</li>
					</list>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a holy symbol as a spellcasting focus for your paladin spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style (defense)</name>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you adopt a style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the following options. You can't take a Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.</p>
					<p><b>Defense</b></p>
					<p>While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.fightingstyledefense@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Fighting Style - Defense</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Dueling</b></p>
					<p>When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.fightingstyledueling@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Fighting Style - Dueling</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Great Weapon Fighting</b></p>
					<p>When you roll a 1 or 2 on a damage die for an attack you make with a melee weapon that you are wielding with two hands, you can re-roll the die and must use the new roll. The weapon must have the two-handed or versatile property for you to gain this benefit.</p>
					<p><b>Protection</b></p>
					<p>When a creature you can see attacks a target other than you that is within 5 feet of you, you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on the attack roll. You must be wielding a shield.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.fightingstyleprotection@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Fighting Style - Protection</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bardic Inspiration</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Action Coding</h>
					<p>Almost everyone will just play this one by hand with the bardic inspiration die rolled and then added manually, but you may use this variant if you want coding that rolls the inspiration die on the next check, attack roll, or saving throw.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.bardicinspiration@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Bardic Inspiration</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You can inspire others through stirring words or music. To do so, you use a bonus action on your turn to choose one creature other than yourself within 60 feet of you who can hear you. That creature gains one Bardic Inspiration die, a d6.</p>
					<p>Once within the next 10 minutes, the creature can roll the die and add the number rolled to one ability check, attack roll, or saving throw it makes. The creature can wait until after it rolls the d20 before deciding to use th Bardic Inspiration die, but must decide before the GM says whether the roll succeeds or fails. Once the Bardic Inspiration die is rolled, it is lost. A creature can have only one Bardic Inspiration die at a time.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Charisma modifier (a minimum of once). You regain any expended uses when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>Your Bardic Inspiration die changes when you reach certain levels in this class. The die becomes a d8 at 5th level, a d10 at 10th level, and a d12 at 15th level.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting (Bard)</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have learned to untangle and reshape the fabric of reality in harmony with your wishes and music. Your spells are part of your vast repertoire, magic that you can tune to different situations.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="lists.spells.bard@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Bard Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>You know two cantrips of your choice from the bard spell list. You learn additional bard cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Bard table.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.id-00035@Incarnate-5eExpansion">The Bard</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Spell Slots</b></p>
					<p>The Bard table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of these spells, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. you regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>For example, if you know the 1st-level spell <i>cure wounds </i>and have a 1st-level and a 2nd-level spell slot available, you can cast <i>cure wounds </i>using either slot.</p>
					<p><b>Spells Known of 1st Level and Higher</b></p>
					<p>You know four 1st-level spells of your choice from the bard spell list.</p>
					<p>The Spells Known column of the Bard table shows when you learn more bard spells of your choice. Each of these spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots, as shown on the table. For instance, when you reach 3rd level in this class, you can learn one new spell of 1st or 2nd level.</p>
					<p>Additionally, when you gain a level in this class, you can choose one of the bard spells you know and replace it with another spell from the bard spell list, which also must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Charisma is your spellcasting ability for your bard spells. Your magic comes from the heart and soul you pour into the performance of your music or oration. You use your Charisma whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Charisma modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a bard spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<list>
						<li><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</li>
						<li><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</li>
					</list>
					<p><b>Ritual Casting</b></p>
					<p>You can cast any bard spell you know as a ritual if that spell has the ritual tag.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use a musical instrument (see &#34;Equipment&#34;) as a spellcasting focus for your bard spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bard Starting Items</name>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p><b>Click the shield below to open you choices for bard starting items.</b></p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_weapontable" recordname="lists.startingequipment.bard@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Bard Starting Equipment Options</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>Note: You only get these if your 1st level is in Bard.</p>
					<p><b>Summary</b></p>
					<p>You start with the following equipment, in addition to the equipment granted by your background:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Your choice of one simple melee weapon OR a rapier</li>
						<li>Your choice of a diplomat's pack or an entertainer's pack.</li>
						<li>Your choice of a lute or any musical instrument.</li>
						<li>You get both leather armor and a dagger.</li>
					</list>
				</text>
			</id-00010>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I'd rather eat my armor than admit when I'm wrong.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">female</gender>
		<height type="string">5'8&#34;</height>
		<hero type="number">3</hero>
		<herodice type="string">d6</herodice>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">27</total>
			<wounds type="number">21</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Greater Good. Our lot is to lay down our lives in defense of others. (Good)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">0</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<ac type="number">2</ac>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A shield is made from wood or metal and is carried in one hand. Wielding a shield increases your Armor Class by 2. You can benefit from only one shield at a time.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield</name>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Shield</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<ac type="number">16</ac>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">75 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Of all the armor categories, heavy armor offers the best protection. These suits of armor cover the entire body and are designed to stop a wide range of attacks. Only proficient warriors can manage their weight and bulk.</p>
					<p>Made of interlocking metal rings, chain mail includes a layer of quilted fabric worn underneath the mail to prevent chafing and to cushion the impact of blows. The suit includes gauntlets.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Chain Mail</name>
				<stealth type="string">Disadvantage</stealth>
				<strength type="string">Str 13</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Heavy Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">55</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">15 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 slashing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Longsword</name>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d4 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bedroll</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">7</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This tin box contains a cup and simple cutlery. The box clamps together, and one side can be used as a cooking pan and the other as a plate or shallow bowl.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mess Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Equipment Kits</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A holy symbol is a representation of a god or pantheon. It might be an amulet depicting a symbol representing a deity, the same symbol carefully engraved or inlaid as an emblem on a shield, or a tiny box holding a fragment of a sacred relic. The Player's Handbook lists many gods in the multiverse and their typical symbols. A cleric or paladin can use a holy symbol as a spellcasting focus, as described in chapter To use the symbol in this way, the caster must hold it in hand, wear it visibly, or bear it on a shield.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">crystal Amulet of Corellon</name>
				<subtype type="string">Holy Symbol</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p></p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Traveler's</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Signet Ring</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00015>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Elvish</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Goblin</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Draconic</name>
			</id-00004>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">3</level>
		<name type="string">Victoria</name>
		<notes type="string">players handbook + sword coast + Xanders\nbring bard to 5 then go back to paladin to 8 then add sorc</notes>
		<pc_label_hero type="string">Hero Point</pc_label_hero>
		<perception type="number">12</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I'm always polite and respectful.</personalitytraits>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<prepared type="number">4</prepared>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells (Bard)</name>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Divine Smite</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">Bardic Inspirtation</name>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<uses type="number">3</uses>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">Divine Sense</name>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<uses type="number">4</uses>
			</id-00005>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">3</max>
				<used type="number">2</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">standard</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<label type="string">DMG: 2d8 radiant</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<label type="string">DMG: 3d8 radiant</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Action Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.divinesmite@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Divine Smite</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, when you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one spell slot to deal radiant damage to the target, in addition to the weapon's damage. The extra damage is 2d8 for a 1st-level spell slot, plus 1d8 for each spell level higher than 1st, to a maximum of 5d8. The damage increases by 1d8 if the target is an undead or a fiend.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Divine Smite</group>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Smite</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The presence of strong evil registers on your senses like a noxious odor, and a powerful good rings like heavenly music in your ears. As an action, you can open your awareness to detect such forces. Until the end of your next turn, you know the location of any celestial, fiend, or undead within 60 feet of you that is not behind total cover. You know the type (celestial, fiend, or undead) of any being whose presence you sense, but not its identity. Within the same radius you also detect the presence of any place or object that has been consecrated or desecrated, as with the <i>hallow </i>spell.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to 1 + your Charisma modifier. When you finish a long rest, you regain all expended uses.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Divine Sense</group>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Sense</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">2</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Action Coding</h>
					<p>Almost everyone will just play this one by hand with the bardic inspiration die rolled and then added manually, but you may use this variant if you want coding that rolls the inspiration die on the next check, attack roll, or saving throw.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.bardicinspiration@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Bardic Inspiration</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>You can inspire others through stirring words or music. To do so, you use a bonus action on your turn to choose one creature other than yourself within 60 feet of you who can hear you. That creature gains one Bardic Inspiration die, a d6.</p>
					<p>Once within the next 10 minutes, the creature can roll the die and add the number rolled to one ability check, attack roll, or saving throw it makes. The creature can wait until after it rolls the d20 before deciding to use th Bardic Inspiration die, but must decide before the GM says whether the roll succeeds or fails. Once the Bardic Inspiration die is rolled, it is lost. A creature can have only one Bardic Inspiration die at a time.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Charisma modifier (a minimum of once). You regain any expended uses when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>Your Bardic Inspiration die changes when you reach certain levels in this class. The die becomes a d8 at 5th level, a d10 at 10th level, and a d12 at 15th level.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Bardic Inspirtation</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bardic Inspiration</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">ATK: 1d4; SAVE: 1d4; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a sprinkling of holy water)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You bless up to three creatures of your choice within range. Whenever a target makes an attack roll or a saving throw before the spell ends, the target can roll a d4 and add the number rolled to the attack roll or saving throw.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bless</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Paladin</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You speak a one-word command to a creature you can see within range. The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or follow the command on its next turn. The spell has no effect if the target is undead, if it doesn't understand your language, or if your command is directly harmful to it.</p>
					<p>Some typical commands and their effects follow. You might issue a command other than one described here. If you do so, the DM determines how the target behaves. If the target can't follow your command, the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>Approach. </b>The target moves toward you by the shortest and most direct route, ending its turn if it moves within 5 feet of you.</p>
					<p><b>Drop. </b>The target drops whatever it is holding and then ends its turn.</p>
					<p><b>Flee. </b>The target spends its turn moving away from you by the fastest available means.</p>
					<p><b>Grovel. </b>The target falls prone and then ends its turn.</p>
					<p><b>Halt. </b>The target doesn't move and takes no actions. A flying creature stays aloft, provided that it is able to do so. If it must move to stay aloft, it flies the minimum distance needed to remain in the air.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can affect one additional creature for each slot level above 1st. The creatures must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Command</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Cleric Knowledge Domain, Warlock (Fiend), Paladin</source>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You attempt to compel a creature into a duel. One creature that you can see within range must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, the creature is drawn to you, compelled by your divine demand. For the duration, it has disadvantage on attack rolls against creatures other than you, and must make a Wisdom saving throw each time it attempts to move to a space that is more than 30 feet away from you; if it succeeds on this saving throw, this spell doesn't restrict the target's movement for that turn.</p>
					<p>The spell ends if you attack any other creature, if you cast a spell that targets a hostile creature other than the target, if a creature friendly to you damages the target or casts a harmful spell on it, or if you end your turn more than 30 feet away from the target.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Compelled Duel</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch regains a number of hit points equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cure Wounds</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you know if there is an aberration, celestial, elemental, fey, fiend, or undead within 30 feet of you, as well as where the creature is located. Similarly, you know if there is a place or object within 30 feet of you that has been magically consecrated or desecrated.</p>
					<p>The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Evil and Good</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Paladin</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any.</p>
					<p>The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Magic</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Eldritch Knight, Eldritch Invocations, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a yew leaf)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you can sense the presence and location of poisons, poisonous creatures, and diseases within 30 feet of you. You also identify the kind of poison, poisonous creature, or disease in each case. The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Poison and Disease</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">DMG: 1d4 radiant; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your prayer empowers you with divine radiance. Until the spell ends, your weapon attacks deal an extra 1d4 radiant damage on a hit.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Favor</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric War Domain, Paladin</source>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A willing creature you touch is imbued with bravery.</p>
					<p>Until the spell ends, the creature is immune to being frightened and gains temporary hit points equal to your spellcasting ability modifier at the start of each of its turns. When the spell ends, the target loses any remaining temporary hit points from this spell.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Heroism</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Paladin</source>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">IFT: TYPE(aberration, celestial, elemental, fey, fiend, undead); GRANTDISATK; IMMUNE: charmed,frightened,possessed; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (holy water or powdered silver and iron, which the spell consumes)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Until the spell ends, one willing creature you touch is protected against certain types of creatures: aberrations, celestials, elementals, fey, fiends, and undead.</p>
					<p>The protection grants several benefits. Creatures of those types have disadvantage on attack rolls against the target. The target also can't be charmed, frightened, or possessed by them. If the target is already charmed, frightened, or possessed by such a creature, the target has advantage on any new saving throw against the relevant effect.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Protection from Evil and Good</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Eldritch Knight, Paladin, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>All nonmagical food and drink within a 5-foot-radius sphere centered on a point of your choice within range is purified and rendered free of poison and disease.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Purify Food and Drink</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid, Paladin</source>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">DMG: 1d6 fire; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The next time you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack during the spell's duration, your weapon flares with white-hot intensity, and the attack deals an extra 1d6 fire damage to the target and causes the target to ignite in flames. At the start of each of its turns until the spell ends, the target must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, it takes 1d6 fire damage.</p>
					<p>On a successful save, the spell ends. If the target or a creature within 5 feet of it uses an action to put out the flames, or if some other effect douses the flames (such as the target being submerged in water), the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the initial extra damage dealt by the attack increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Searing Smite</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">AC: 2; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a small parchment with a bit of holy text written on it)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A shimmering field appears and surrounds a creature of your choice within range, granting it a +2 bonus to AC for the duration.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield of Faith</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Cleric War Domain, Paladin</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">DMG: 2d6 thunder; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The first time you hit with a melee weapon attack during this spell's duration, your weapon rings with thunder that is audible within 300 feet of you, and the attack deals an extra 2d6 thunder damage to the target. Additionally, if the target is a creature, it must succeed on a Strength saving throw or be pushed 10 feet away from you and knocked prone.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Thunderous Smite</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">DMG: 1d6 psychic; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Frightened; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The next time you hit with a melee weapon attack during this spell's duration, your attack deals an extra 1d6 psychic damage. Additionally, if the target is a creature, it must make a Wisdom saving throw or be frightened of you until the spell ends. As an action, the creature can make a Wisdom check against your spell save DC to steel its resolve and end this spell.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wrathful Smite</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<type type="string">psychic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You unleash a string of insults laced with subtle enchantments at a creature you can see within range. If the target can hear you (though it need not understand you), it must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or take 1d4 psychic damage and have disadvantage on the next attack roll it makes before the end of its next turn. This spell's damage increases by 1d4 when you reach 5th level (2d4), 11th level (3d4), and 17th level (4d4).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Bard)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Vicious Mockery</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard</source>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell is a minor magical trick that novice spellcasters use for practice. You create one of the following magical effects within range:</p>
					<list>
						<li>You create an instantaneous, harmless sensory effect, such as a shower of sparks, a puff of wind, faint musical notes, or an odd odor.</li>
						<li>You instantaneously light or snuff out a candle, a torch, or a small campfire.</li>
						<li>You instantaneously clean or soil an object no larger than 1 cubic foot.</li>
						<li>You chill, warm, or flavor up to 1 cubic foot of nonliving material for 1 hour.</li>
						<li>You make a color, a small mark, or a symbol appear on an object or a surface for 1 hour.</li>
						<li>You create a nonmagical trinket or an illusory image that can fit in your hand and that lasts until the end of your next turn.</li>
					</list>
					<p>If you cast this spell multiple times, you can have up to three of its non-instantaneous effects active at a time, and you can dismiss such an effect as an action.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Bard)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Prestidigitation</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">psychic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You whisper a discordant melody that only one creature of your choice within range can hear, wracking it with terrible pain. The target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, it takes 3d6 psychic damage and must immediately use its reaction, if available, to move as far as its speed allows away from you. The creature doesn't move into obviously dangerous ground, such as a fire or a pit. On a successful save, the target takes half as much damage and doesn't have to move away. A deafened creature automatically succeeds on the save.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Bard)</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dissonant Whispers</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Warlock (Great Old One)</source>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature of your choice that you can see within range regains hit points equal to 1d4 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d4 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Bard)</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Healing Word</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
								<stat type="string">paladin</stat>
								<statmult type="number">5</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Action Coding</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="power" recordname="spell.layonhands@Incarnate-5eExpansion">Lay on Hands</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>Your blessed touch can heal wounds. You have a pool of healing power that replenishes when you take a long rest. With that pool, you can restore a total number of hit points equal to your paladin level x 5.</p>
					<p>As an action, you can touch a creature and draw power from the pool to restore a number of hit points to that creature, up to the maximum amount remaining in your pool.</p>
					<p>Alternatively, you can expend 5 hit points from your pool of healing to cure the target of one disease or neutralize one poison affecting it. You can cure multiple diseases and neutralize multiple poisons with a single use of Lay on Hands, expending hit points separately for each one.</p>
					<p>This feature has no effect on undead and constructs.</p>
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lay on Hands</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a pinch of soot and salt)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you understand the literal meaning of any spoken language that you hear. You also understand any written language that you see, but you must be touching the surface on which the words are written. It takes about 1 minute to read one page of text.</p>
					<p>This spell doesn't decode secret messages in a text or a glyph, such as an arcane sigil, that isn't part of a written language.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Bard)</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Comprehend Languages</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00025>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">thunder</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A wave of thunderous force sweeps out from you. Each creature in a 15-foot cube originating from you must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, a creature takes 2d8 thunder damage and is pushed 10 feet away from you. On a successful save, the creature takes half as much damage and isn't pushed.</p>
					<p>In addition, unsecured objects that are completely within the area of effect are automatically pushed 10 feet away from you by the spell's effect, and the spell emits a thunderous boom audible out to 300 feet.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Bard)</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Thunderwave</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self (15-foot cube)</range>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Tempest Domain, Druid, Eldritch Knight, Monk, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00025>
			<id-00026>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<label type="string">Fey Ancestry: immune to sleep; Advantage vs charmed.</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against being charmed, and magic can't put you to sleep.</p>
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fey Ancestry</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
			</id-00026>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">2</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: dice, Lure, Lute</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple weapons, martial weapons</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Armor: All armor, shields</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Armor: Light armor</name>
			</id-00004>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Half-Elf</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.half_elf@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<senses type="string">Darkvision 60</senses>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00019>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00001_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Skill Versatility</name>
				<source type="string">Half-Elf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain proficiency in two skills of your choice.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fey Ancestry</name>
				<source type="string">Half-Elf</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on saving throws against being charmed, and magic can't put you to sleep.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">slashing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<handling type="number">0</handling>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Longsword</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00003</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<handling type="number">0</handling>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00004</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<handling type="number">0</handling>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">1</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00004</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00003>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">115</weight>
	</character>
</root>
