<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:3">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">9</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">11</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">10</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">12</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">13</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">30</age>
		<alignment type="string">Chaotic Good</alignment>
		<appearance type="string">He looks quite dishevelled; Messy hair, singed clothes. The ends of his fingers are scarred from &#34;communion&#34; with his deity. He has a tendency to lose touch with himself when he uses his fire magic or is distressed, turning to a darker character in the heat of battle.</appearance>
		<background type="string">Hermit</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>reference.backgrounddata.hermit@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">I'm still seeking the enlightenment I pursued in my seclusion, and it still eludes me.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">1</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d8</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<name type="string">Warlock</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.warlock@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">65</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">95</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">36</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">1</armor>
				<disstealth type="number">0</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">11</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<deity type="string">Alzrius</deity>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">30</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">60</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">180</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">33.95</load>
			<max type="number">90</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">485</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">500</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Discovery</name>
				<source type="string">Hermit</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>The quiet seclusion of your extended hermitage gave you access to a unique and powerful discovery. The exact nature of this revelation depends on the nature of your seclusion. It might be a great truth about the cosmos, the deities, the powerful beings of the outer planes, or the forces of nature. It could be a site that no one else has ever seen. You might have uncovered a fact that has long been forgotten, or unearthed some relic of the past that could rewrite history. It might be information that would be damaging to the people w ho or consigned you to exile, and hence the reason for your return to society. Work with your DM to determine the details of your discovery and its impact on the campaign.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">The Fiend</name>
				<source type="string">Warlock</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have made a pact with a fiend from the lower planes of existence, a being whose aims are evil, even if you strive against those aims. Such beings desire the corruption or destruction of all things, ultimately including you. Fiends powerful enough to forge a pact include demon lords such as Demogorgon, Orcus, Fraz'Urb-luu, and Baphomet; archdevils such as Asmodeus, Dispater, Mephistopheles, and Belial; pit fiends and balors that are especially mighty; and ultroloths and other lords of the yugoloths.</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.warlock.features.expandedspelllist_fiend_1@DD PHB Deluxe">Expanded Spell List (Fiend)</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.warlock.features.darkone_sblessing1@DD PHB Deluxe">Dark One's Blessing</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.warlock.features.darkone_sownluck6@DD PHB Deluxe">Dark One's Own Luck</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.warlock.features.fiendishresilience10@DD PHB Deluxe">Fiendish Resilience</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.warlock.features.hurlthroughhell14@DD PHB Deluxe">Hurl Through Hell</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Expanded Spell List (Fiend)</name>
				<source type="string">Warlock</source>
				<specialization type="string">The Fiend</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>The Fiend lets you choose from an expanded list of spells when you learn a warlock spell. The following spells are added to the warlock spell list for you.</p>
					<h>Fiend Expanded Spells</h>
					<p><b>Warlock Level - Spell</b></p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.burninghands@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>1st - Burning Hands</linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.command@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>1st - Command
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.blindness_deafness@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>2nd - Blindness/Deafness
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.scorchingray@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>2nd - Scorching Ray
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.fireball@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>3rd - Fireball
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.stinkingcloud@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>3rd - Stinking Cloud
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.fireshield@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>4th - Fire Shield
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.walloffire@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>4th - Wall of Fire
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.flamestrike@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>5th - Flame Strike
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.hallow@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>5th - Hallow
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Pact Magic</name>
				<source type="string">Warlock</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your arcane research and the magic bestowed on you by your patron have given you facility with spells. See chapter 10 for the general rules of spellcasting and chapter 11 for the warlock spell list.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_colindex" recordname="reference.spelllists.warlock@DD PHB Deluxe">Warlock Spells</link>
					</linklist>
					<p><b>Cantrips</b></p>
					<p>You know two cantrips of your choice from the warlock spell list. You learn additional warlock cantrips of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips Known column of the Warlock table.</p>
					<p><b>Spell Slots</b></p>
					<p>The Warlock table shows how many spell slots you have. The table also shows what the level of those slots is; all of your spell slots are the same level. To cast one of your warlock spells of 1st level or higher, you must expend a spell slot. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>For example, when you are 5th level, you have two 3rd-level spell slots. To cast the 1st-level spell <i>witch bolt </i>, you must spend one of those slots, and you cast it as a 3rd-level spell.</p>
					<p><b>Spells Known of 1st Level and Higher</b></p>
					<p>At 1st level, you know two 1st-level spells of your choice from the warlock spell list.</p>
					<p>The Spells Known column of the Warlock table shows when you learn more warlock spells of your choice of 1st level and higher. A spell you choose must be of a level no higher than what's shown in the table's Slot Level column for your level. When you reach 6th level, for example, you learn a new warlock spell, which can be 1st, 2nd, or 3rd level.</p>
					<p>Additionally, when you gain a level in this class, you can choose one of the warlock spells you know and replace it with another spell from the warlock spell list, which also must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Ability</b></p>
					<p>Charisma is your spellcasting ability for your warlock spells, so you use your Charisma whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Charisma modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a warlock spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p><b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p><b>Spellcasting Focus</b></p>
					<p>You can use an arcane focus (found in chapter 5) as a spellcasting focus for your warlock spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dark One's Blessing</name>
				<source type="string">Warlock</source>
				<specialization type="string">The Fiend</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 1st level, when you reduce a hostile creature to 0 hit points, you gain temporary hit points equal to your Charisma modifier + your warlock level (minimum of 1).</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Eldritch Invocations</name>
				<source type="string">Warlock</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>In your study of occult lore, you have unearthed eldritch invocations, fragments of forbidden knowledge that imbue you with an abiding magical ability.</p>
					<p>At 2nd level, you gain two eldritch invocations of your choice. Your invocation options are detailed at the end of the class description. When you gain certain warlock levels, you gain additional invocations of your choice, as shown in the Invocations Known column of the Warlock table.</p>
					<p>Additionally, when you gain a level in this class, you can choose one of the invocations you know and replace it with another invocation that you could learn at that level.</p>
					<p>A level prerequisite in an invocation refers to warlock level, not character level.</p>
					<h>Eldritch Invocations</h>
					<p>If an eldritch invocation has prerequisites, you must meet them to learn it. You can learn the invocation at the same time that you meet its prerequisites.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Name</b></td>
							<td><b>Prerequisite</b></td>
							<td colspan="5"><b>Description</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Agonizing Blast</b></td>
							<td>eldritch blast cantrip</td>
							<td colspan="5">When you cast eldritch blast, add your Charisma modifier to the damage it deals on a hit.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.eldritchblast@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Eldritch Blast</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Armor of Shadows</b></td>
							<td>-</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>mage armor </i>on yourself at will, without expending a spell slot or material components.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.magearmor@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Mage Armor</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Ascendant Step</b></td>
							<td>9th level</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>levitate </i>on yourself at will, without expending a spell slot or material components.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.levitate@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Levitate</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Beast Speech</b></td>
							<td>-</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>speak with animals </i>at will, without expending a spell slot.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.speakwithanimals@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Speak with Animals</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Beguiling Influence</b></td>
							<td>-</td>
							<td colspan="5">You gain proficiency in the Deception and Persuasion skills.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Bewitching Whispers</b></td>
							<td>7th level</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>compulsion </i>once using a warlock spell slot.You can't do so again until you finish a long rest.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.compulsion@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Compulsion</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Book of Ancient Secrets</b></td>
							<td>Pact of the Tome feature</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can now inscribe magical rituals in your Book of Shadows. Choose two 1st-level spells that have the ritual tag from any class's spell list. The rituals needn't be from the same spell list. The spells appear in the book and don't count against the number of spells you know. With your Book of Shadows in hand, you can cast the chosen spells as rituals. You can't cast the spells except as rituals, unless you've learned them by some other means. You can also cast a warlock spell you know as a ritual if it has the ritual tag. On your adventures, you can add other ritual spells to your Book of Shadows. When you find such a spell, you can add it to the book if the spell's level is equal to or less than half your warlock level (rounded up) and if you can spare the time to transcribe the spell. For each level of the spell, the transcription process takes 2 hours and costs 50 gp for the rare inks needed to inscribe it.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Chains of Carceri</b></td>
							<td>15th level, Pact of the Chain feature</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>hold monster </i>at will-targeting a celestial, fiend, or elemental-without expending a spell slot or material components. You must finish a long rest before you can use this invocation on the same creature again.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.holdmonster@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Hold Monster</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Devil's Sight</b></td>
							<td>-</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can see normally in darkness, both magical and nonmagical, to a distance of 120 feet.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Dreadful Word</b></td>
							<td>7th level</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>confusion </i>once using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you finish a long rest.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.confusion@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Confusion</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Eldritch Sight</b></td>
							<td>-</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>detect magic </i>at will, without expending a spell slot.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.detectmagic@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Detect Magic</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Eldritch Spear</b></td>
							<td>eldritch blast cantrip</td>
							<td colspan="5">When you cast eldritch blast, its range is 300 feet.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.eldritchblast@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Eldritch Blast</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Eyes of the Rune Keeper</b></td>
							<td>-</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can read all writing.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Fiendish Vigor</b></td>
							<td>-</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>false life </i>on yourself at will as a 1st-level spell, without expending a spell slot or material components.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.falselife@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>False Life</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Gaze of Two Minds</b></td>
							<td>-</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can use your action to touch a willing humanoid and perceive through its senses until the end of your next turn. As long as the creature is on the same plane of existence as you, you can use your action on subsequent turns to maintain this connection, extending the duration until the end of your next turn. While perceiving through the other creature's senses, you benefit from any special senses possessed by that creature, and you are blinded and deafened to your own surroundings.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Lifedrinker</b></td>
							<td>12th level, Pact of the Blade feature</td>
							<td colspan="5">When you hit a creature with your pact weapon, the creature takes extra necrotic damage equal to your Charisma modifier (minimum 1).</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Mask of Many Faces</b></td>
							<td>-</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>disguise self </i>at will, without expending a spell slot.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.disguiseself@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Disguise Self</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Master of Myriad Forms</b></td>
							<td>15th level</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>alter self </i>at will, without expending a spell slot.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.alterself@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Alter Self</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Minions of Chaos</b></td>
							<td>9th level</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>conjure elemental </i>once using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you finish a long rest.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.conjureelemental@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Conjure Elemental</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Mire the Mind</b></td>
							<td>5th level</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>slow </i>once using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you finish a long rest.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.slow@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Slow</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Misty Visions</b></td>
							<td>-</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>silent image </i>at will, without expending a spell slot or material components.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.silentimage@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Silent Image</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>One with Shadows</b></td>
							<td>5th level</td>
							<td colspan="5">When you are in an area of dim light or darkness, you can use your action to become invisible until you move or take an action or a reaction.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Otherworldly Leap</b></td>
							<td>9th level</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>jump </i>on yourself at will, without expending a spell slot or material components.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.jump@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Jump</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Repelling Blast</b></td>
							<td>eldritch blast cantrip</td>
							<td colspan="5">When you hit a creature with eldritch blast, you can push the creature up to 10 feet away from you in a straight line.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.eldritchblast@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Eldritch Blast</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Sculptor of Flesh</b></td>
							<td>7th level</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>polymorph </i>once using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you finish a long rest.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.polymorph@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Polymorph</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Sign of Ill Omen</b></td>
							<td>5th level</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>bestow curse </i>once using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you finish a long rest.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.bestowcurse@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Bestow Curse</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Thief of Five Fates</b></td>
							<td>-</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>bane </i>once using a warlock spell slot. You can't do so again until you finish a long rest.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.bane@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Bane</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Thirsting Blade</b></td>
							<td>5th level, Pact of the Blade feature</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can attack with your pact weapon twice, instead of once, whenever you take the Attack action on your turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Visions of Distant Realms</b></td>
							<td>15th level</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>arcane eye </i>at will, without expending a spell slot.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.arcaneeye@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Arcane Eye</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Voice of the Chain Master</b></td>
							<td>Pact of the Chain feature</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can communicate telepathically with your familiar and perceive through your familiar's senses as long as you are on the same plane of existence. Additionally, while perceiving through your familiar's senses, you can also speak through your familiar in your own voice, even if your familiar is normally incapable of speech.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Whispers of the Grave</b></td>
							<td>9th level</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can cast <i>speak with dead </i>at will, without expending a spell slot.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.speakwithdead@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Speak with Dead</linklist>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Witch Sight</b></td>
							<td>15th level</td>
							<td colspan="5">You can see the true form of any shapechanger or creature concealed by illusion or transmutation magic while the creature is within 30 feet of you and within line of sight.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Pact Boon - Pact of the Tome</name>
				<source type="string">Warlock</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level, your otherworldly patron bestows a gift upon you for your loyal service. You gain one of the following features of your choice.</p>
					<h>Pact of the Chain</h>
					<p>You learn the <i>find familiar </i>spell and can cast it as a ritual. The spell doesn't count against your number of spells known.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="spell.findfamiliar@DD PHB Deluxe"><b>Spell: </b></link>Find Familiar</linklist>
					<p>When you cast the spell, you can choose one of the normal forms for your familiar or one of the following special forms: imp, pseudodragon, quasit, or sprite. Additionally, when you take the Attack action, you can forgo one of your own attacks to allow your familiar to make one attack of its own. When you let your familiar attack, it does so with its reaction.</p>
					<h>Pact of the Blade</h>
					<p>You can use your action to create a pact weapon in your empty hand. You can choose the form that this melee weapon takes each time you create it (see chapter 5 for weapon options). You are proficient with it while you wield it. This weapon counts as magical for the purpose of overcoming resistance and immunity to nonmagical attacks and damage.</p>
					<p>Your pact weapon disappears if it is more than 5 feet away from you for 1 minute or more. It also disappears if you use this feature again, if you dismiss the weapon (no action required), or if you die.</p>
					<p>You can transform one magic weapon into your pact weapon by performing a special ritual while you hold the weapon. You perform the ritual over the course of 1 hour, which can be done during a short rest.</p>
					<p>You can then dismiss the weapon, shunting it into an extra dimensional space, and it appears whenever you create your pact weapon thereafter. You can't affect an artifact or a sentient weapon in this way. The weapon ceases being your pact weapon if you die, if you perform the 1-hour ritual on a different weapon, or if you use a 1-hour ritual to break your bond to it. The weapon appears at your feet if it is in the extra dimensional space when the bond breaks.</p>
					<h>Pact of the Tome</h>
					<p>Your patron gives you a grimoire called a Book of Shadows. When you gain this feature, choose three cantrips from any class's spell list. While the book is on your person, you can cast those cantrips at will. They don't count against your number of cantrips known. Any cantrip you cast with this feature is considered a warlock cantrip for you.</p>
					<p>If you lose your Book of Shadows, you can perform a 1-hour ceremony to receive a replacement from your patron. This ceremony can be performed during a short or long rest, and it destroys the previous book. The book turns to ash when you die.</p>
					<h>Your Pact Boon</h>
					<p>Each Pact Boon option produces a special creature or an object that reflects your patron's nature.</p>
					<p><b>Pact of the Chain. </b>Your familiar is more cunning than a typical familiar. Its default form can be a reflection of your patron, with sprites and pseudodragons tied to the Archfey and imps and quasits tied to the Fiend. Because the Great Old One's nature is inscrutable, any familiar form is suitable for it.</p>
					<p><b>Pact of the Blade. </b>If your patron is the Archfey, your weapon might be a slender blade wrapped in leafy vines. If you serve the Fiend, your weapon could be an axe made of black metal and adorned with decorative flames. If your patron is the Great Old One, your weapon might be an ancient-looking spear, with a gemstone embedded in its head, carved to look like a terrible unblinking eye.</p>
					<p><b>Pact of the Tome. </b>Your Book of Shadows might be a fine, gilt-edged tome with spells of enchantment and illusion, gifted to you by the lordly Archfey. It could be a weighty tome bound in demon hide studded with iron, holding spells of conjuration and a wealth of forbidden lore about the sinister regions of the cosmos, a gift of the Fiend. Or it could be the tattered diary of a lunatic driven mad by contact with the Great Old One, holding scraps of spells that only your own burgeoning insanity allows you to understand and cast.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<source type="string">Warlock</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability s cores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I harbor dark, bloodthirsty thoughts that my isolation and meditation failed to quell.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">3'5&#34;</height>
		<hp>
			<deathsavefail type="number">1</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">26</total>
			<wounds type="number">26</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Self-Knowledge. If you know yourself, there's nothing left to know. (Any)</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">0</total>
		</initiative>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<ac type="number">11</ac>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Made from supple and thin materials, light armor favors agile adventurers since it offers some protection without sacrificing mobility. If you wear light armor, you add your Dexterity modifier to the base number from your armor type to determine your Armor Class.</p>
					<p>The breastplate and shoulder protectors of this armor are made of leather that has been stiffened by being boiled in oil. The rest of the armor is made of softer and more flexible materials.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">Yes</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Leather</name>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Light Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 slashing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Handaxe</name>
				<properties type="string">Light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Common</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A book might contain poetry, historical accounts, information pertaining to a particular field of lore, diagrams and notes on gnomish contraptions, or just about anything else that can be represented using text or pictures. A book of spells is a spellbook (described later in this section).</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Book of Shadows (Tome of Flames)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This kit contains a variety of instruments such as clippers, mortar and pestle, and pouches and vials used by herbalists to create remedies and potions. Proficiency with this kit lets you add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make to identify or apply herbs. Also, proficiency with this kit is required to create antitoxin and potions of healing.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Belt</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Herbalism Kit</name>
				<subtype type="string">Kits / Sets</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A component pouch is a small, watertight leather belt pouch that has compartments to hold all the material components and other special items you need to cast your spells, except for those components that have a specific cost (as indicated in a spell's description).</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Belt</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Component Pouch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">3</count>
				<damage type="string">1d4 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Belt</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light, thrown (range 20/60)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This cylindrical leather case can hold up to ten rolled-up sheets of paper or five rolled-up sheets of parchment.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Belt</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Case, Full of Notes</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">10</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Parchment (One Sheet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.02</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Belt</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Knife (Small)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.25</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ink Pen</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.02</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ink (1-ounce Bottle)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.06</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A book might contain poetry, historical accounts, information pertaining to a particular field of lore, diagrams and notes on gnomish contraptions, or just about anything else that can be represented using text or pictures. A book of spells is a spellbook (described later in this section).</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Book of Lore</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Blanket</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<location type="string">Backpack</location>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bag (Sand)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.05</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">501 - 5,000 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 slashing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="imagewindow" recordname="image.img_beserker_axe_jpg@*"><b>Image: </b></link>Berserker Axe</linklist>
					<p>You gain a +1 bonus to attack and damage rolls made with this magic weapon. In addition, while you are attuned to this weapon, your hit point maximum increases by 1 for each level you have attained.</p>
					<p><b><i>Curse. </i></b>This axe is cursed, and becoming attuned to it extends the curse to you. As long as you remain cursed, you are unwilling to part with the axe, keeping it within reach at all times. You also have disadvantage on attack rolls with weapons other than this one, unless no foe is within 60 feet of you that you can see or hear.</p>
					<p>Whenever a hostile creature damages you while the axe is in your possession, you must succeed on a DC 15 Wisdom saving throw or go berserk. While berserk, you must use your action each round to attack the creature nearest to you with the axe. If you can make extra attacks as part of the Attack action, you use those extra attacks, moving to attack the next nearest creature after you fell your current target. If you have multiple possible targets, you attack one at random. You are berserk until you start your turn with no creatures within 60 feet of you that you can see or hear.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">0</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Berserker Battleaxe</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Majestic Battleaxe</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">This axe is clearly of Dwarven origin and bears all the hallmarks of the quality you would expect from that race. There are some strange runes along the shaft and on the blade.</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10), magic</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Rare (Requires Attunement)</rarity>
				<spells>
					<id-00001>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class></class>
							<recordname></recordname>
						</link>
						<name type="string">Berserker Axe</name>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class></class>
							<recordname></recordname>
						</link>
						<name type="string">Battleaxe</name>
					</id-00002>
				</spells>
				<subtype type="string">Battleaxe</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<name type="string">Small vial of deathroot antidote</name>
				<weight type="number">0.5</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>cold forged (grown) pins from a sprillon</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">0</isidentified>
				<name type="string">Iron pins</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">iron pin</nonid_name>
				<weight type="number">0.1</weight>
			</id-00019>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Common</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Gnomish</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Abyssal</name>
			</id-00003>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">4</level>
		<name type="string">Doris</name>
		<notes type="string">Doris is shrunk to tiny size for 2 days.\nMagic potion reduced charisma 7</notes>
		<perception type="number">11</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I'm oblivious to etiquette and social expectations.</personalitytraits>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">Spells (Tome)</name>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
				<name type="string">Eldritch Invocations</name>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
			</id-00003>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">2</max>
				<used type="number">2</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">combat</powermode>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8,d8,d8</dice>
								<type type="string">thunder</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a chip of mica)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A sudden loud ringing noise, painfully intense, erupts from a point of your choice within range. Each creature in a 10-foot-radius sphere centered on that point must make a Constitution saving throw. A creature takes 3d8 thunder damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one. A creature made of inorganic material such as stone, crystal, or metal has disadvantage on this saving throw.</p>
					<p>A nonmagical object that isn't being worn or carried also takes the damage if it's in the spell's area.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shatter</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric Tempest Domain, Eldritch Knight, Monk, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create three rays of fire and hurl them at targets within range. You can hurl them at one target or several. Make a ranged spell attack for each ray. On a hit, the target takes 2d6 fire damage.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you create one additional ray for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Scorching Ray</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric Light Domain, Eldritch Knight, Warlock (Fiend), Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You speak a one-word command to a creature you can see within range. The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or follow the command on its next turn. The spell has no effect if the target is undead, if it doesn't understand your language, or if your command is directly harmful to it.</p>
					<p>Some typical commands and their effects follow. You might issue a command other than one described here. If you do so, the DM determines how the target behaves. If the target can't follow your command, the spell ends.</p>
					<p><b>Approach. </b>The target moves toward you by the shortest and most direct route, ending its turn if it moves within 5 feet of you.</p>
					<p><b>Drop. </b>The target drops whatever it is holding and then ends its turn.</p>
					<p><b>Flee. </b>The target spends its turn moving away from you by the fastest available means.</p>
					<p><b>Grovel. </b>The target falls prone and then ends its turn.</p>
					<p><b>Halt. </b>The target doesn't move and takes no actions. A flying creature stays aloft, provided that it is able to do so. If it must move to stay aloft, it flies the minimum distance needed to remain in the air.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can affect one additional creature for each slot level above 1st. The creatures must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Command</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Cleric Knowledge Domain, Warlock (Fiend), Paladin</source>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<onmissdamage type="string">half</onmissdamage>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00003>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6,d6,d6,d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00003>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>As you hold your hands with thumbs touching and fingers spread, a thin sheet of flames shoots forth from your outstretched fingertips. Each creature in a 15-foot cone must make a Dexterity saving throw. A creature takes 3d6 fire damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.</p>
					<p>The fire ignites any flammable objects in the area that aren't being worn or carried.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Burning Hands</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self (15-foot cone)</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric Light Domain, Eldritch Knight, Warlock (Fiend), Monk, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Mage Hand 30ft</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A spectral, floating hand appears at a point you choose within range. The hand lasts for the duration or until you dismiss it as an action. The hand vanishes if it is ever more than 30 feet away from you or if you cast this spell again.</p>
					<p>You can use your action to control the hand. You can use the hand to manipulate an object, open an unlocked door or container, stow or retrieve an item from an open container, or pour the contents out of a vial. You can move the hand up to 30 feet each time you use it.</p>
					<p>The hand can't attack, activate magic items, or carry more than 10 pounds.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Mage Hand</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">RESIST: bludgeoning,piercing,slashing</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You extend your hand and trace a sigil of warding in the air. Until the end of your next turn, you have resistance against bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing damage dealt by weapon attacks.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Blade Ward</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Abjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A flickering flame appears in your hand. The flame remains there for the duration and harms neither you nor your equipment. The flame sheds bright light in a 10-foot radius and dim light for an additional 10 feet. The spell ends if you dismiss it as an action or if you cast it again.</p>
					<p>You can also attack with the flame, although doing so ends the spell. When you cast this spell, or as an action on a later turn, you can hurl the flame at a creature within 30 feet of you. Make a ranged spell attack. On a hit, the target takes 1d8 fire damage.</p>
					<p>This spell's damage increases by 1d8 when you reach 5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Tome)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Produce Flame</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d10</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You hurl a mote of fire at a creature or object within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes 1d10 fire damage. A flammable object hit by this spell ignites if it isn't being worn or carried.</p>
					<p>This spell's damage increases by 1d10 when you reach 5th level (2d10), 11th level (3d10), and 17th level (4d10).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Tome)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fire Bolt</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Dancing Lights 10ft; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a bit of phosphorus or wychwood, or a glowworm)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create up to four torch-sized lights within range, making them appear as torches, lanterns, or glowing orbs that hover in the air for the duration. You can also combine the four lights into one glowing vaguely humanoid form of Medium size. Whichever form you choose, each light sheds dim light in a 10-foot radius.</p>
					<p>As a bonus action on your turn, you can move the lights up to 60 feet to a new spot within range. A light must be within 20 feet of another light created by this spell, and a light winks out if it exceeds the spell's range.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Tome)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Dancing Lights</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can read all writing.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Eldritch Invocations</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Eyes of the Rune Keeper</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Invocations</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Detect Magic 30ft; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any.</p>
					<p>The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Eldritch Invocations</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Eldritch Sight (Detect Magic)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Eldritch Knight, Eldritch Invocations, Paladin, Ranger, Sorcerer, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
							</id-00001>
							<id-00002>
								<stat type="string">warlock</stat>
							</id-00002>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<healtype type="string">temp</healtype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">Dark One's Blessing</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<shortdescription type="string">Reset every level</shortdescription>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">Produce Flame of Whispers</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<name type="string">Produce Flame of Muffled Laughter</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This spell is a minor magical trick that novice spellcasters use for practice. You create one of the following magical effects within range:</p>
					<list>
						<li>You create an instantaneous, harmless sensory effect, such as a shower of sparks, a puff of wind, faint musical notes, or an odd odor.</li>
						<li>You instantaneously light or snuff out a candle, a torch, or a small campfire.</li>
						<li>You instantaneously clean or soil an object no larger than 1 cubic foot.</li>
						<li>You chill, warm, or flavor up to 1 cubic foot of nonliving material for 1 hour.</li>
						<li>You make a color, a small mark, or a symbol appear on an object or a surface for 1 hour.</li>
						<li>You create a nonmagical trinket or an illusory image that can fit in your hand and that lasts until the end of your next turn.</li>
					</list>
					<p>If you cast this spell multiple times, you can have up to three of its non-instantaneous effects active at a time, and you can dismiss such an effect as an action.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Prestidigitation</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">10 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Paralyzed; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a small, straight piece of iron)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose a humanoid that you can see within range.</p>
					<p>The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be paralyzed for the duration. At the end of each of its turns, the target can make another Wisdom saving throw. On a success, the spell ends on the target.</p>
					<p><b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, you can target one additional humanoid for each slot level above 2nd. The humanoids must be within 30 feet of each other when you target them.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hold Person</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Druid, Druid Arctic Circle, Eldritch Knight, Monk, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00016>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">2</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Tool: Herbalism kit</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple weapons</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Armor: Light armor</name>
			</id-00003>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Rock Gnome</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.gnome@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<senses type="string">Darkvision 60</senses>
		<size type="string">tiny</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History (Artificer's Lore)</name>
				<prof type="number">2</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<linklist>
						<link class="ref_ability" recordname="....traitlist.id-00002">Artificer's Lore</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
				<total type="number">7</total>
			</id-00019>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">25</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">25</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00034_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Gnome Cunning</name>
				<source type="string">Gnome</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have advantage on all Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma saving throws against magic.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Artificer's Lore</name>
				<source type="string">Rock Gnome</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Whenever you make an Intelligence (History) check related to magic items, alchemical objects, or technological devices, you can add twice your proficiency bonus, instead of any proficiency bonus you normally apply.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinker</name>
				<source type="string">Rock Gnome</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have proficiency with artisan's tools (tinker's tools). Using those tools, you can spend 1 hour and 10 gp worth of materials to construct a Tiny clockwork device (AC 5, 1 hp). The device ceases to function after 24 hours, or when you use your action to dismantle it; at that time, you can reclaim the materials used to create it. You can have up to three such devices active at a time.</p>
					<p>When you create a device, choose one of the following options.</p>
					<p>Clockwork Toy. This toy is a clockwork animal or person, such as a frog, mouse, bird, or soldier. When placed on the ground, the toy moves 5 feet across the ground on each of your turns in a random direction. It makes noises as appropriate to the creature it represents.</p>
					<p>Fire Starter. The device produces a miniature flame, which you can use to light a candle, torch, or campfire. Using the device requires your action.</p>
					<p>Music Box. When opened, this music box plays a single song at a moderate volume. The box stops playing when it reaches the song's end or when it is closed.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">subracial</type>
			</id-00003>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">slashing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Handaxe</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00002</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">slashing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">1</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Handaxe</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00002</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00007</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">3</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Dagger</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00007</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">slashing,magic</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">0</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">** Majestic Battleaxe **</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00017</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00005>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">40 lb</weight>
	</character>
</root>
