<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:3">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">-1</bonus>
				<save type="number">-1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">8</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">13</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">3</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">17</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">12</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">4</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<save type="number">0</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">11</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<adventurelist>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">23</age>
		<alignment type="string">Neutral Good</alignment>
		<appearance type="string">Hailing from the boundless vista of the Elemental Plane of Air, the Aarakocra, or &#34;bird folk&#34;, evoke fear and wonder.\n\nKreek, a notable young Sky Warden, was a prideful Aarakocra with brilliant white and grey covert plumage across his head, back and chest contrasting his flight feathers and thighs which were as black as onyx. Having nothing but pity for those earthbound people forced to live and toil on the ground, deemed himself superior to those of the Material Plane.\nSuch as it was, until it was not...\nThe Aarakocras sworn foe, Ogr&#233;moch, Prince of Elemental Earth, sent hordes of Gargoyles to destroy the Aarakocra Kingdom. During the battles that raged across the Elemental Planes of Earth and Air, the Gargoyles managed to push into a settlement. Kreek, stationed there for the final duration of his admittance into the Sky Wardens, attempted to protect the inhabitants until a defence legion could reach them.\n\nIn battle, he proved a dynamic and acrobatic flier, moving with remarkable speed and grace. Then as quickly as it began, it ended. A Gargoyle slammed into Kreek, nearly knocking him unconscious from the blow. They grappled, each trying to overcome the other falling through the sky. Kreek landed a fatal hit with his talons but not before the Gargoyle mangled his wing.\n\nHe awoke in this world under the care of those he would look upon with pity. Although they managed to mend his wounds, his wing was crippled and it was he who was now looked upon with pity.\n\nConfinement terrifies the Aarakocra. To be grounded, trapped underground, or imprisoned by the cold, unyielding earth is a torment few Aarakocra can withstand.\n---------\nKreek left his pride with his kin in the Elemental Plane, although he normally stood 5'7, he rarely did. Hunched over with his wings tucked under his cloak, he could be easily mistaken for a Halfling. His hood, drawn nearly over his eyes, hid the featherless red face only exposing the yellow facial trim which highlighted his hooked bill. Noticeably once Obsidian, his beak now was weathered and worn to a dull blue-grey. It's been 20 years since his injury, during which time he spent as an outcast, using his martial skill to live as a freelance sword for hire.</appearance>
		<background type="string">Sword for Hire</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class></class>
			<recordname></recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">I protect those who cannot protect themselves.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">0</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">d10</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<name type="string">Fighter</name>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.fighter@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
				</shortcut>
			</id-00001>
		</classes>
		<coins>
			<slot1>
				<amount type="number">15</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</slot1>
			<slot2>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</slot2>
			<slot3>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</slot3>
			<slot4>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot4>
			<slot5>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot5>
			<slot6>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
			</slot6>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">1</armor>
				<disstealth type="number">0</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">0</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">14</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<deity type="string">N/A</deity>
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">70</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">140</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">420</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">58.25</load>
			<max type="number">210</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">340</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">400</expneeded>
		<featlist>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">CS Maneuver 1: Distracting Strike</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to distract the creature, giving your allies an opening. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll. The next attack roll against the target by an attacker other then you has advantage if the attack is made before the start of your next turn.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Second Wind</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have a limited well of stamina that you can draw on to protect yourself from harm. On your turn, you can use a bonus action to regain hit points equal to 1d10 + your fighter level. Once you use this feature, you must finish a short or long rest before you can use it again.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style: Two-Weapon Fighting</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You adopt a particular style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the following options. You can't take a Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.</p>
					<p>Two-Weapon Fighting</p>
					<p>When you engage in two-weapon fighting, you can add your ability modifier to the damage of the second attack.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Action Surge</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, you can push yourself beyond your normal limits for a moment. On your turn, you can take one additional action on top of your regular action and a possible bonus action.</p>
					<p>Once you use this feature, you must finish a short or long rest before you can use it again. Starting at 17th level, you can use it twice before a rest, but only once on the same turn.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">CS Maneuver 2: Trip Attack</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to knock the target down. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and if the target is large or smaller, it must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, you knock the target prone.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">CS Maneuver 3: Riposte</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When a creature misses you with a melee attack, you can use your reaction and expend one superiority die to make a melee weapon attack against the creature. If you hit, you add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Background: Mercenary Life</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You know the mercenary life as only someone who has experienced it can. You are able to identify mercenary companies by their emblems, and you know a little about any such company, including the names and reputations of its commanders and leaders, and who has hired them recently. You can find the taverns and festhalls where mercenaries abide in any area, as long as you speak the language. You can find mercenary work between adventures sufficient to maintain a comfortable lifestyle</p>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Battle Master</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Those who emulate the archetypal Battle Master employ martial techniques passed down through generations. To a Battle Master, combat is an academic field, sometimes including subjects beyond battle such as weapon smithing and calligraphy. Not every fighter absorbs the lessons of history, theory, and artistry that are reflected in the Battle Master archetype, but those who do are well-rounded fighters of great skill and knowledge.</p>
					<h>Features</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.combatsuperiority3@DD PHB Deluxe">Combat Superiority</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.studentofwar3@DD PHB Deluxe">Student of War</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.knowyourenemy7@DD PHB Deluxe">Know Your Enemy</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.improvedcombatsuperiority10@DD PHB Deluxe">Improved Combat Superiority</link>
						<link class="reference_classfeature" recordname="reference.classdata.fighter.features.relentless15@DD PHB Deluxe">Relentless</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Student of War: Smith</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specialization type="string">Battle Master</specialization>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 3rd level, you gain proficiency with one type of artisan's tools of your choice.</p>
					<p>Chosen: Smith</p>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Combat Superiority</name>
				<source type="string">Fighter</source>
				<specialization type="string">Battle Master</specialization>
				<specializationchoice type="number">0</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you choose this archetype at 3rd level, you learn maneuvers that are fueled by special dice called superiority dice.</p>
					<p><b>Maneuvers. </b>You learn three maneuvers of your choice, which are detailed under &#34;Maneuvers&#34; below. Many maneuvers enhance an attack in some way. You can use only one maneuver per attack.</p>
					<p>You learn two additional maneuvers of your choice at 7th, 10th, and 15th level. Each time you learn new maneuvers, you can also replace one maneuver you know with a different one.</p>
					<p><b>Maneuvers</b></p>
					<p>The maneuvers are presented in alphabetical order.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Maneuver</b></td>
							<td colspan="3"><b>Description</b></td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Commander's Strike</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you take the Attack action on your turn, you can forgo one of your attacks and use a bonus action to direct one of your companions to strike. When you do so, choose a friendly creature who can see or hear you and expend one superiority die. That creature can immediately use its reaction to make one weapon attack, adding the superiority die to the attack's damage roll.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Disarming Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to disarm the target, forcing it to drop one item of your choice that it's holding. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and the target must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, it drops the object you choose. The object lands at its feet.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Distracting Strike</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to distract the creature, giving your allies an opening. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll. The next attack roll against the target by an attacker other than you has advantage if the attack is made before the start of your next turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Evasive Footwork</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you move, you can expend one superiority die, rolling the die and adding the number rolled to your AC until you stop moving.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Feinting Attack.</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">You can expend one superiority die and use a bonus action on your turn to feint, choosing one creature within 5 feet of you as your target. You have advantage on your next attack roll against that creature. If that attack hits, add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll. The advantage is lost if not used on the turn you gain it.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Goading Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to goad the target into attacking you. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and the target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, the target has disadvantage on all attack rolls against targets other than you until the end of your next turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Lunging Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you make a melee weapon attack on your turn, you can expend one superiority die to increase your reach for that attack by 5 feet. If you hit, you add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Maneuvering Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to maneuver one of your comrades into a more advantageous position. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and you choose a friendly creature who can see or hear you. That creature can use its reaction to move up to half its speed without provoking opportunity attacks from the target of your attack.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Menacing Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to frighten the target. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and the target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, it is frightened of you until the end of your next turn.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Parry</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When another creature damages you with a melee attack, you can use your reaction and expend one superiority die to reduce the damage by the number you roll on your superiority die + your Dexterity modifier.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Precision Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you make a weapon attack roll against a creature, you can expend one superiority die to add it to the roll. You can use this maneuver before or after making the attack roll, but before any effects of the attack are applied.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Pushing Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to drive the target back. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and if the target is Large or smaller, it must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, you push the target up to 15 feet away from you.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Rally</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">On your turn, you can use a bonus action and expend one superiority die to bolster the resolve of one of your companions. When you do so, choose a friendly creature who can see or hear you. That creature gains temporary hit points equal to the superiority die roll + your Charisma modifier.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Riposte</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When a creature misses you with a melee attack, you can use your reaction and expend one superiority die to make a melee weapon attack against the creature. If you hit, you add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Sweeping Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to damage another creature with the same attack. Choose another creature within 5 feet of the original target and within your reach. If the original attack roll would hit the second creature, it takes damage equal to the number you roll on your superiority die. The damage is of the same type dealt by the original attack.</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td><b>Trip Attack</b></td>
							<td colspan="3">When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to knock the target down. You add the superiority die to the attack's damage roll, and if the target is Large or smaller, it must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, you knock the target prone.</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
					<p><b>Superiority Dice. </b>You have four superiority dice, which are d8s. A superiority die is expended when you use it. You regain all of your expended superiority dice when you finish a short or long rest.</p>
					<p>You gain another superiority die at 7th level and one more at 15th level.</p>
					<p><b>Saving Throws. </b>Some of your maneuvers require your target to make a saving throw to resist the maneuver's effects. The saving throw DC is calculated as follows:</p>
					<p><b>Maneuver save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Strength or Dexterity modifier (your choice)</p>
				</text>
			</id-00010>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">I judge others harshly, and myself even more severely.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Male</gender>
		<height type="string">5'7&#34;</height>
		<hp>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">25</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Fastidious about his plumage, he frequently tends to his feathers and equipment.</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">3</total>
		</initiative>
		<inspiration type="number">0</inspiration>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<ac type="number">11</ac>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Made from supple and thin materials, light armor favors agile adventurers since it offers some protection without sacrificing mobility. If you wear light armor, you add your Dexterity modifier to the base number from your armor type to determine your Armor Class.</p>
					<p>The breastplate and shoulder protectors of this armor are made of leather that has been stiffened by being boiled in oil. The rest of the armor is made of softer and more flexible materials.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">Yes</dexbonus>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Leather</name>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Light Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">50 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Longbow</name>
				<properties type="string">Ammunition (range 150/600), heavy, two-handed</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Ranged Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Arrows (20)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Ammunition</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 piercing</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shortsword</name>
				<properties type="string">Finesse, light</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Piton</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.25</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Rations consist of dry foods suitable for extended travel, including jerky, dried fruit, hardtack, and nuts.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rations (1 Day)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Waterskin</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Backpack (Empty)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Hammer</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A torch burns for 1 hour, providing bright light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional 20 feet. If you make a melee attack with a burning torch and hit, it deals 1 fire damage.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Torch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>This small container holds flint, fire steel, and tinder (usually dry cloth soaked in light oil) used to kindle a fire. Using it to light a torch-or anything else with abundant, exposed fuel-takes an action. Lighting any other fire takes 1 minute.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tinderbox</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Using a crowbar grants advantage to Strength checks where the crowbar's leverage can be applied.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Crowbar</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">1 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Rope, Hempen (50 Feet)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00015>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 bludgeoning</damage>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Quarterstaff</name>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d8)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>These special tools include the items needed to pursue a craft or trade. The table shows examples of the most common types of tools, each providing items related to a single craft. Proficiency with a set of artisan's tools lets you add your proficiency bonus to any ability checks you make using the tools in your craft. Each type of artisan's tools requires a separate proficiency.</p>
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Leatherworker's Tools</name>
				<subtype type="string">Artisan's Tools</subtype>
				<type type="string">Tools</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00016>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">You can speak, read and write Dwarvish.</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">You can speak, read, and write Common, Aarakocra and Auran.</name>
			</id-00002>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">3</level>
		<name type="string">Kreek</name>
		<perception type="number">12</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">I have a strong code of honor or sense of propriety that others don't comprehend. I can stare down a hell hound without flinching\n</personalitytraits>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powermode type="string">standard</powermode>
		<powers>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">2</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple weapons, martial weapons</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Armor: All armor, shields</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Tools: Leatherworker, Smith</name>
			</id-00003>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Aarakocra</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.aarakocra@DD Elemental Evil Players Companion</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">5</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">-1</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">0</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">25</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">25</total>
		</speed>
		<temp>
		</temp>
		<token type="token">portrait_id-00038_token</token>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Talons</name>
				<source type="string">Aarakocra</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You are proficient with your unarmed strikes, which deal 1d4 slashing damage on a hit.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Language</name>
				<source type="string">Aarakocra</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You can speak, read, and write Common, Aarakocra, and Auran.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Flight</name>
				<source type="string">Aarakocra</source>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You have a flying speed of 50 feet. To use this speed, you can't be wearing medium or heavy armor.</p>
				</text>
				<type type="string">racial</type>
			</id-00003>
		</traitlist>
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">20</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Longbow</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00002</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">1</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<attackstat type="string">dexterity</attackstat>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Shortsword</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00004</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">bludgeoning</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Quarterstaff</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00015</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00003>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">110lb</weight>
	</character>
</root>
